<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>原标题：“走廊医生”兰越峰诉央视主持人王志安名誉侵权一审败诉</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">Original title: “Corridor doctor” Lan Yuefeng loses defamation suit against CCTV host Wang Zhi’an</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">Original title: "Corridor Doctor" Lanne v. CCTV host Wang Zhian reputation infringement first Instance loses</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">The original title: "Corridor Doctor" Lan Yufeng v CCTV presenter Wang Zhian reputation infringement first instance lost</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>法制晚报讯因央视主持人王志安在新浪微博上发表针对“走廊医生”事件的言论，兰越峰将王志安及北京微梦创科网络技术有限公司诉至法院。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">Fawan (legal evening news) reported that Lan Yuefeng has pressed charges against Wang Zhian as well as Beijing Weibo Internet Technology Co., Ltd. for posts published by the China Central Television anchor Wang Zhian on Sina Weibo regarding the “corridor physicians” incident.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">Legal Evening News because CCTV host Wang Zhian on Sina Weibo posted on the "Corridor Doctor" incident speech, Lanne will Wang Zhian and Beijing Micro Dream Network Technology Co., Ltd. to court.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">Lan Yuefeng brought Wang Zhian and Beijing Micro-Dream Network Technology Co., Ltd. to court over comments made by CCTV host Wang Zhian on Sina Weibo in response to the incident involving the "Corridor Doctor."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>昨天下午，海淀法院对该案进行了宣判，判决认定王志安及微梦公司不构成侵权，驳回了兰越峰的全部诉讼请求。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">Yesterday afternoon, Haidian Court pronounced judgment on this case, and ruled that the conduct of Wang Zhi’an and Microdream Co., Ltd. did not constitute infringement, rejecting all the legal claims of Lan Yuefeng.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">Yesterday afternoon, the Haidian court sentenced the case, the decision that Wang Zhian and micro-dream Company does not constitute infringement, rejected Lanne all the litigation request.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">Yesterday afternoon, the Haidian court handed down its verdict in the case, finding that Wang Zhian and Weimeng Company did not constitute infringement and rejecting all the claims of Lan Yuefeng.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2014年初，央视记者王志安调查发现，尽管在医院走廊里坐了600多天的兰越峰被媒体塑造为被体制打压的悲情英雄，但这些报道存在大量不实信息。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">In early 2014, CCTV reporter Wang Zhian found during an investigation that Lan Yuefeng, who had been sitting in the hospital corridor for more than 600 days, have been established by the media as a tragic heroine oppressed by the system. However, many such reports contain a great deal of misinformation.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">At the beginning of 2014, CCTV reporter Wang Zhian survey found that despite more than 600 days in the hospital corridor Lanne was portrayed by the media as a system suppressed the tragic hero, but these reports there is a lot of false information.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">In early 2014, an investigation by CCTV reporter Wang Zhian found that despite the fact that Lan Yuefeng, who had been sitting in a hospital corridor for more than 600 days, was portrayed by the media as a tragic hero crushed by the system, there was a great deal of misinformation in those reports.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2014年3月29日，央视新闻调查制作的《走廊医生》节目播出。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">On March 29, 2014, CCTV News investigated the broadcast of the production of the Corridor Doctor program.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">March 29, 2014, CCTV News survey produced "Corridor Doctor" broadcast.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">The Corridor Doctor programme, produced by the CCTV news investigation, was broadcast on March 29, 2014.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>兰越峰向媒体举报的各种所谓过度医疗的信息，均没有证据支持。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">Lan Yuefeng has informed the media of various so-called excessive medical treatment but has not provided any evidence to substantiate her claims.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">There is no evidence to support the various so-called Lanne medical Information reported to the media.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">Lan Yuefeng reported to the media a variety of so-called excessive medical information, there is no evidence to support it.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>王志安也在实名认证的微博中，描述“兰越峰之所以走到这一步是性格使然、其带有明显的偏执人格等”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">Wang Zhian also posted on a Weibo account that have been verified to his real name that “Lan Yuefeng reached this step partly because of her personality that is characterized by distinctive paranoia.”</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">Wang Zhian also in the real-name certification of the microblog, describing "the reason why Lanne to this step is the character, with obvious paranoid personality, etc.".</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">Wang Zhian also in the real-name authentication of the Twitter account, described "Lan Yue Feng has come to this point because of the character, it has obvious paranoid personality and so on."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>兰越峰提出要求王志安删除微博、向其致歉并赔偿精神损害抚慰金10万元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">Lan Yuefeng demanded Wang Zhian to delete the Weibo posts, apologize to her, and pay a compensation of 100,000 RMB for psychological damage that she has endured.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">Lanne Request Wang Zhian Delete Micro Bo, apologize to him and compensation for spiritual damage consolation gold 100,000 yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">LanYueFeng request WangZhiAn delete microblog, to its apology and compensation for spiritual damage consolation 10 million yuan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在当时的庭审中，双方就王志安是否侵犯了兰越峰的名誉权进行了激辩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.ht">During the court proceedings, both parties engaged in a hot debate whether Wang Zhian violated Lan Yuefeng’s right to reputation.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.gg">During the trial, both sides debated whether Wang Zhian violated Lanne's reputation right.</translation>
    <translation system="069_ifeng0812.news.49765656_0_zh.c6">At the court hearing at the time, the two sides debated whether Wang Zhian had violated Lan Yuefeng's right to reputation.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
