<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>１１日晚，中国国家京剧院携名剧《白蛇传》穿越千里来到墨西哥城，在墨国家美术宫为当地民众呈现了一场原汁原味的京剧盛宴。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">On the night of the 11th, China National Peking Opera Company brought the Legend of the White Snake to Mexico City, presenting a true blue Peking Opera feast to local audiences at the Mexico Palace of Fine Arts.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">11th evening, the Chinese National Opera House with the famous drama "White Snake Biography" traveled thousands of miles to Mexico City, in the Mexican National Art Palace for the local people presented an authentic Beijing opera feast.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">On Monday night, China's National Peking Opera Theater traveled thousands of miles to Mexico City with the famous opera "The Legend of the White Snake" to present an original feast of Beijing opera to local people at Mexico's National Palace of Fine Arts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>作为“中拉文化交流年”重点演出项目，８月９日至２３日，中国国家京剧院在墨西哥首都墨西哥城以及科尔多瓦、华雷斯等５座城市演出７场京剧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">As a key performance item for the China-Latin America Cultural Exchange Year, the China National Peking Opera Company shall provide a total of 7 Peking Opera performances at 5 cities, including Mexico City, the capital of Mexico, Córdoba, and Juárez.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">As a key performance project of the "China-la cultural exchange Year", the National Peking Opera troupe performed 7 Beijing opera in 5 cities, such as Mexico City and Cordoba and Juarez, from August 9 to 23rd.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">As a key performance item of the "Year of Cultural Exchange between China and Latin America," from August 9 to 23, the Chinese National Peking Opera performed seven Peking Opera performances in Mexico City, the capital of Mexico, as well as five cities, including Córdoba and Juarez.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>观众们跟着《白蛇传》情节的起承转合、演员的唱念做打，时而会心微笑，时而热烈鼓掌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">The audience smiled and applauded with the evolving plot and the theatrical performance given by the artistes of the Legend of the White Snake.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">The audience followed the "White Snake biography" plot of the transforms, the actor's singing, sometimes smiled, and sometimes warm applause.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">The audience followed the plot of "The Story of the White Snake" from beginning to end, the actors singing and playing, sometimes with a smile, sometimes with warm applause.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>１５年前曾观看过京剧演出的玛丽萨·希门尼斯·卡乔陪着女儿看完演出。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">Marisa Giménez Cacho, who had watched a Peking Opera performance 15 years ago, accompanied her daughter throughout the entire show.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">玛丽萨·希门尼斯·卡乔, who had watched the performance of Beijing opera 15 years ago, accompanied her daughter.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">Marissa Jimenez Cacho, who had watched the Beijing opera 15 years ago, accompanied her daughter through the show.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这是一场精彩绝伦的表演，音乐、灯光、舞台表演都让我印象深刻，……我觉得很有必要让女儿也来了解中国文化和中国京剧艺术。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">“This was a fantastic performance. The music, lighting and stage performance left an indelible impression on me ...... I feel that it is absolutely necessary for my daughter to also come and understand Chinese culture and the art of Chinese Peking opera.”</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">"This is a wonderful performance, music, lighting, stage performances have impressed me, ... I think it is necessary for my daughter to understand Chinese culture and the art of Chinese opera. ”</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">"It was a brilliant performance, and I was impressed by the music, the lighting and the stage performance... I felt it was necessary for my daughter to learn about Chinese culture and the art of Beijing Opera as well."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>墨西哥观众的热情给白娘子扮演者、青年演员付佳留下深刻印象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">The passion of the Mexican audience left an indelible impression on Fu Jia, the young actress who played the role of Madame White Snake.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">The enthusiasm of the Mexican audience impressed the white snake player, the young actress Shangjia.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">The enthusiasm of the Mexican audience left a deep impression on the young actress Fu Jia, who plays the White Lady.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“我没有想到墨西哥观众这么热情，原本我对他们能否理解故事还有些担心，但是今天看到他们能抓住故事情节和许多笑点，这出乎我的意料。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">“I didn’t realize that the Mexican audience was so passionate. Originally, I was somewhat concerned about whether they would understand the story, but I could see today that they were able to grasp the plot and numerous jokes. I didn't expect that.”</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">"I didn't expect the Mexican audience to be so enthusiastic and I was worried that they could understand the story, but it was a surprise to see them catch the storyline and a lot of laughs today," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">"I didn't expect the Mexican audience to be so enthusiastic. I was a little worried about their ability to understand the story, but today I was surprised to see that they were able to capture the storyline and a lot of laughs."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>中国驻墨西哥大使邱小琪说，今年“中拉文化交流年”的各项文化交流活动对推动中墨两国人民加深了解、增进友谊具有积极作用。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">Qiu Xiaoqi, the Chinese Ambassador to Mexico, said that the various cultural exchange events for the China-Latin America Cultural Exchange Year will play an active role in improving mutual understanding and friendship between the people of China and Mexico.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">The Chinese ambassador to Mexico, Qiu, said that the cultural exchange activities of this year's "China-China Cultural exchange Year" have played a positive role in promoting better understanding and friendship between the Chinese and Mexican peoples.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">Qiu Xiaoqi, Chinese ambassador to Mexico, said that the cultural exchange activities of this year's "Sino-Latin American Year of Cultural Exchange" will play a positive role in promoting greater understanding and friendship between the peoples of China and Mexico.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.sl">
    <source>明年是中墨两国建交４５周年，届时将会有更多文化交流活动在中墨两国举办。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.ht">Next year is the 45th anniversary for the establishment of official diplomatic ties between China and Mexico. Additional cultural exchanges and events will be held in two countries.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.gg">Next year is the 45 anniversary of the establishment of diplomatic ties between China and Mexico, and more cultural exchanges will be held in China and Mexico.</translation>
    <translation system="095_ifeng0812.news.49768283_0_zh.c6">Next year marks the 45th anniversary of the establishment of diplomatic relations between China and Mexico, when more cultural exchange events will be held in the two countries.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
