<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>今日19点35分，在中超第22轮率先开打的一场比赛中，重庆力帆客场挑战北京国安。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">On 19:35 today, Chongqing Dangdai Lifan will play away against Beijing Sinobo Guoan in one of the first matches of the 22nd round of the Chinese Super League.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">At 19:35 today, in the 22nd round of the first in the Super game, Chongqing Lifan away to challenge Beijing Guoan.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">At 19: 35 today, Chongqing Lifan challenged Beijing Guoan in the first match of the 22nd round of the Chinese Super League.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第29分钟，王栋操刀点球破门，第39分钟，新援卡尔德克在费尔南多助攻下收获中超首球，第81分钟，国安扳回一球。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">At the 29th minute, Wang Dong scored a goal with a penalty kick. At the 39th minute, the newly fielded Kardec, assisted by Fernando, scored his first goal in the Chinese Super League. At minute 81, the Guoan team managed to score a goal.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">The first 29 minutes, dong Fencing penalty break, the first 39 minutes, the new Caldech in Fernando assists in the harvest of the first ball, 81 minutes, Guoan to recover a goal.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">In the 29th minute, Wang Dong opened the scoring with a penalty, and in the 39th minute, new signing Caldecott scored the first goal of the Chinese Super League with an assist from Fernando, and in the 81st minute, Guoan pulled one back.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>比赛进行10分钟后，力帆连续冲击中连获角球机会，费尔南多小角度抽射被国安防线挡出底线。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">After the game was on for 10 minutes, Lifan continued to press their offense and won multiple corner kick opportunities. Fernando attempted a small-angle volley strike that was kept out of the endline by Guoan defenses.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">10 minutes after the match, Lifan continued to hit the corner of the opportunity, Fernando Small angle volley by the security line to block the bottom line.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">Ten minutes after the game, the power sails in a row to win a corner, Fernando small angle volley by the national security defensive line off the line.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第15分钟，张稀哲中场直线挑传，伊尔马兹已直冲禁区，单兵防守的刘宇抢先出脚将球破坏。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">In the 15th minute, Zhang Xize crossed in midfield with Yilmaz having already rushed into the penalty box, but lone defender Liu Yu kicked the ball away.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">The first 15 minutes, Zhang dilute Zhe midfield straight pick, Ilmaz has been straight to the restricted area, the Liu preemptive foot to the ball damage.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">In the 15th minute, Zhang Ranzhe midfield straight through, Ilmaz has been straight into the penalty area, the individual defense of Liu Yu rushed out to destroy the ball.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>1分钟后朴成在左路前插传中，于大宝禁区中路扫射未踢正部位，力帆门将邓小飞将球没收。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">After 1 minute, Piao Cheng managed to work his way in from the left. Yu Dabao made a sweeping shot at the goal within the penalty area but missed the shot. Deng Xiaofei, the goalkeeper of Lifan, managed to keep the ball safe in his custody.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">1 minutes later Park Cheng in the left before inserting crosses, in the Grand Treasure area of the middle of the road shooting not kicking, Lifan goalkeeper Deng will the ball confiscated.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">A minute later Park Cheng in the left in front of the cross, in the middle of the box Dabao strafing did not kick the right part of the force sails goalkeeper Deng Xiaoping to confiscate the ball.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>费尔南多右路一对二回带后突然挑传门前，卡尔德克前插接应时被雷腾龙飞扑动作放倒，裁判判定点球，并向雷腾龙出示黄牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">Fernando struck from the right, back passing when faced with two defenders before suddenly launching a pick pass to the goal area. Kardec rushed forward through the defense but was floored by Lei Tenglong’s flying tackle. The referee rewarded Kardec with a penalty kick and gave Lei Tenglong with a yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">Fernando right a pair of two back to the front of a sudden pick up the door, Caldech before inserting the Rethen Dragon flying flapping action, the referee decided the penalty, and to Retenron show yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">Fernando right after a pair of two back with a sudden pick in front of the ball, Caldecker before the plug was put down by Leitenglong flying action, the referee awarded a penalty, and to Leitenglong showed yellow card.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>国安在第37分钟就进行换人调整，张晓彬下场，张池明登场反戈旧主。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">Guoan swapped out a player in the 37th minute. Zhang Xiaobin was replaced by Chang Chiming to defy his ex-team.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">Guoan in the first 37 minutes on the substitution adjustment, Zhang Xiaobin fate, Zhang Zhiming debut fange old Master.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">Guoan in the 37th minute on the replacement adjustment, ZhangXiaoBin off, ZhangChiming stage anti-Ge old master.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>卡尔德克禁区前摆脱分球，费尔南多禁区左侧低平球传中，卡尔德克顺势推射破门。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">Kardec broke away and crossed in front of the penalty area. Fernando sent a low shot from the left, and Kardec conveniently shot the ball in for a goal.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">Caldech to get rid of the ball before the penalty box, Fernando on the left side of the restricted ball crosses, Caldech homeopathy push break.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">Caldech got rid of the tiebreaker in front of the penalty area, Fernando passed the ball low on the left side of the penalty area and Caldecker pushed the ball down the line to break it.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这也是卡尔德克在中超首发的赛事中就取得入球，力帆2:0领先。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">This is the goal by Kardec in his first CSL game. Lifan leads by 2:0.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">This is also Caldech in the super start of the tournament scored scored, Lifan 2:0 lead.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">It was also Caldecott's goal in the opening event of the Chinese Super League, with Lifan leading 2-0.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>下半场刚刚开场费尔南多就以强行突破赢得右侧任意球，可惜小角度攻门打高。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">Not long after the start of the second half, Fernando forced his way through the defense and won a free kick on the right. However, the shot was at a tight angle and blasted over the goal.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">In the second half, Fernando won the right Free-kick with a forced breakthrough, but a small angle of header played high.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">Fernando had just opened the second half to force a breakthrough to win the right side of the free kick, but unfortunately a small angle to hit high.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在邓小飞被判定拖延时间领到黄牌后，替补出场的彭欣力因禁区前犯规也领到黄牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">After Deng Xiaofei was given a yellow card for wasting time, substitute Peng Xinli was also given a yellow card for a foul in the penalty area.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">After Deng was judged to delay the time to receive a yellow card, the replacement of the Peng Xinli due to foul in front of the penalty also received a yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">After Deng Xiaoping was convicted of delaying time to receive a yellow card, substitute Peng Xinli also received a yellow card for a foul in front of the penalty area.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第56分钟，张池明左路内切中与张稀哲传递配合，其弧线球攻门被邓小飞挡出。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">At the 56th minute, Zhang Chiming cut in from the left, and passed the ball to Zhang Xizhe who curled the ball toward goal but was blocked by Deng Xiaofei.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">The first 56 minutes, Zhang Zhiming left inside and Zhang dilute ZHE transmission cooperation, its ARC ball header was Deng block out.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">The 56th minute, Zhang Chiming left inside the cut with Zhang Xizhe transmission coordination, its curveball attack was blocked by Deng Xiaoping.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刘宇禁区前凶狠铲抢侵犯克里梅茨，他与情绪激动的王栋相继领到黄牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">In the penalty area, Liu Yu savagely raked Krimets. He and the emotional Wang Dong received the yellow card one after another.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">Liu before the Forbidden area ferocious shovel Rob invasion Krimmetz, he and emotional dong successively received yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">LiuYu box before the fierce shovel robbery invasion Krimetz, he and emotional WangDong have received yellow cards.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第63分钟，费尔南多右路奔袭时被克里梅茨直接撞翻，费尔南多对克里梅茨的动作非常不满，克里梅茨领到黄牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">At the 63rd minute, Fernando attempted an offensive from the right, but was directly rammed by Krimets, causing him to fall over. Fernando was extremely displeased with Krimets’s action, and the latter was given a yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">The first 63 minutes, Fernando right strikes was Krimmetz directly knocked over, Fernando Krimmetz action very dissatisfied, Krimmetz received yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">In the 63rd minute, Fernando was knocked over directly by Krimmetz while running on the right, who was so unhappy with Krimmetz's movements that Krimmetz received a yellow card.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>1分钟后费尔南多再度在右路展示奔袭能力，于大宝追防犯规也领到黄牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">After a minute, Fernando then went through the right, demonstrating his rapid offensive skills. Yu Dabao took after him in desperate defense, fouling in the process and receiving a yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">After 1 minutes, Fernando again on the right display strikes ability, in the big treasure Chase fouls also receive yellow card.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">A minute later Fernando again in the right to show the running ability, Yu Dabao pursuit foul also received a yellow card.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>伊尔马兹禁区线内强行突破，在郑又荣伸腿拦截动作下倒地，裁判判定点球，伊尔马兹操刀破门，力帆2:1国安。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">Yılmaz managed to breakthrough the penalty area but fell after being intercepted by Zheng Yourong. The referee decided to provide Yılmaz with a penalty kick which he then scored, resulting in a 2:1 for Lifan versus Guoan.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">Ilmaz restricted area line force break through, in Zheng and Rong legs interception action under the ground, referee judge penalty, Ilmaz fencing, Lifan 2:1 Guoan.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">Ilmaz forced a break in the penalty area line, Zheng Yourong extended his legs to intercept the action under the fall, the referee decided that the penalty, Ilmaz knife break, Lifan 2: 1 national security.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第86分钟，周挺右路送出传中，谢尔盖耶夫在禁区中路胸部停球后顺势施射，邓小飞再次以精彩扑救将球封出。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">On the 86th minute, Zhou Ting crossed the ball in on the right. Sergeev chested the ball down in the middle of the box and took shot at goal. Deng Xiaofei again dived splendidly to push the ball away.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">The first 86 minutes, zhouting on the right to send a cross, Sergeev in the closed area of the chest after the ball to stop the shot, Deng again with wonderful saves the ball sealed out.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">In the 86th minute, Zhou Ting sent a cross from the right, Sergeyev stopped the ball in the middle of the penalty area after the chest, Deng Xiaoping once again blocked the ball with a brilliant save.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>4分钟补时过后，力帆将2-1的比分保持到终场，于客场战胜国安。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">After the four-minute overtime, Lifan kept the score at 2-1 until the final whistle, and beat Guoan in the away game.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">4 minutes after the injury, Lifan will 2-1 of the score to the final, away from the homeland to win.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">After four minutes of stoppage time, Lifan kept the score 2-1 until the end of the game to win the game on the road.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.sl">
    <source>拿下这宝贵的3分之后，目前力帆的积分达到27分，暂居积分榜第10位。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.ht">After taking 3 valuable points, Lifan’s total score has reached 27 points, currently giving the team a rank 10 position on the leaderboards.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.gg">After winning this valuable 3 points, the current Lifan points to 27 points, the temporary standings 10th place.</translation>
    <translation system="055_ifeng0812.news.49768431_0_zh.c6">After taking the precious three points, the sails now have 27 points and are temporarily in 10th place in the table.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
