<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这5000元资助，解了我的燃眉之急。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">“This 5,000 RMB subsidy really resolved my current crisis.”</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">"The 5000-dollar subsidy has solved my immediate urgency." ”</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">"This $5000 grant has solved my immediate need."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>花垣县长乐乡米迫村贫困建档立卡户女孩周芬收到了南华大学录取通知书。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">Zhou Fen, a girl from a poor household for which information has been recorded and archived, living in Mipo Village, Changle Township, Huayuan County, received an admission notice from Nanhua University.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">Huayuan County Changle Township Rice forced village poor construction stall girl Zhou Fen received a letter of acceptance from Nanhua University.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">Zhou Fen, a poor girl who built stalls in Mizuo Village, Changle Township, Huayuan County, received an acceptance letter from the University of Southern China.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>正当她为入学费用犯愁时，8月9日，团县委及时给她落实了5000元资助款。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">Just as she started to worry about tuition fees, the county committee of the league provided her with a timely sum of aid money of 5,000 RMB on August 9.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">Just as she was worried about the cost of admission, August 9, the group of the county party to give her a timely implementation of the 5000-yuan subsidy.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">When she was worried about the cost of admission, on August 9, the Youth League County Committee gave her a timely implementation of the 5000 yuan grant.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>连日来，县有关部门还为690余名贫困大学生落实283.8万元就学资助。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">For days, relevant departments in the counties have provided 2.838 million RMB of bursaries for over 690 college students from poor families.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">In recent days, the county departments also for more than 690 poor university students to implement the 2.838 million yuan schooling funding.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">Over the past few days, the county authorities have also provided 2.838 million yuan in financial aid to more than 690 impoverished college students.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>同时，对于家庭经济状况特别困难的，还通过组织社会捐资助学等形式，帮助其完成学业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">For families facing extremely difficult economic situations, social donations for school subsidies are also organized to help students complete their academic careers.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">At the same time, the family economic situation is particularly difficult, but also through the organization of social donations to help students to complete their studies.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">At the same time, if the family's financial situation is particularly difficult, they are also helped to complete their studies by organizing social donations and other forms of education.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>花垣今年整合助学资金1850多万元，财政自筹250多万元，由财政部门按规定时限打入贫困学生实名银行卡中。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">For this year, Huayuan has consolidated a sum of over 18.50 million RMB for academic scholarships and independently financed a sum of over 2.5 million RMB for this purpose. The financial department will transfer the fees to a named bank account of the needy students within the specified time period.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">Huayuan this year, the integration of student funds more than 18.5 million yuan, the financial self-financing more than 2.5 million yuan, by the financial sector in accordance with the prescribed time limit into the poor students real-name bank card.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">This year, Hua Yuan consolidated more than 18.5 million yuan in student aid funds and raised more than 2.5 million yuan in self-financed funds, which were transferred by the financial department into real-name bank cards of poor students within a specified time limit.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她感激地说：“我原以为爸爸去世了，我和哥哥都上不成大学了，没想到县里及时为我们解决了困难。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">She thankfully said: “I thought my older brother and I would never make it to college after my father passed away. We never thought that the county will promptly provide us with assistance to address the issue.”</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">She said gratefully: "I thought my father died, my brother and I can not be university, did not expect the county in time for us to solve the difficulties." ”</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">"I thought my dad had died and my brother and I weren't going to college," she said gratefully. "I didn't think the county would solve the problem for us in time."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>截至8月8日，花垣已为13140名贫困学生落实今年上半年各种救助资金2100多万元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">As of August 8, Huayuan has provided poor students with over 21 million RMB in subsidies and bursaries for 13,140 poor students for the first half of this year.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">As of August 8, Huayuan has implemented the first half of this year a variety of rescue funds for 13,140 poor students more than 21 million yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">As of August 8, Hanagaki has provided more than 21 million yuan in various relief funds for 13,140 impoverished students in the first half of this year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.sl">
    <source>所有本县籍贫困学生实现了应助尽助、该补则补。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.ht">Every poor student in this county has received financial assistance and subsidy.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.gg">All the impoverished students in the county have realized the support and complement.</translation>
    <translation system="061_ifeng0812.news.49763859_0_zh.c6">All of the county's poor students to achieve the necessary help, the supplement.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
