<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>邓亚萍在14年的运动生涯中，共拿到18个世界冠军，成为中国奥运历史上第一个夺得四枚奥运金牌的人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">During her 14 years of sports career, Ms. Deng Yaping won 18 world champions and became the first winner of four Olympic gold medals in Chinese history.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">Deng Yaping in the 14 sports career, a total of 18 world championships, the Chinese Olympic Games in the history of the first win four Olympic gold medals.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">During her 14-year career, Deng Yaping has won 18 world championships, becoming the first person in China's Olympic history to win four Olympic gold medals.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她在乒坛排名连续8年保持世界第一，是乒乓球史上排名“世界第一”时间最长的女运动员。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">She has topped the world leaderboard in table tennis for 8 consecutive years, making her the longest reigning “world queen” in the history of table tennis.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">She kept the world first in the tennis rankings for 8 consecutive years and was the longest-running female athlete in the history of table tennis.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">She has been ranked number one in the world for eight consecutive years and is the longest-serving female player in the history of table tennis to be ranked number one in the world.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2010年9月26日，任人民日报社副秘书长兼人民搜索网络股份公司总经理，正厅级干部。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">On September 26, 2010, he served as the deputy secretary general of People’s Daily and the general manager of the People Search Internet Corporation, making him a member of the upper management.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">September 26, 2010, Deputy Secretary-General of People's daily and the general manager of the popular search network AG, the stall-level cadres.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">On 26 September 2010, he was appointed Deputy Secretary-General of the People's Daily and General Manager of the People's Search Network Co., Ltd., a leading official.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日前，她将和俞敏洪联手共同打造国内第一家体育产业创新创业平台。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">A few days ago, she and Yu Minhong together jointly created the first sports industry innovation and entrepreneurial platform in China.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">Recently, she will join hands with Yu to create the first domestic sports industry innovation and entrepreneurship platform.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">Recently, she will join hands with Yu Minhong to build the first domestic sports industry innovation and entrepreneurship platform.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>中国体坛上也有这样一群明星教练：他们在运动员时代风光无限，为国家赢得无数荣耀；退役后将多年所学传授于后来者，培养出中夺冠军。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">The athletic associations in China also have their own team of superstar coaches. These coaches have won numerous glories for their country as athletes. After retiring from their athletic career, they began teaching their experiences and what they’ve learned to younger athletes who would then go on to become champions in their own right.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">Chinese sports also have such a group of star coaches: they are in the athletes era of unlimited glory for the country to win countless, after the retirement will be taught for many years later, to cultivate the winner.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">In Chinese sports, there is also a group of star coaches who have won numerous honors for their country in their days as athletes, and who, after retiring from the sport, have passed on what they have learned over the years to those who have gone on to win the championship.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>作为中国男子体操首位世界冠军，黄玉斌退役后选择拿起教鞭。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">As the first Chinese world champion in men’s gymnastics, Huang Yubin became a coach after retirement.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">As the first world champion of Chinese men's gymnastics, Huang chose to pick up the pointer after retiring.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">As China's first world champion in men's gymnastics, Huang chose to pick up the pointer after retiring.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从女队教练到男队教练，再到总教练，黄玉斌打造了一支“奥运金团”，更率队在北京奥运会取得了9金1银4铜的神话战绩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">Working up from the women's team coach to the men's team coach, then to the main coach, Huang Yubin has created an “Olympic gold medalist winners”, leading the team to acquire the legendary achievement of 9 golds, 1 silver, and 4 bronzes in the Beijing Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">From the female team coach to the male team coach, then to head coach, Huang built an "Olympic gold Regiment", the more rate team in the Beijing Olympic Games won 9 Gold 1 silver 4 bronze myth record.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">From the coach of the women's team to the coach of the men's team to the head coach, Huang Yubin built an "Olympic gold team" and led the team to a mythical record of nine gold, one silver and four bronze medals at the Beijing Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.sl">
    <source>此后，田亮一直广告代言不断，更是在近年扮演了“牛郎”、“雷锋”等重要角色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.ht">Subsequently, Tian Liang continued to be an advertisement spokesperson. In recent years, he has also played the roles of a “cowboy”, “Lei Feng” and other major characters.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.gg">Since then, Tian has been advertising endorsements, but also in recent years played a "cowboy", "Lei Feng" and other important roles.</translation>
    <translation system="019_ifeng0812.news.49768309_0_zh.c6">Since then, Tian Liang has been constantly advertising endorsement, but also in recent years played a "Cowherd", "Lei Feng" and other important roles.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
