<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.sl">
    <source>8月9日，在丹凤县棣花古镇文化旅游景区，商洛供电公司10余名青年职工来到这里开展“相约古镇情满电力”暨我们的节日·七夕主题活动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.ht">On August 9, over 10 young volunteers from Shangluo Electric Power Supply Company arrived at the Cultural Tourism Area of Dihua Town in Danfeng County to initiate the “Powering the Romantic Old Town” program and to celebrate the Double Seven Festival of China.</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.gg">August 9, in Danfeng County di Flower Town Cultural Tourism Scenic Area, Shangluo power supply company more than 10 young workers came here to carry out "Meet the town full of power" and our festivals and Tanabata theme activities.</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.c6">On August 9, more than 10 young workers from Shangluo Power Supply Company came to Di Hua Ancient Town Cultural Tourism Scenic Area in Danfeng County to carry out "Meet the Ancient Town and Feel the Power" and our festival and Tanabata theme activities.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.sl">
    <source>商洛供电公司丹凤县公司结合精神文明建设工作，积极组织开展“相约古镇情满电力”暨我们的节日·七夕主题活动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.ht">The Danfeng County company of Shangluo Power Supply Company incorporated ideological progress, and enthusiastically carried out the “Ancient city rendezvous; love-filled power” and our holiday - Chinese Valentine’s Day activities.</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.gg">Shangluo power supply Company Danfeng County Co., Ltd. combined with the construction of spiritual civilization, and actively organize to carry out "Meet the town full of power" and our festivals and Tanabata theme activities.</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.c6">Danfeng County Company of Shangluo Power Supply Company, in conjunction with the construction of spiritual civilization, actively organized and carried out the "Meet the ancient town full of love power" and our festival and Tanabata theme activities.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.sl">
    <source>参加活动的公司职工表示：“自己平时主要精力都用在工作和学习上，缺少时间和平台去和同事、朋友交流。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.ht">Company employees who participated in the event expressed: “We often spend most of our time in work and learning, and lack the time to socialize with our colleagues and friends on the platform.”</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.gg">Employees of the company said: "Their main energy is used in work and study, lack of time and platform to communicate with colleagues and friends." ”</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.c6">Company employees who attended the event said: "I usually focus on work and study, lack of time and platform to communicate with colleagues and friends."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.sl">
    <source>“这次公司为我们提供了这样一个轻松、快乐、和谐的平台，我非常喜欢，有意义又不失趣味。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.ht">“I really liked the relaxing, enjoyable, and harmonious platform the company provided us this time. It was meaningful and interesting at the same time.”</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.gg">"This time the company provides us with such a relaxed, joyful, harmonious platform, I like very much, has the significance and the interest without losing the fun." ”</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.c6">"This company has provided us with such a relaxed, happy and harmonious platform, which I like very much, meaningful and interesting."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.sl">
    <source>七夕活动受到了现场青年职工们的广泛好评，纷纷希望该公司以后多举办这样的活动，与更多其他的青年加强沟通与交流。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.ht">The Double Seven event was positively reviewed by young workers at the venue and they hope that the company will hold other similar events in the future where they can strengthen their communication and dialog skills with other fellow youths.</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.gg">Tanabata activities by the scene of the young workers are widely praised, and hope that the company will hold more such activities, and more other young people to strengthen communication and communication.</translation>
    <translation system="113_peopledaily0812.sn.c360642-28826991_zh.c6">Tanabata activities by young workers at the scene of the wide acclaim, one after another hope that the company will hold more such activities, and more other young people to strengthen communication and exchanges.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
