<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>北海油田工人停止罢工，继续谈判</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">North Sea oil field workers end strike, negotiations continue</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">North Sea oil workers stop strike and continue negotiations</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">North Sea oil field workers stop strike, continue negotiations</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>首席谈判代表表示，北海油田的工人停止了关于薪酬的罢工，此次纠纷的各方开始了新一轮的谈判。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">The chief negotiations representative expressed that the North Sea Oil workers have stopped strikes regarding employee pay. Both parties have initiated a new round of negotiations for this dispute.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">The chief negotiator said workers at the North Sea oil field had halted the pay strike, and the parties to the dispute began a new round of negotiations.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">The chief negotiator said workers at North Sea oil fields had halted strikes over pay and the parties to the dispute had begun a new round of negotiations.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>荷兰皇家壳牌经营的北海石油平台上出现了多次针对油田服务公司 Wood Group 的罢工。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">The North Sea oil platform operated by the Royal Dutch Shell has experienced multiple strikes directed against the oil field service company Wood Group.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">A number of strikes against Wood Group, the Oil-field Service company, have appeared on the North Sea oil platform operated by Royal Dutch Shell.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">There have been a number of strikes against oil field services company Wood Group on North Sea oil platforms operated by Royal Dutch Shell.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>根据一份联合声明，“Wood Group 以及 Unite 和 RMT 工会可以确认我们已同意重启当前纠纷的解决进程。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">According to a joint statement, “Wood Group, Unite, and RMT unions can verify that we have agreed to restart the process to address the current dispute.”</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">According to a joint statement, "Wood Group and the Unite and RMT unions can confirm that we have agreed to restart the current dispute resolution process." ”</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">According to a joint statement, "Wood Group and the Unite and RMT unions can confirm that we have agreed to restart the process of resolving the current dispute."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>我们将从下周早些时候开始，在未来几周举行多场全天会议，重新审视这些问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">We will start earlier from next week onward. In the next few weeks, multiple full-day conferences will be held. These issues will be re-examined.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">We will revisit these issues from the beginning of next week with a number of all-day meetings in the coming weeks.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">We will be reviewing these issues with a number of full-day meetings in the coming weeks, starting early next week.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>工会表示其近期采取的行动是为了抗议最高可能达到30%的减薪，而这也是工会25年以来首次采取这一行动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">The union expressed that actions taken recently is to protest salary reduction that may reach as high as 30%. This is the first time in 25 years that the union has taken such an act.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">The union said it had recently taken action to protest the highest possible pay cut of 30% per cent, which was the first by the Union since 25.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">The union said its recent action, the first of its kind in 25 years, was in protest at a possible pay cut of up to 30 per cent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>Wood Group 今年因市场压力而将北海承包商的报酬降低了约9%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">Wood Group lowered the compensation of North Sea contractors by about 9% this year because of market pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">Wood Group has reduced the compensation for North Sea contractors by about 9% this year due to market pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">Wood Group has reduced compensation for North Sea contractors by about 9 per cent this year because of market pressures.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>此次减薪前，该公司在2014年将海上承包商的报酬降低了10%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">Prior to this salary reduction, this company has reduced remuneration paid for overseas contractors by 10%.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">Prior to the pay cut, the company lowered its offshore contractor's pay by 10% in 2014.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">The pay cut comes after the company cut compensation for offshore contractors by 10 per cent in 2014.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>公司表示，再次减薪将帮助公司度过市场萧条的难关。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">The company said that another salary cut would help tide the company over the market downturn.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">The company said another pay cut would help the company tide over the market depression.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">The company said another pay cut would help the company ride out the market slump.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>壳牌已裁减了数千名员工并且宣布计划关停10个国家的油气设备，这是因为公司在与英国能源公司英国天然气集团合并后需要精简其业务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">Shell has laid off thousands of workers and announced that it will be shutting down oil and gas facilities and plants in 10 countries. This is because Shell is required to streamline its businesses after its merger with British Gas.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">Shell has cut thousands of of its staff and announced plans to shut down 10 of its oil and gas facilities because it needs to streamline its operations after it merged with British Gas group, a UK energy company.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">Shell has cut thousands of jobs and announced plans to shut down oil and gas equipment in 10 countries because of the need to streamline its operations following its merger with British energy company British Gas.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>能源公司正在面临来自原油价格下降以及英国六月脱欧决定的压力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">Energy companies are facing pressure from declining crude oil prices and the Brexit decision in June.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">Energy companies are under pressure from a drop in crude oil prices and the UK's decision to take off Europe in June.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">Energy companies are coming under pressure from lower crude oil prices and the UK's decision to leave the European Union in June.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰议会成员戴夫·安德森在本周早些时候与工会领导人会面，共同探讨北海这一代人最大的劳动纠纷。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">David Anderson, a member of the Scottish Parliament, said earlier this week that he met with union leaders to investigate the biggest North Sea labor dispute in this generation.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">戴夫·安德森, a member of the Scottish Parliament, met with union leaders earlier this week to discuss the biggest labor dispute in the North Sea generation.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">Scottish Parliament member Dave Anderson met union leaders earlier this week to discuss the biggest labour dispute of the North Sea generation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>他表示，北海对于地区经济而言至关重要。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">He said that the North Sea is extremely crucial to the region’s economy.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">He says the North Sea is crucial to the region's economy.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">He said the North Sea was vital to the region's economy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>戴夫在声明中表示：“在北海和整个国家，我们需要一种服务于多数人而非少数人的经济。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">In this statement, Dave expressed: “In the North Sea and for the entire country, we need an economy that serves the majority, and not the minority.”</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">"In the North Sea and across the country, we need an economy that serves the majority, not the few," Dave said in a statement. ”</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">"In the North Sea and across the country, we need an economy that works for the many, not the few," Dave said in the statement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="088_upi.103611_en.sl">
    <source>2016年，北海新项目的支出预计不超过14亿美元，而过去五年的平均项目支出达到约70亿美元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.ht">In 2016, expenditure for new North Sea projects are not expected to exceed US$1.4  billion. In the last five years, the average project expenditure was approximately US$7 billion.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.gg">The new North Sea project was expected to spend no more than $1.4 billion in 2016, while the average project expenditure in the past five years amounted to about $7 billion.</translation>
    <translation system="088_upi.103611_en.c6">Spending on new projects in the North Sea is expected to be no more than $1.4 billion in 2016, compared with an average of around $7 billion over the past five years.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
