<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>据媒体披露，由于此前资本大规模涌入互联网医药，造成目前产品同质化的问题严重，投资热潮渐退，资本进入观望期。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Media revealed that the deluge of capital that swamped online health care resulted in the severe product homogeneity problem we see today. The investment boom is waning gradually. Capital has entered a wait-and-see period.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">According to media disclosure, as a result of large-scale capital influx of internet medicine, resulting in the current product homogeneity problem serious, investment boom gradually receded, capital into the wait-and-see period.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">According to media reports, due to the previous large-scale influx of capital into Internet medicine, resulting in the current serious problem of product homogenization, the investment boom gradually receded, capital into a wait and see period.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>另据香港艾力彼医院管理研究中心数据显示，创业一年内的互联网医疗公司大量死亡，约20%的初创互联网医疗企业已不复存在。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Figures from Hong Kong Ailibi Hospital Management Research Center revealed that many online health care companies close down within the first year of incorporation; approximately 20% of newly founded online health care enterprises no longer exist.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">According to data from the Hong Kong Centre for Management Studies at the Ellie Hospital, internet healthcare companies have died in a year, and about 20% of start-ups have ceased to exist.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">According to data from the Centre for Management Research at Ellison Hospital in Hong Kong, a large number of Internet medical companies have died within one year of their establishment, and about 20 per cent of the start-up Internet medical companies have ceased to exist.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>然而，就在大部分互联网医疗企业挣扎在A轮或B轮的融资路上的时候，有几家细分领域领先企业仍能获得资本热捧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">However, while most Internet health care companies were struggling to choose between Series A or Series B financing, a number of leading companies in specialized sectors were still able to attract capital.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">However, as most internet healthcare companies struggle to finance a round or B-round financing, several segments of the leading companies are still gaining capital heat.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">However, just as most internet healthcare companies struggle to finance rounds A and B, several segment leaders are still gaining traction.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>看来，互联网医疗创业断不可“一窝蜂”，而是要看准市场需求，沉得下心做专，做深。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">It seems that “rushing headlong” into the Industry healthcare sector is not the wisest option. One must accurately assess market requirements, be patient, and improve the professionalism and depth of services provided.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">It seems that the Internet medical start-up can not "swarm", but to look at the market demand, sinking heart to do the special, do deep.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">It seems that the Internet can not be a medical entrepreneurship "swarm", but to look at the market demand, sink down to do special, do deep.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>鱼跃出资1200.00万元，占注册资本的40%，九州通器械公司出资1800.00万元，占注册资本的60%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Yuyue contributed 12.0000 million dollars, comprising 40% of the registered capital, while Jointown Pharmaceutical provided 18.0000 million dollars for 60% of the registered capital.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">Diving capital of 12 million yuan, accounting for 40% of the registered capital, Kyushu Tong Equipment Company contributed 18 million yuan, accounting for 60% of the registered capital.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">Yuyue made a capital contribution of 12 million yuan, accounting for 40 percent of the registered capital, and Kyushu Tong Instrument Company made a capital contribution of 18 million yuan, accounting for 60 percent of the registered capital.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>近年来，随着国家在医疗信息化方面的政策支持，电子化、集成化的供应链管理系统逐步进入各级医院。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">In recent years, thanks to national policy support in terms of medical informatization, electronic and integrated supply chain management systems have been gradually introduced into different classes of hospitals.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">In recent years, with the state's policy support in medical informatization, electronic and integrated supply chain management system has gradually entered all levels of hospitals.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">In recent years, with the state's policy support in medical information, electronic, integrated supply chain management system gradually into all levels of hospitals.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>此次鱼跃与九州通的合作正是瞄准了市场的需求，帮助医院搭建先进供应链管理系统，并以此为契机谋求更多合作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">The partnership between Yuyue and Jointown Pharmaceutical aims at meeting market demands and helping hospital establish an advanced supply chain management system. The partnership is also an opportunity to seek additional partnerships.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">The cooperation between the diving and Kyushu is aimed at the demand of the market, to help the hospital to build an advanced supply chain management system, and as a chance to seek more cooperation.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">The cooperation between Yuyue and Kyushu Tong is precisely aimed at the needs of the market, helping hospitals to build advanced supply chain management system, and using this as an opportunity to seek more cooperation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>与很多互联网医疗公司贪大求全不同，iBaby从最初就专注于互联网产科垂直领域，深耕孕妈和医生两端。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Unlike many Internet health care companies obsessed with scale and extensive coverage, iBaby focused on the vertical industry of obstetrics from the very beginning, channeling their efforts toward supporting both pregnant mothers and their physicians.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">Unlike many internet health-care companies, China Ibaby from its initial focus on the vertical field of Internet obstetrics, deep pregnant moms and doctors.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">Unlike many internet healthcare companies, iBaby has been focused on the internet obstetrics vertical since its inception, working both as a mother and a doctor.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>孕妈不仅可以免费24小时和一对一的主管医生问诊，还可以付费定向寻医问诊。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Pregnant mothers can receive 24-hours one-on-one consultation with a specialist physician for free. They can also pay for personal consultation with a specified physician.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">Not only can pregnant mothers be free for 24 hours and one-on-one doctor visits, but also can pay directional medical consultations.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">Pregnant mothers are not only entitled to free 24-hour and one-on-one consultation with a doctor in charge, but are also entitled to paid, directed medical consultation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>而在医生端，iBaby通过采取组织专家给基层医生开展在线讲座、同行交流、病例讨论等微讲座的形式，打破地域限制。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">At the doctors’ end, iBaby has broken down regional restrictions by way of organizing experts to carry out webinars, peer exchanges, case discussions and other mini-seminars.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">And at the doctor's end, Ibaby through the organization of experts to grassroots doctors on-line lectures, peer exchanges, case discussions and other micro-lectures on the form of breaking the geographical restrictions.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">At the doctor's end, iBaby breaks geographical boundaries by organizing experts to give microlectures, such as online lectures, peer-to-peer exchanges, and case discussions, to doctors at the grass-roots level.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>目前医生端开设三个板块，分别为医生继续教育、医生社交和医生求助。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Currently, three segments have been set up at the doctor’s end, namely, continuing education for doctors, social networking for doctors, and help for doctors.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">At present, doctors offer three sections for continuing education, Doctor's social and Doctor's help.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">At present, the doctor side opened three sections, respectively, for doctors to continue education, doctors social and doctors for help.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>提供包括在线学习、病例讨论、学术交流；同医院、同科室医生之间社交平台；医患关系或个人生活所需要的法律援助、创业支持等服务内容。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">The contents provided include online learning, medical case studies, and academic exchange; social networking platform between physicians of the same hospital or same departments; and doctor-patient relationships or legal assistance necessary for personal lifestyles, entrepreneurship support, and other services.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">Provides services including online learning, case discussions, academic exchanges, social platforms with hospitals and physicians, legal aid and entrepreneurial support for physician-patient relationships or personal life.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">Services include online learning, case discussions, academic exchanges, social networking platforms with hospitals and doctors in departments, legal assistance for doctor-patient relationships or personal life, and support for entrepreneurship.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>据媒体报道，CEO王磊近日表示阿里健康“愿意沉下心来”拿下健康大数据。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Media report that CEO Wang Lei expressed that Alibaba Health is “willing to settle down” and takeover the Big Data analytics for health.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">According to media reports, CEO Wang Lei recently said Ali Health "willing to sink heart to" take the health of large data.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">CEO Wang Lei recently said Ali Health was "willing to sink in" to take down health big data, according to media reports.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>互联网公司、数据公司缺少专业性，在同一词条上的书写方法上都达不到统一。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Online businesses and data companies lack professionalism, and were unable to achieve uniformity in the terminologies of identical keywords.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">The lack of professionalism in internet companies and data companies is not uniform in the way they write on the same entry.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">Internet companies, data companies lack professionalism in the same entry on the writing methods are not uniform.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>阿里目前在医疗健康领域的布局分为三块，分别是阿里健康、天猫医药馆和支付宝未来医院。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Alibaba has structured its presence in the health care industry into three segments, namely Alibaba Health, Tmall Pharmacy, and Alipay's Future Hospital.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">Ali currently in the Medical and health field of the layout is divided into three pieces, respectively, Ali Health, the day Cat Medicine Museum and pay Treasure future hospital.</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">Ali's current layout in the field of health care is divided into three sections, namely Ali Health, Tmall Medicine Hall and Alipay Future Hospital.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.sl">
    <source>王磊坦言，医疗健康创业会比其他行业要难，“这不仅仅是有多少钱的事情，还要沉得下心，耐得住寂寞慢慢去做。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.ht">Wang Lei disclosed that starting a medical healthcare company is more challenging when compared to other sectors. “This is not just about making money. You must be patient and get used to loneliness to do this properly.”</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.gg">Wang Lei Frankly, health care business will be more difficult than other industries, "this is not only how much money, but also to sink the heart, endure loneliness slowly to do." ”</translation>
    <translation system="006_peopledaily0812.health.c398004-28632031_zh.c6">"It's not just a matter of how much money you have," Wang admits. "It's a matter of getting down and being able to live with the loneliness and do it slowly."</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
