<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>厦门姑娘张彬彬：“手型漂亮”开始射击之路职业生涯几经“逆转”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Binbin, a daughter of Xiamen, had “wonderful hand posture” and experienced multiple “reversals” during her career as a shooter.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Xiamen Girl Zhang Binbin: "Beautiful Hand" began shooting road career after several "reversal"</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Xiamen girl Zhang Binbin: "beautiful hand" began shooting career path several "reversal"</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>厦门翔安区东园村的张东红前几天刚把家中29寸的老电视，换成了65寸的大电视。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Donghong, a resident at Dongyuan Village at Xiang’an District in Xiamen, just swapped his old 29-inch television for a large 65-inch set several days ago.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Xiamen Xiang an district East Garden village Zhang Donggong a few days ago just put a 29-inch old TV, replaced by a 65-inch big TV.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang Donghong, of Dongyuan Village, Xiamen's Xiang'an District, just a few days ago replaced the 29-inch old TV in his home with a 65-inch one.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这位普通农民的女儿，就是11日晚为中国斩获里约奥运会女子50米步枪三姿决赛银牌的张彬彬。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">This daughter of a common farmer is Zhang Binbin, who just won a silver medal for China in the 50 meter rifle three positions in the Rio Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">The ordinary peasant's daughter, is 11th night for China to win the Rio Olympic Games women's 50-meter rifle three-posture final silver Zhang Binbin.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">The daughter of an ordinary farmer is Zhang Binbin, who won the silver medal in the women's 50-meter rifle three-position final for China at the Rio Olympics on Monday night.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>11日夜，就在这部新电视前，张东红夫妇和几十位亲戚好友，一起见证了女儿一路奋起直追，从几乎预赛就被淘汰到差点大逆转的神奇过程。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">During the evening of the 11th, Zhang Donghong, his wife, and dozens of other family members and friends stood before this new television and witnessed how his daughter started a miraculous spree that brought her from the brink of being dropped out of the competition to a medal winning score.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">11th night, just before this new television, Zhang Donggong couples and dozens of relatives and friends, together witnessed the daughter's way to catch up, from almost the preliminaries were eliminated to almost a reversal of the magical process.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">11 Day and night, just in front of the new TV, the Zhang Donghong couple and dozens of relatives and close friends, together witnessed the daughter all the way to catch up, from almost the preliminary round was eliminated to almost a complete reversal of the magical process.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在当日的比赛中，张彬彬一度排名中下游，似乎距离决赛十分遥远。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">On the day of the competition, Zhang Binbin had a mid to low ranking at one point, and a spot in the final appeared extremely remote.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">In that day's game, Zhang Binbin once ranked midstream and downstream, seems to be far away from the final.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">In that day's competition, Zhang Binbin once ranked in the middle and lower reaches, seems to be very far away from the final.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但父母和亲朋好友没有放弃，不停地刷着文字直播，看到随着其他选手完赛，张彬彬名次一路提升，最终锁定决赛席位，其家中顿时爆发从一阵欢呼。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Parents, family, and friends did not give up, and continued to watch to live stream. When the other athletes completed their firing, Zhang Binbin’s rank kept rising until she secured the right to compete in the finals. Everyone at her home exploded in a great cheer.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">But parents and friends and family did not give up, constantly brushing the text live, see with the other contestants finish the game, Zhang Binbin ranking all the way up, finally locked the final seat, his home suddenly erupted from a burst of cheer.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">But the parents and friends did not give up, kept brushing the text live, see with the other players finished, Zhang Binbin all the way up the ranking, eventually locked up the final seat, his home immediately erupted from a burst of cheers.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>决赛中，张彬彬又是在一度排名靠后的情况下，最后几枪越打越稳，仅以落后冠军0.2环成绩夺得银牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">In the finals, Zhang Binbin, who again fell behind in the rankings at one point, became increasingly steady as she fired the last few shots. She finished just 0.2 points behind the champion, clinching the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">In the final, Zhang Binbin was once ranked after the situation, the last few shots more stable, only to the 0.2-ring score of the trailing champion won the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">In the final, Zhang Binbin was once ranked in the situation, the last few shots more and more stable, only 0.2 ring behind the champion to win the silver medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>今年已经27岁的张彬彬，在16年的射击生涯中，其实有几度都差点与这块来之不易的银牌擦身而过。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Across her 16-year shooting career, Zhang Binbin, who is 27-year old this year, brushed past this hard-won silver medal on several occasions.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">The 27-year-old Zhang Binbin, who had been in the shooting career of 16, almost had a few degrees of friction with the Hard-won silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang, now 27, has come close to winning the hard-won silver medal several times in his 16-year shooting career.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>其母张小龙告诉记者，就在他们犹豫时，张彬彬找来了同村的几个“小说客”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">The mother, Zhang Xiaolong, told the reporter that when everyone was still hesitant, Zhang Binbin found several “young persuaders” from the same village.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">His mother Zhangxiaolong told reporters, in their hesitation, Zhang Binbin found several "novel visitors" with the village.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang Xiaolong, his mother, told reporters that just as they hesitated, Zhang Binbin sought several "novelists" from the same village.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这些“小说客”是当年同时被推荐参加集训的同村小孩，其中还有张彬彬的表姐。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">The "little lobbyists” are the kids from the same family participated the training by recommendation at hat time, including the cousin of Zhang Binbin.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">The "novel Guest" was also recommended to participate in the training of the same village children, including Zhang Binbin cousin.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">These "novelists" were children from the same village who had been recommended for training at the same time, including Zhang's cousin.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>就在进入厦门队后不久，张彬彬又一度因为家庭困难等原因，主动回到翔安的学校读书。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Not long after entering the Xiamen team, Zhang Binbin once again actively returned to study at a school in Xiang’an due to family difficulties and other reasons.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Shortly after entering the Xiamen team, Zhang Binbin again because of family difficulties and other reasons, the initiative to return to the school of Xiang Ann.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Shortly after entering the Xiamen team, Zhang Binbin and once again because of family difficulties and other reasons, take the initiative to return to the school in Xiang'an.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但是在其启蒙教练张亚杰反复做工作后，张彬彬又回到了厦门队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Binbin returned to Xiamen Team after being repeatedly persuaded by her first coach Zhang Yajie.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">But after its Enlightenment coach Zhang Yaje repeated work, Zhang Binbin returned to the Xiamen team.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">But after his enlightenment coach Zhang Yajie did the work repeatedly, Zhang Binbin returned to the Xiamen team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而进入省队后，张彬彬又曾因为迟迟进不了国家队，一度因为看不到希望而再度回到家里。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">After joining the provincial team, Zhang Binbin, who took a long time to advance to the national team, returned home at one point because she saw no hope.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">After entering the provincial team, Zhang Binbin again because of the delay into the national team, once because of the hope and return home.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">After entering the provincial team, Zhang Binbin and because of the delay into the national team, once because there was no hope and returned home again.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这次，不仅张亚杰教练，厦门射击射箭运动中心和福建省队的领导和教练都来到家里，最终劝说张彬彬回到省队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">This visit included more than just Coach Zhang Yajie. Official leaders and coaches from the Xiamen Shooting Shejian Sports Center and Fujian Provincial Team also came by and successfully persuaded Zhang Binbin to return to the provincial team.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">This time, not only Zhang Yaje coach, Xiamen shooting Archery Sports Center and Fujian province team leaders and coaches have come home, eventually persuaded Zhang Binbin back to the provincial team.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">This time, not only coach Zhang Yajie, Xiamen Shooting and Archery Sports Center and Fujian Province team leaders and coaches came to the home, and eventually persuaded Zhang Binbin to return to the provincial team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>就如同昨天的比赛，这位厦门姑娘的用坚持实现了射击之路上的一个个逆转。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Just like the competition yesterday, this daughter of Xiamen persisted and once again turned the tables in her shooting career.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Just like yesterday's game, the Xiamen Girl's insistence on the road of shooting a reversal.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Just as yesterday's game, the Xiamen girl with the stick to achieve a shooting on the road to a reversal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“每个教练挑选队员的方法不一样，当时我看到彬彬的手长得很漂亮，就一下子相中了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">“Every coach has different way of picking team members. At the time, I noticed that Binbin has really nice hands, and fell in love with them immediately.”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">"The way each coach picks up the team is different, and I saw Binbin's long very nicely," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">"Every coach picks his players differently, and I saw that Benny's hands were so beautiful that I fell in love with him."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张东红也回忆，在集训测试中，女儿虽然成绩不是最好，但打出的环数很稳定，这也是张彬彬吸引教练的重要原因。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Donghong also recalled that although his daughter’s performance was not the best at the group training test, the number of rounds she shot was very stable. This was also a key factor why Zhang Binbin attracted the attention of her coach.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Zhang Donggong also recalls, in the training test, although the daughter is not the best, but the number of rings is very stable, which is Zhang Binbin to attract coaches important reasons.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang Donghong also recalled that in the training test, his daughter, although not the best results, but hit the ring number is stable, which is an important reason for Zhang Binbin attracted coaches.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在训练张彬彬的过程中，张亚杰印象最深的，则是这位农家女孩的投入。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">During training, the farm girl Zhang Binbin was so committed that she left a lasting impression with Zhang Yajie.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">In the process of training Zhang Binbin, Zhang Yaje is the most impressive, it is the peasant girl's input.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">In the process of training Zhang Binbin, Zhang Yajie was most impressed by the dedication of the peasant girl.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他回忆说，张彬彬进入厦门射击队一年后多，队里进行立射的持久举枪训练，要求队员半个小时不能动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">He recollected that more than one year after Zhang Binbin joined the Xiamen shooting team, the team conducted a standing posture rifle firing training. Team members were required to stand still for half an hour.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">He recalls that Zhang Binbin into the Xiamen shooting team more than a year later, the team to carry out Li She sustained gun training, the team required half an hour to move.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">He recalled that more than a year after Zhang Binbin entered the Xiamen Shooting Team, the team carried out a standing practice of raising a gun and asked the team members not to move for half an hour.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张小龙告诉记者，女儿一直是个安静乖巧的孩子，从小就喜欢画画和自制手工玩具，</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Xiaolong told the reporter that her daughter is a quiet and obedient child and has loved drawing and making her own toys since a young age.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Zhangxiaolong told reporters, daughter has been a quiet well-behaved children, since childhood like painting and homemade handmade toys,</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang Xiaolong told reporters that his daughter has been a quiet and well-behaved children, from an early age like painting and homemade hand-made toys,</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“原来我会在家里做做衣服、缝缝补补，彬彬就会捡一些边角料自己做娃娃。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">“Originally, I stayed at home to tailor some clothes, sewing and mending them as needed. Binbin would sit by the corner, collecting the scrap fabrics to make her own fabric doll.”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">"Originally I will do in the home to make clothes, sew, Binbin will pick up some scraps to do their own dolls." ”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">"Originally I would make clothes at home, sewing, Binbin will pick up some bits and pieces to make their own dolls."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她说，女儿常常会自己缝制手工玩具，加上她擅长画画，从娃娃的五官到衣饰，总能做得栩栩如生。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">She said that her daughter would often sew and make her own toys. Coupled with the fact that she was good at drawing, she was able to create a lifelike face and clothing for the dolls she made.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">She says her daughter often sews her own handmade toys, plus she is good at drawing, from the doll's facial features to the dress, can always be lifelike.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">She says her daughter often sews her own handmade toys and, with her expertise in painting, makes everything from the doll's features to her clothes and accessories come to life.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>作为运动员，张彬彬和家人聚少离多，只有节假日才能回家，平时多靠电话联系。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">As an athlete, Zhang Binbin spends little time with family, and could only return home during weekends and public holidays. Usually, they communicate using the telephone.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">As an athlete, Zhang Binbin and family gather less and more, only holidays can go home, usually by telephone contact.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">As an athlete, Zhang Binbin and his family gathered less and more, only the holidays to go home, usually by telephone contact.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>父母说，无论是见面还是打电话，张彬彬很少说自己的辛苦，更多的是跟父母聊些开心的事。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Her parents said that whether when meeting in person or talking on the phone, Zhang Binbin seldom said she found things difficult. More often than not, she would chat about happy things with parents.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Parents say, whether meet or call, Zhang Binbin rarely said their hard, more is to talk with parents happy things.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Parents said, whether it is to meet or call, Zhang Binbin rarely said their hard work, more with their parents to talk about something happy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>平时见不到女儿，父母在家中将女儿小时候的画作以及历年的荣誉都细心收存着。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Since they hardly see their daughter, the parents carefully preserved the artwork that their girl has made as a child and the glories that she had later won.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Usually see the daughter, parents at home will be the daughter of the painting and years of honor are carefully stored.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Usually can not see his daughter, parents at home will be his daughter's childhood paintings as well as the honor of the calendar year are carefully preserved.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张小龙将女儿的动漫画作展示给记者，“如果没有当射击运动员，她应该还会继续画画”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Xiaolong showed the reporter the cartoon artwork his daughter created. “If she didn’t become a archer, she would probably continue to draw.”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Zhangxiaolong her daughter's anime painting to reporters, "if not as a shooting athlete, she should continue to paint."</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang showed his daughter's animated cartoon to reporters, "If she hadn't been a shooter, she should have continued to draw."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而在张彬彬家二楼客厅，有一个柜子内放满了她所获得的奖章、奖牌和证书。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">There is a cabinet located at the second floor living room in Zhang Binbin’s home that is filled with the plaques, medals, and certificates that she had won.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">In the living room on the second floor of the Zhang Binbin House, there was a cupboard full of medals, medals and certificates she had received.</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">And in the living room on the second floor of Zhang Binbin's home, there is a cupboard full of medals, medals and certificates she has received.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张东红将奖牌和奖章整齐摆放，证书则统一放进了文件夹保存，“这些都是彬彬十几年心血换来的荣誉，我们都很珍惜。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.ht">Zhang Donghong displayed the medals and awards neatly, and kept all the certificates in a folder. “These are the honors Binbin has received over the years on the basis of her hard work and dedication. All of us cherish them.”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.gg">Zhang Donggong will medals and medals neatly placed, the certificate is unified into the folder to save, "These are binbin more than 10 years of painstaking efforts in exchange for the honor, we are very cherish." ”</translation>
    <translation system="075_ifeng0812.news.49765230_0_zh.c6">Zhang Donghong neatly placed the medals and medals, certificates are unified into the folder preservation, "these are Binbin more than ten years of hard work in exchange for the honor, we all cherish."</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
