<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>海伦·格拉芙和希瑟·斯坦宁受身患癌症的教练的鼓舞，夺得赛艇金牌</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Helen Glover and Heather Stanning, encouraged by their coach who was afflicted with cancer, won the gold medal for the sculls event.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">海伦·格 love and 希瑟·斯坦宁, encouraged by the cancer coach, won the rowing gold medal.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Helen Graf and Heather Stanning were inspired by their cancer-stricken coach to win rowing gold</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>毫不夸张地说，这是最让人感动的一块金牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">It isn’t an overstatement to describe this as the most emotional gold medal.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It is no exaggeration to say that this is one of the most moving gold medals.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It's no exaggeration to say that this is the most moving piece of gold medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>从第一次划桨开始到现在，海伦·格拉芙和希瑟·斯坦宁已接受了220次惩罚性拉举训练，而她们在 Estacio da Lagoa夺得的这块金牌具有更非凡的的意义。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Since they started rowing, Helen Glover and Heather Stanning have received 220 sessions of punitive pulling training. The gold medal they won at Estacio da Lagoa is especially meaningful for them.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">From the first paddle to the present, 海伦·格 love and 希瑟·斯坦宁 have received 220 punitive training, and their gold medal in Estacio da Lagoa has a more remarkable significance.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Helen Graff and Heather Stanning have trained 220 times since their first paddle, and the gold medal they won at Estacio da Lagoa is even more remarkable.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>虽然划桨的只有她们两人，但船上还有一个人——教练罗宾·威廉姆斯——的声音一直陪伴着她们冲击连续第二块女子双人桨奥运会金牌，这是英国首对达到这一高度的赛艇女子组合。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Although there were only two rowers on the boat, there was another presence, that of their coach Robin Williams, whose voice accompanied them in their charge to achieve their second Olympic gold medal in the women’s double sculls. The women are the first British pair to win a women’s sculls event at such level.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Though they were the only two to paddle, there was a man on board--coach Robin--who had been accompanying them for the second consecutive women's double paddle Olympic gold medal, which was the UK's first to reach this height of the rowing women's combination.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Although they were the only two to paddle, the voice of one other person on board - coach Robin Williams - had been with them as they hit their second straight Olympic gold medal in the women's double sculls, the first British combination of rowing women to reach that height.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>她们已保持了39场不败纪录，具有绝对的优势。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">They have defended a record of 39 consecutive victories and enjoy definitive advantage.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">They have maintained 39 unbeaten records and have an absolute advantage.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">They have maintained an unbeaten record of 39 matches and have an absolute advantage.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我们所看到的是这两名天才运动员在水面上优雅前行，但这并不是这一胜利的全部。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">You witnessed the two talent swimmer sliding gracefully across the surface. But it is not  what the victory all about.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">What we are seeing is that these two talented athletes are walking gracefully on the water, but this is not the whole of the victory.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">What we're seeing is these two talented athletes moving gracefully on the water, but that's not the whole story of this victory.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>在每一块赛艇金牌的背后都有许多自愿帮助的人，正是他们的不断奉献创造了不同，而其中帮助最大的莫过于一位30个月前得知自己身患癌症、不知道自己能否活着看到这一天的教练。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">There are many volunteer supporters behind a rowing metal who made difference by their devotions. The most helpful hand was the coach who did not expect witness the victory day because he was diagnosed of cancer 30 months before.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">There are many volunteers behind every gold medal, and it is their constant devotion that makes a difference, and the greatest help is a coach who learned that he had cancer 30 months ago and did not know if he could live to see the day.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">There are many volunteers behind every rowing gold medal, and it is their constant dedication that makes a difference, and none more so than a coach who learned 30 months ago that he had cancer and didn't know if he would live to see the day.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>正如他所说，死亡随时可能到来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Just as he said, death strikes at any time.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">As he said, death may come at any moment.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">As he said, death could come at any moment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我患上了膀胱癌，他们为我做了手术。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">I had bladder cancer, and went for surgery.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">I had bladder cancer and they operated on me.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">I had bladder cancer and they operated on me.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>如果不做手术的话，癌细胞会扩撒到全身。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">If the operation is not implemented, the cancer cells will spread throughout the entire body.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">If you do not operate, the cancer cells will spread throughout the body.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Without surgery, the cancer will spread throughout the body.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这样，情况会糟糕得多。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">The situation will be a lot worse this way.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">In this way, the situation will be much worse.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">That way, the situation would be much worse.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这会略微改变你的看法。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">This will slightly change your views.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">This will change your mind slightly.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">This will change your mind a little bit.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>威廉姆斯在2013年12月被确诊为癌症。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Williams was diagnosed with cancer in December 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Williams was diagnosed with cancer in December 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Williams was diagnosed with cancer in December 2013.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>幸运的是，他在2014年年初开始了治疗，将影响降到最低，虽然在这种情况下这么说可能并不合适。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Fortunately, after initiating treatment in early 2014, he was able to minimize the effects to the minimum. However, it may be inappropriate to describe it as such under such circumstances.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Luckily, he started treatment in early 2014, minimizing the impact, although in this case it might not be appropriate to say so.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Fortunately, he began treatment in early 2014 to minimize the impact, although that might not be appropriate in the circumstances.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我需要拿到工资，因此我必须赶快好起来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">I must get paid, so I must get better as quickly as possible.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">I need to get paid, so I have to be better soon.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">I need to get paid, so I've got to get better soon.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这对我来说是一种激励。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">This was an incentive for me.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It's an inspiration to me.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It was an inspiration for me.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我住在医院里，虽然他们说走几步就足够了，但我还是每次绕着病房走上20英尺、30英尺、50英尺。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">I live in the hospital. Although they say taking a few steps is enough, I would walk 20 feet, 30 feet, 50 feet around the ward every time.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">I live in a hospital, and although they say it's enough to walk a few steps, I walk 20 feet, 30 feet, 50 feet every time I go around the ward.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">I was in the hospital, and although they said a few steps would be enough, I walked around the ward 20 feet, 30 feet, 50 feet at a time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这就是一切的起点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">This was the origin of all things.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">This is the beginning of everything.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">This is where it all started.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>赛艇运动本身是一次旅程，而这让这段旅程变得更长一点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Rowing is a journey in and of itself, and this has made the journey somewhat longer.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">The rowing movement itself was a journey, which made the journey a little longer.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Rowing is a journey in itself, and that makes the journey a little bit longer.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>在夺金的那一刻，她们首先想到的是威廉姆斯。今天早上的威廉姆斯比平时略微健谈一些，这是为了克服他的焦虑。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">They thought about Williams first when the gold metal was secured. Williams was a little bit more talkative this morning, a way to get rid of his anxiety.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">The first thing they thought of was Williams at the moment of the gold medal. Williams was slightly talkative this morning than usual, to overcome his anxiety.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">The first thing on their minds at the moment they won gold was Williams, who was slightly more talkative than usual this morning in an attempt to overcome his anxiety.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>曾是皇家炮兵团队长的斯坦宁之后将前往阿富汗，她表示：“我这周的心情很不好，可能有点极端，但这块金牌的确意义非凡。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Once a captain of the Royal Regiment of Artillery, Stanning will go to Afghanistan later. She said, “I was out of sorts this week, perhaps a little extreme, but the significance of this gold medal is extraordinary.”</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">"I was in a bad mood this week and it might be a bit extreme, but the gold medal really means a lot," said Stanning, who was the head of the Royal Artillery team. ”</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">"I'm in a bad mood this week, maybe a little extreme, but this gold medal is really something," said Stanning, a former captain of the Royal Artillery Regiment, who will travel to Afghanistan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>它反复告诉我这对于我而言有多重要，我、海伦以及罗宾付出了多大的努力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">It repeatedly told me how important this is, how much Helen, Robin, and I have dedicated ourselves to this.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It repeatedly told me how important it was to me, how much effort I, Helen, and Robin had made.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It told me over and over again how much it meant to me and how hard I, Helen and Robin worked.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这是海伦、罗宾和我努力了三年的回报。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">These are the returns Helen, Robin and I have worked hard for for the last three years.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">This is Helen, Robin and I have been trying for three years in return.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It's a reward for three years of hard work by Helen, Robin and me.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>如果没有罗宾，我们还只是无名小卒，非常感谢他，他是全世界最棒的教练。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">If not for Luo Bin, we would still be nobodies. We are very grateful to him. He is the best coach in the world.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Without Robin, we're just nobody, thank him very much, he's the best coach in the world.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Without Robin, we're still just nobody, thank you very much, he's the best coach in the world.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我不可能找到比他更棒的训练师和教练。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">I couldn’t possibly have found a trainer and coach better than him.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">I can't find a better trainer and coach than him.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">I couldn't have found better trainers and coaches than him.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>海伦·格拉芙和希瑟·斯坦宁在五年中未尝败绩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Helen Glover and Heather Stanning have been undefeated for five years.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">海伦·格 Love and 希瑟·斯坦宁 were undefeated in five years.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Helen Graff and Heather Stanning were unbeaten in five years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这对组合所设置的惩罚力度是她们的对手所无法比拟的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Their opponents prove to be unable to withstand the punishing power of this combination.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">The penalties set by the combination are unmatched by their rivals.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">The pair set penalties that their opponents could not match.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>即便是在最后的500米，新西兰队和丹麦队开始逼近时，斯坦宁和格拉芙仍有大量的体能储备。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Although the New Zealand and Denmark teams began to close in in the 500 meters, Stanning and Glover still had massive physical reserves.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Even at the end of the 500 metres, New Zealand and Denmark are approaching, stanning and Graff still have plenty of physical reserves.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Even in the final 500 metres, when New Zealand and Denmark began closing in, Stanning and Graf still had plenty of physical reserves.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>当时真是惊心动魄。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">It was extremely thrilling.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It was so thrilling.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It was really scary at the time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>海伦叫着：“保持节奏、保持节奏”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">"Keep the beat, the beat!" Helen screamed.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Helen shouted: "Keep the rhythm, keep the rhythm."</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Helen called: "Keep up the pace, keep up the pace."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>不被对手所影响的确非常重要。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">It is very important to not be influenced by your opponent.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It is really important not to be affected by your opponents.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It's really important not to be influenced by your opponents.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我们有一个很好的开始，同时我们并没有期盼着做什么惊天动地的大事。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">We had a very good start, and did not expect to do anything earth-shattering.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">We have a good start, and we are not looking forward to doing something big and earthshaking.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">We're off to a great start and we're not looking forward to doing anything earth-shattering.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我们没有去想今天的荣耀，我们只是想着划好每一桨和赢得这场比赛，并且我们做到了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">We didn't think of the glory we won today. We only thought about making every row count and winning the competition, and we did just that.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">We did not think of today's glory, we just wanted to paddle each oar and win the game, and we did it.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">We didn't think about the glory today, we just wanted to paddle every paddle and win this race, and we did.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="34" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这对组合花了一年时间决定自己的未来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">This combination took a year to decide its future.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">The combination took a year to determine its future.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It took the pair a year to decide their future.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="35" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>格拉芙下个月将与电视探险员史蒂夫·巴克沙尔结婚。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Glover will be marrying Steve Backshall, a television explorer, next month.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">Graff will marry the TV explorer 史蒂夫·巴克沙尔 next month.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Graff will marry TV adventurer Steve Bachchard next month.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="36" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>不过现在，她只想享受当下。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">But now she is only interested in enjoying the good times.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">But now, she just wants to enjoy the moment.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">Now, though, she just wants to enjoy the moment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="37" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>我不想说这是我的最后一场比赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">I don’t want to say that this is my last match.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">I don't want to say it's my last game.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">I don't want to say this is my last game.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="38" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这会给我带来太大的压力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">This will give me too much pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">This will bring me too much pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It would put too much pressure on me.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="39" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>在伦敦，我用了约六个月时间才意识到我是奥运冠军。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">In London, I spent about 6 months before I realized that I’m a Olympic champion.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">In London, it took me about six months to realize that I was the Olympic champion.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">In London, it took me about six months to realise I was an Olympic champion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="40" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>这是一种全新的体验，而我感到十分紧张。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">This is a brand new expereince, and I’m very nervous.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It was a whole new experience and I felt very nervous.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">It was a completely new experience, and I felt very nervous.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="41" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>现在已过去了约4分钟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">Approximately 4 minutes have passed.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">It has now elapsed for about 4 minutes.</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">About four minutes have passed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="42" doc-id="111_independent.142390_en.sl">
    <source>她表示“我感觉好多了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.ht">She expressed: “I feel much better.”</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.gg">"I feel much better," she says. ”</translation>
    <translation system="111_independent.142390_en.c6">"I'm feeling much better," she said.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
