<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在太仓市东林村的集体大棚里，48岁的王雪芬正带着工人给梨树喷洒农药。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">In the large collective greenhouse of Donglin Village, Taicang City, workers, led by 48-year-old Wang Xuefen, are spraying pesticide on pear trees.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">The 48-year-old Wang Shefen is carrying workers to the pear tree spraying pesticide in the collective shed at Taicang East Lam Tsuen.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Wang Xuefen, 48, was taking workers to spray pear trees in a collective shed in the village of Donglin, Taicang City.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>全村150亩果园，10多个树种，只需要12位工人加1位技术工程师。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Twelve workers and one technician are enough for the 150mu groove with 10 varieties.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">The Village 150 Mu of orchard, more than 10 species, only need 12 workers plus 1 technical engineers.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">The village of 150 acres of orchards, more than 10 tree species, only 12 workers plus a technical engineer.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>去年5万块钱一共，像我这个年龄，如果在工厂打工肯定拿不到这个钱。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Last year, the total amount of money was fifty thousand. At my age, I definitely couldn’t make this amount of money if I were to work at a factory.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Last year 50,000 dollars altogether, like my age, if I work in the factory will not get the money.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Last year fifty thousand dollars altogether, like my age, if you work in a factory certainly can't get this money.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>去年，东林村村级收入达到2200万元，其中农业总收入占比近一半。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Last year, village-level revenue of Donglin Village reached 22.00 million, of which agricultural income accounted for nearly half of this figure.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Last year, the village-level income reached 22 million yuan, of which total agricultural income accounted for nearly half.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Last year, Donglin's village-level income reached 22 million yuan, of which agriculture accounted for nearly half of total revenue.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>村书记苏齐芳：人均土地种植面积每年在提升，刚开始50亩，现在已经超过100亩；亩均效益每年在增加，职业农民的收入也每年都有增长的余地。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Village Secretary Su Qifang: arable land area per capita is rising each year. It was 50 mu initially, and more than 100 mu now; average efficiency per mu is also rising annually. There is also room for the income of professional farmers to grow each year as well.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Village Secretary Suzifang: Per capita land planting area in ascension each year, just beginning 50 acres, now more than 100 acres, the annual increase in the efficiency of MU, the income of professional farmers also have room for growth every year.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Village Secretary Su Qifang: Per capita land acreage is rising every year, just 50 acres, now more than 100 acres; per acre efficiency is increasing every year, the income of professional farmers have room to grow every year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>股份量化到每一个村民，苏南农村集体经济改革的最大亮点就在于明晰农村集体经营性资产产权并探索政经分开。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Shares have been quantified and distributed to every villager. The biggest highlight of the Sunan Rural Collective Economy Reform is clearly stipulating the ownership of business operation assets of the rural collective and investigating the separation of politics and economy.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Shares quantified to every villager, the biggest bright spot of rural collective economic reform in southern Jiangsu is to clarify the property rights of rural collectively-operated assets and explore the political economy separately.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">The biggest highlight of the rural collective economic reform in southern Jiangsu is to clarify the property rights of rural collective operating assets and to explore the separation of politics and economy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2015年7月，无锡市锡山区安镇街道14个农村经济合作组织与所在村村委会“分账管理”，村委会履行农村公共事务管理，合作组织则主要从事经营。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">The 14 Rural Economic Cooperatives（REC) in Anzhen Neighborhood, Xishan Dis., Wuxi and their corresponding village committees adopted the " account-divided management" from July, 2015. The committees were responsible for public affair, while the cooperatives for operation.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">July 2015, Wuxi Xishan District Town Street, 14 rural Economic Cooperation Organization and Village Committee, "Divide Management", village committee to perform rural public affairs management, cooperative organization is mainly engaged in business.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">In July 2015, 14 rural economic cooperation organizations in the streets of Anzhen, Xishan District, Wuxi City, conducted "separate account management" with their village committees, which performed the management of rural public affairs, while the cooperative organizations were mainly engaged in business operations.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>两个机构两本账，互不“搭界”，防止村干部参与集体资产经营发生腐败现象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">The two institutions will keep separate accounting books to avoid “overlaps”. This will prevent village officials from engaging in corrupt practices when  managing collective assets.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Two institutions two accounts, not "connection", to prevent cadres from participating in the collective asset management corruption phenomenon.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">The two institutions have two sets of accounts and do not "tie up boundaries" with each other, so as to prevent corruption in village cadres' participation in the management of collective assets.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>江苏省农委副主任祝保平介绍说，江苏下一步将继续推动社区股份合作制改革，鼓励农民联合发展，建立村级的民主权力运行机制。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">According to Zhu Baoping, deputy director of the Jiangsu Agriculture Committee, the next step for Jiangsu is to continue to promote reforms pertaining to the community joint stock cooperative system, encourage joint development among farmers, and establish a village-level operating mechanism for democratic rights.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Jiang Caopaoping, deputy director of agriculture of Jiangsu Province, said that the next step will be to promote community shareholding cooperation system reform, encourage farmers to jointly develop, and establish village-level democratic power operation mechanism.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Zhu Baoping, deputy director of the Jiangsu Provincial Agriculture Commission, said that the next step in Jiangsu will be to continue to promote the reform of the community joint-stock cooperative system, encourage the joint development of farmers, and establish a mechanism for the operation of democratic power at the village level.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>祝保平：进一步把改革往前推进，搞社区股份合作，把资产量化到社员，固定到农户，形成明确的产权。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Zhu Baoping: Expand the scope of reforms, implement community shareholding and partnerships, ensure that assets are distributed to community members, ensure fixed shareholding benefits to the farmers, and establish a clear ownership over the industry.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Caopaoping: Further push forward the reform, engage in community share cooperation, quantify the assets to the members, fixed to the farmers, form a clear property rights.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Zhu Baoping: Further push forward the reform, engage in community joint-stock cooperation, quantify the assets to the members, fixed to the farmers, to form a clear property rights.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>通过互联网+，落实他的知情权，决策的参与权及民主管理的监督权，三个权利落实给农户，确实让它变成规范的股份合作的运行机制。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">By way of Internet+, his right to know, right to participate in decision-making, and right to supervise democratic administration are put into practice. The implementation of these three rights for farmers has indeed made it a standard joint stock cooperative operating mechanism.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">Through the Internet +, the implementation of his right to know, decision-making participatory rights and the supervision of democratic management, three of rights to farmers, indeed let it become a normative share of the operating mechanism of cooperation.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">Through the Internet +, the implementation of his right to know, the right to participate in decision-making and supervision of democratic management, the implementation of the three rights to farmers, indeed let it become a standard operating mechanism of joint-stock cooperation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.sl">
    <source>目前，苏南农村新集体经济主要形成了资产租赁型、企业股份型、农业开发型、联合发展型4种发展模式。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.ht">Currently, the new collective economy of Sunan Village is primarily comprised of four development models - the asset lease model, the stock enterprise model, the agricultural development model and the united development model.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.gg">At present, the new rural collective economy of South Jiangsu Province mainly forms 4 kinds of development models, such as asset leasing type, enterprise share type, agricultural development type and joint development type.</translation>
    <translation system="014_ifeng0812.news.49764760_0_zh.c6">At present, the new rural collective economy in southern Jiangsu has mainly formed four types of development models, namely, asset leasing, enterprise shareholding, agricultural development and joint development.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
