<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据外媒报道，当地时间10日，英国首相府唐宁街宣布：英国首相特蕾莎·梅将到瑞士度过暑假，但没有透露具体的休假地点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">Overseas media reported that at 10 AM, local time, the British Prime Minister’s residence at Downing Street announced: British Prime Minister Teresa May will be taking her summer vacation at Switzerland. However, no information has been provided on the exact location of her trip.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">According to foreign media reports, 10th local time, British Prime Minister House Downing Street announced: British Prime Minister Tracy 莎·梅 will go to Switzerland for the summer vacation, but did not disclose the specific vacation location.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">British Prime Minister Theresa May is to spend her summer holidays in Switzerland, Britain's prime minister Downing Street announced Thursday, without giving details of where she will be taking the holiday, foreign media reported.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>有媒体称，在英国公投脱欧后，英国新首相选择到欧洲大陆上的“中立国”瑞士度假，带有某种政策象征性。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">Some media said that after the UK referendum to leave the European Union, the new British Prime Minister opted to have a vacation in Switzerland that has been regarded as a “neutral state” in continental Europe, and act that may be symbolic in terms of policy.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">The media said the British new Prime minister opted for a "neutral" Swiss holiday on the European continent after the British referendum took off, with some kind of policy symbolism.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">Media captionIn the wake of the British referendum on Brexit, Britain's new prime minister chose to take a holiday in Switzerland, a "neutral country" on the European continent, with some sort of policy symbolism.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>英国《卫报》评论称，瑞士这个中立国所代表的象征性在英国首相第一次度假地的选择上发挥了作用。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">A comment in The Guardian claimed that the neutral symbolism of Switzerland has played a role in the UK Prime Minister’s choice of her first holiday destination.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">The British Guardian commented that the symbolism represented by the neutral country in Switzerland played a role in the choice of the British Prime Minister's first resort.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">The Guardian has commented that the symbolism represented by Switzerland as a neutral country played a role in the choice of the British prime minister's first holiday destination.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>英国《每日电讯报》评论指出，特蕾莎·梅选择到瑞士度假，这是撒切尔夫人后，首次再有英国首相到瑞士度假。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">A review in the UK’s The Daily Telegraph pointed out that Theresa May chose to holiday in Switzerland. This was the first time a UK Prime Minister holidayed in Switzerland after Mrs Thatcher.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">The British Daily Telegraph commented that Tracy 莎·梅 chose to go to Switzerland for her holiday, the first time a British prime minister went on holiday in Switzerland after Mrs Thatcher.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">The Daily Telegraph review noted that Theresa May chose to holiday in Switzerland, the first time a British prime minister has visited the country since Mrs Thatcher.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>两位女首相的选择和布莱尔和卡梅伦两位男首相喜欢到较热的地方度假形成了反差。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">The choice of the two female Prime Ministers contrasts with that of the two male Prime Ministers, Blair and Cameron, who liked to holiday in warmer places.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">The choice between the two prime ministers and the two prime ministers of Blair and Cameron, who like to go on holiday in hotter places, contrasts.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">The choice of two female prime ministers contrasts with the two male prime ministers, Tony Blair and David Cameron, who prefer to spend their holidays in hotter places.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据悉，英国新首相特蕾莎·梅将在8月24日返回伦敦，之后等待她的是一系列重要工作和活动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">It was reported that Theresa May, the new Prime Minister of Great Britain, will return to London on August 24. What awaits her next is a series of important tasks and activities.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">It is reported that British new Prime Minister Tracy 莎·梅 will return to London on August 24, after waiting for her is a series of important work and activities.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">It is understood that Britain's new prime minister, Theresa May, will return to London on 24 August, after which a series of important jobs and activities await her.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>英国议会将于9月5日复会，辩论的议题中包括网上要求的举办第二次脱欧公投事宜。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">The British parliament will resume on September 5. Topics for debate include holding a second Brexit referendum as requested online.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">The British Parliament will reconvene on September 5 to include a second Oupang vote on the Internet request.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">The British Parliament will resume on 5 September to debate issues including an online request to hold a second Brexit referendum.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.sl">
    <source>6月23日英国公投决定脱欧，但英国新首相不愿在年底前启动里斯本条约有关成员国脱欧的第50款内容。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.ht">In June 23, the British launched a referendum to leave the European Union (EU). However, the new British Prime Minister is unwilling initiate the contents of Article 50 of the Treaty of Lisbon regarding to withdrawal of member states from the EU before the end of the year.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.gg">The June 23 British referendum decided to take off Europe, but the new prime minister did not want to start the Lisbon Treaty in the 50th section of the member countries off Europe.</translation>
    <translation system="153_ifeng0812.news.49765323_0_zh.c6">The UK voted to leave the EU in a referendum on 23 June, but Britain's new prime minister is reluctant to trigger Article 50 of the Lisbon treaty on member Brexit before the end of the year.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
