<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从表面上看，网络社交平台扩大了交际圈，降低了人们的孤独感。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">On the surface, social networking platforms have widened the social circle and reduced loneliness.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">On the face of it, the network social platform expands the communication circle and reduces people's sense of loneliness.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">On the surface, online social platforms have expanded the social circle and reduced people's feelings of loneliness.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>网络社交的势力范围越发广泛，不仅逐渐取代传统的电话联络，甚至渗入到线下真实的生活圈，悄然改变当下民众的社交生活。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">The scope of influence of online social networking has become increasingly widespread. Not only has it gradually replaced traditional phone communication, it has even permeated actual offline living circles, quietly changing the social activities of the masses.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">The network social sphere is more and more widespread, not only gradually replaces the traditional telephone contact, even penetrates the real life circle under the line, quietly changes the social life of the present people.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">The influence of social networking is becoming more and more extensive, not only gradually replacing the traditional telephone contact, and even infiltrated into the real life circle offline, quietly changing people's social life.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>线上社交的好处是显而易见的，比如方便快捷，所以特别容易受到年轻族群的青睐。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">The benefit of online social networking is obvious. It is easy and convenient, and is therefore much preferred by younger demographics.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">The benefits of online socializing are obvious, such as convenient and quick, so it's especially easy to be favored by younger groups.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">The benefits of online social networking are obvious, such as convenience and speed, making it particularly popular with young people.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>一项针对大学生社交习惯的调查显示，57%的大学生每天使用手机的时间超过5小时，日常生活基本“机不离手”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">A survey investigating college student socializing habits found that 57% of college students spend more than 5 hours a day on cellphones, literally making cellphones “inseparable” during everyday lives.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">A survey of college students ' social habits shows that 57% of college students use their mobile phones more than 5 hours a day, and the basics of daily life are "not on hand".</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">According to a survey on college students' social habits, 57 percent of college students spend more than five hours a day using their mobile phones.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“社交网络具有低成本、传输速度快、多人同时交流等特点，符合当代大学生的需求。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">“The characteristics of social networks include being low-cost, having fast transmission rates, and allowing many people to interact simultaneously. This suits the needs of contemporary university students.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">"Social networks have the characteristics of low cost, fast transmission speed and simultaneous communication among many people, which is in line with the needs of contemporary college students." ”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">"Social networking has the characteristics of low cost, high transmission speed and multiple people communicating at the same time, which meets the needs of contemporary college students."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>扩大人际关系圈，更平等地对话，避免社交顾虑，才是我们越发深爱线上聊的主要原因。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">Expanded relationship circles, being able to chat on equal footing, and avoidance of social stigma are the main reasons why we become increasingly fond of online chat.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">Expanding the circle of relationships, talking more equitably, and avoiding social concerns are the main reasons why we love online chat.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Expanding the circle of relationships, having more equal conversations, and avoiding social concerns are the main reasons why we love online chatting more and more.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刚进公司的新人热爱跟同事线上交流，“因为才进单位大家不太熟，通过社交平台的点赞评论，关系才比以前近了许多”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">The newcomers enjoy online communication with other employees, " because we are not familiar with each other at the beginning. But the 'like' and comment in the social media will close the distance."</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">Just entered the company's new love with colleagues online communication, "because only into the unit is not very familiar, through the social platform of Praise comments, the relationship is much closer than before."</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Newcomers to the company love to communicate with colleagues online, "because they are not familiar with the unit, through the social platform praise comments, the relationship is much closer than before."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>爱交友的也常用线上交流，“之前跟朋友因为一些误会有段时间没联络了，后来在一个大群里先对话几句才又热络起来。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">People who enjoy making friends also used online networking. “I haven’t been contacting a friend for a while due to some misunderstanding. We then shared a few words in a larger group and things got better from there.”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">Love friends also commonly used on-line communication, "before with friends because some misunderstanding for a period of time did not contact, and later in a large group of dialogue before a few words and heat up." ”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Love to make friends is also commonly used online communication, "with friends before because of some misunderstanding did not contact for some time, and later in a large group of first dialogue a few words before they warm up again."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>IT工程师吴言是深度网络社交爱好者，他大部分的社交生活都发生于线上，网络联系人更数倍于线下朋友圈人数。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">IT engineer Wu Yan is strong fan for social networking, and spends most of his socializing time and life online, with many more online contacts than friends he meet offline.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">It engineer Wu Yan is a deep network of social enthusiasts, most of his social life occurs online, network contacts are more than the number of online friends circle.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Wu Yan, an IT engineer, is a deep social network enthusiast. Most of his social life takes place online, with online contacts several times larger than the number of offline friends.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>吴言自己也坦言在网络上更“如鱼得水”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">Wu Yan himself honestly said that he feels like “fish returned to the water” when he goes online.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">Wu Yan himself also frankly in the network more "duck to water."</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Wu Yan himself also admitted to being more "like a duck to water" on the Internet.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“可以在自己方便愿意的时候回复朋友，因为有很多斟酌字句的时间，表述也能更清楚。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">“You may reply to a friend when you are willing at a time that is convenient for you to do so because there is plenty of time for you to deliberate the wordings, and you can also express yourself more clearly.”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">"You can reply to your friends when you want to, because there are a lot of time to think about it. ”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">"You can reply to a friend when it's convenient for you, because you have a lot of time to think about words and you can express them more clearly."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“隐藏在ID之下的你来我往避免了面对面的人际碰撞，不仅有了回旋的余地，甚至给了彼此更多思忖言行的时间和空间。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">“The ID provides one with a cover to avoid all face-to-face interpersonal conflicts, providing one with more room to maneuver and also provided both sides with more time and space to think about what they say.”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">"Hidden under the ID of you come to me to avoid face-to-face interpersonal collisions, not only have the leeway to maneuver, even give each other more time and space to contemplate words and deeds. ”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">"Hidden under the ID, you and I avoid face-to-face collisions, not only have room to maneuver, and even give each other more time and space to think about words and deeds."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“不同身份的人有了同样发言的权利和效率，现实生活中的种种社交顾虑，在网络空间似乎都一下消除。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">“People of different status are given the same rights to speech and the same voice. Various social taboos in real life seem to disappear in the online world.”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">"People of different identities have the same rights and efficiency to speak, and social concerns in real life seem to have been eliminated in cyberspace," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">"People of different identities have the right and efficiency to speak the same way, and social concerns in real life seem to be dispelled in cyberspace."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>然而吴言的朋友小鹏却觉得，生活中的吴言是个“蛮无趣的宅男”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">Xiaopeng, a friend of Wu Yan, felt that the real life Wu Yan is a “boring geek”.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">However, Wu Yan's friend Xiao Peng felt that the life of Wu Yan is a "pretty boring otaku."</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">However, Wu Yan's friend Xiao Peng feels that Wu Yan in life is a "pretty boring house man."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>小鹏和吴言在一个大群里相识，因为两人都是积极发言者，很快就熟络起来了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">Xiaopeng and Wu Yan met in a big group. As they were both active speakers, they became acquainted very quickly.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">Xiao Peng and Wu Yan in a large group of acquaintances, because both are active speakers, soon cooked up.</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Xiao Peng and Wu Yan met in a large group because they were both active speakers and soon became familiar with each other.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.sl">
    <source>小鹏觉得吴言跟网络上判若两人，言语枯燥，也不主动发表意见，翻来覆去就是几句“呵呵，好的，是吗”，要不就是“这个我要上网查一下”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.ht">Xiaopeng felt that Wu Yan was completely different from his online personality. The real Wu Yan used little words and never gave any opinions. The only phrases he would use were: “Ho ho. Alright. Really?” or “I’ll check that online.”</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.gg">Xiaopeng think Wu talk with the network, speech boring, also do not take the initiative to comment, tossing and turning is a few words "hehe, good, is it", or "This I want to check the Internet."</translation>
    <translation system="025_ifeng0812.news.49767202_0_zh.c6">Xiao Peng feels that Wu Yan is different from the Internet, the language is boring, do not take the initiative to express their views, flipping over and over is a few words, "Oh, OK, is it", or "This I want to check on the Internet."</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
