<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>中新网记者梳理发现，目前至少已有河北、吉林、天津、江西、四川、海南、甘肃、福建、北京等9个省市出台了居住证实施细则。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">China News Service reporter compiled the facts and found that enforcement rules for the residence permit have been established in 9 provinces and cities, namely: Hebei, Jilin, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Sichuan, Hainan, Gansu, Fujian, and Beijing.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">Beijing reporter combed found that at present at least Hebei, Jilin, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Sichuan, Hainan, Gansu, Fujian, Beijing and other 9 provinces and cities issued a residence permit implementation rules.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">At least nine provinces and cities, including Hebei, Jilin, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Sichuan, Hainan, Gansu, Fujian and Beijing, have issued detailed rules for the implementation of residence permits, according to Xinhua.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>对于申领居住证的条件，上述地区普遍提出，需居住半年以上，符合有合法稳定就业、合法稳定住所、连续就读条件之一。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">As regards the conditions for applying for a residence permit, the above regions generally state that a person has to stay for more than half a year, comply with one of the conditions of having legal and stable employment, legal and stable residence, and continuous study.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">For the conditions of applying for residence permit, the above-mentioned areas are generally proposed to live for more than half a year, in accordance with the legal stability of employment, lawful stable residence, one of the conditions of continuous study.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">With regard to the conditions for applying for a residence permit, the above-mentioned areas generally propose that they need to live for more than six months and meet one of the conditions for having legal and stable employment, legal and stable residence and continuous schooling.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>中新网记者注意到，在居住证提供的待遇方面，各地“含金量”不一，与国家版的规定相比，一些地区提供的公共服务和便利的范围有所扩大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">China News Service reporters noticed that benefits that came with a residence permit differ in terms of “value” from place to place. Compared to the provisions stipulated in the national version, the scope of public services and conveniences provided by some regions has been extended.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">Beijing, the reporter noted that the treatment of residence permits, the "gold" in different places, compared with the national version of the provisions of some areas to provide public services and facilitate the scope of expansion.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">In terms of the treatment offered by residence permits, the "gold content" varies from place to place, and the range of public services and facilities offered in some areas has expanded compared with the state version of the rules.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>这些地区均增加了子女在满足相关条件下可在当地参加中高考的便利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">These regions have added the convenience of allowing children who meet relevant terms and conditions to take part in college entrance exams.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">These areas have increased the ease with which children can participate in the local college entrance examination under the relevant conditions.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">These areas have increased the convenience for children to participate in the local entrance examination under the relevant conditions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>此外，北京等多地还明确要求，逐步扩大提供公共服务和便利的范围，并定期向社会公布。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">Moreover, Beijing and many other cities decided to expand public services progressively with regular public announcement.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">In addition, Beijing has also clearly asked for a gradual expansion of the scope of public services and facilitation, and is regularly published to the community.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">In addition, Beijing and other places have also explicitly requested that the scope of the provision of public services and facilities be gradually expanded and made known to the public on a regular basis.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>如，福建提出，至少每3年向社会公布一次居住证持有人享受的公共服务和便利的范围。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">For instance, as proposed by Fujian, an announcement should be made to the public at least once every three years as regards the scope of public services and conveniences enjoyed by persons holding residence permits.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">For example, Fujian proposes to publish to society at least every 3 years the scope of public services and conveniences enjoyed by the holder of a residence permit.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">For example, Fujian proposed that the scope of public services and facilities enjoyed by holders of residence permits should be made known to the public at least once every three years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>《居住证暂行条例》规定，对符合居住证办理条件的，公安机关应当自受理之日起15日内制作发放居住证。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">The Interim Regulation on Residence Permits stipulate that an individual who meets the criteria for applying for a residence permit, the police department shall, within 15 days after accepting the application, prepare and issue the residence permit.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">The "Temporary residence permit" stipulates that the public security organs shall, within 15th from the date of acceptance, make the issuance of residence permits in accordance with the conditions of the residence permit.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">According to the Interim Regulations on Residence Permits, the public security organs shall, within 15 days from the date of acceptance, make and issue residence permits for those who meet the requirements for the processing of residence permits.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>对于发证时限，大部分地区跟国家版的意见一致，即在15日内发放。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">As to the release time, most areas will follow the national regulation, namely, in 15 workdays.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">With regard to the time limit for issuance, most areas are in line with the national version, which is to be issued within 15th.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">With regard to the time frame for the issuance of certificates, most regions are in agreement with the national version, which is issued within 15 days.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>河北明确，对符合申领条件、材料齐全的，居住地公安派出所应自受理之日起3个工作日内发放居住证。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">Hebei clearly states that any individual who fulfills the criteria and provides the required documents, the local police station of the place of residence shall issue a residence permit within 3 days after the applications were accepted.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">Hebei clear, to meet the requirements of the conditions, material complete, residential police stations should be accepted from the date of 3 working days from the issuance of residence permits.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">Hebei has made it clear that for those who meet the requirements for application and have complete materials, the police station of their place of residence shall issue their residence permits within three working days from the date of acceptance.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>江西规定，符合居住证申领条件且证明材料齐全的，公安机关应当自受理之日起5个工作日内制作发放居住证。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">The regulations of Jiangxi stipulated that for those who fulfill the conditions for receiving a residence permit and have provided all evidentiary documents, the local police station must prepare and issue a residence permit within 5 working days after accepting the application.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">Jiangxi stipulates that the public security organs shall make the issuance of residence permits within 5 working days from the date of acceptance, in accordance with the conditions for applying for residence permits and the complete proof materials.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">Jiangxi stipulates that if the conditions for applying for a residence permit are met and the supporting documents are complete, the public security organ shall make and issue a residence permit within five working days from the date of accepting the application.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>按照《居住证暂行条例》规定，上述地区均明确，首次申领居住证，免收证件工本费。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">According to the Provisional Regulations of Residence Permit, the applicants for the permit will be free of administrative fee in the above-mentioned areas.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">In accordance with the "temporary residence permit" provisions, the above areas are clear, the first time to apply for a residence permit, exemption certificate fees.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">In accordance with the provisions of the Provisional Regulations on Residence Permits, the above-mentioned areas have all made it clear that they will apply for a residence permit for the first time and will be exempted from the payment of documentation fees.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.sl">
    <source>如，四川要求，各地公安派出所或者受委托的社区服务机构要严格执行核定的收费项目及收费标准，坚决禁止超范围、超标准收费或搭车收费。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.ht">For instance, Sichuan Province requested that local police stations or authorized community service organizations should rigorously implement approved charges and tariffs, firmly forbidding tariffs or fares that exceeded their range or standard.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.gg">For example, Sichuan requirements, local police stations or commissioned community service agencies to strictly enforce the approved fee items and fees standards, resolutely prohibit the super scope, super standard fees or ride charges.</translation>
    <translation system="093_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9305340_zh.c6">For example, Sichuan requires that local police stations or commissioned community service agencies strictly implement the approved charging items and rates, and resolutely prohibit overcharging, overcharging or hitchhiking charges.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
