<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>波特兰冶炼厂的未来因供电合同的取消而充满不确定性</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">Future of Portland smelter uncertain with cancellation of power supply contract</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">Future of the Portland smelter is fraught with uncertainty due to the cancellation of the power supply contract</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The future of the Portland smelter is fraught with uncertainty due to the cancellation of the power supply contract</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>由于为工厂供电的电力公司透露了一名工厂所有人将终止一份供应合同，从而使所有供应合同失效，位于维多利亚的波特兰铝冶炼厂以及工厂数百名工人目前正面临着不确定的未来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">The power company supply power to the plants disclosed that the owner of the plant will be terminating a supplier contract, an act that would lead to termination of all supplier contracts. The Portland Aluminum Smelter plant in Victoria and hundreds of workers currently face an uncertain future.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">As the factory-powered power company disclosed that a factory owner would terminate a supply contract to invalidate all supply contracts, the hundreds of workers at the Portland aluminium smelter in Victoria and the factory are facing an uncertain future.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The Portland aluminium smelter in Victoria, as well as hundreds of workers at the plant, is now facing an uncertain future as the power company that powers the plant has revealed that a factory owner will terminate a supply contract, thus invalidating all supply contracts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>这一举措发生在维多利亚政府决定不继续发放保证工厂运营的补贴之后。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">This measure was enacted after the government of Victoria decided to stop issuing subsidies that help keep the plants in business.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">The move comes after the Victorian government decided not to continue to subsidize factory operations.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The move comes after the Victorian government decided not to continue paying subsidies to keep factories operating.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>这笔为期20年的固定补贴将在11月终止。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">This 20-year fixed subsidy will end in November.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">The 20-year fixed subsidy will expire in November.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The 20-year fixed subsidy is due to expire in November.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>美铝公司波特兰工厂的2000名工人可能面临失业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">The 2,000 workers at the Portland plant of Alcoa Corporation may lose their jobs.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">2000 workers at Alcoa's Portland plant may face unemployment.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">Two thousand workers at Alcoa's Portland plant could face losing their jobs.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>一旦工厂关闭，可能有多达2000人直接或间接失业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">Once the factory shuts down, up to 2,000 people may find themselves directly or indirectly out of a job.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">As soon as the factory closes, there may be as many as 2000 people directly or indirectly unemployed.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">As many as 2,000 people could lose their jobs, directly or indirectly, once the plant closes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>并且由于该工厂的用电量占到维多利亚全部电力输出的约10%，因此可能还会产生连锁反应。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">As total energy use of this plant makes up 10% of total power output of Victoria, it is unlikely that it would generate a chain reaction.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">And because the plant uses about 10% of all of Victoria's electricity output, it may also have a ripple effect.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">And since the plant accounts for about 10 per cent of Victoria's total electricity output, there could be a knock-on effect.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>2014年，美铝公司关闭了汉瑞角冶炼厂，这导致了去年安格尔西岛发电厂的关闭。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">Alcoa Corporation shut down the Point Henry aluminum plant in 2014, which led to the shutdown of the Anglesey power station last year.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">Alcoa closed the Hanry Kok smelter in 2014, leading to the closure of the Anglesey power plant last year.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">Alcoa closed the Cape Hanley smelter in 2014, which led to the closure of the Anglesey power plant last year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>美铝公司波特兰冶炼厂目前正在亏损并且面临关闭风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">Alcoa’s Portland smelting plant is now loss-making and is at risk of closing down.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">Alcoa's Portland smelter is currently losing money and facing a risk of closure.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">Alcoa's Portland smelter is losing money and is at risk of closure.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>此举是在对工厂未来几年作出预测之后作出的，最初的原因是澳元的走强，而最近则是因为工厂产品的价格。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">This measure was implemented after making predictions on the near future of the factory. The initial reason was the appreciation of the Australian Dollar. The recent reason is the price of the factory products.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">The move comes after a forecast for the factory in the next few years, initially because of the strength of the Australian dollar and, more recently, the price of the factory's products.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The move follows forecasts for the plant over the next few years, initially due to a stronger Australian dollar and more recently because of the price of the factory's products.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>AGL通过拉特罗布山谷老埃杨发电厂为这座大型铝冶炼厂提供电能。该公司预测另外三名工厂所有人也将终止其协议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">AGL made use of the Latrobe Valley Loy Yang power plant to supply electrical power to this large aluminum smelting facility. This company also expects 3 owners of the factory to terminate the contract in the future.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">AGL supplies electricity to the large aluminium smelter through the Latrobe Valley old Eyang power plant. The company predicts that three other factory owners will also terminate their agreement.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">AGL, which supplies electricity to the large aluminium smelter through the Laoeyang power plant in the Latrobe Valley, predicted that three other plant owners would also terminate their agreement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>工厂的最大股东是一家美铝公司和氧化铝公司的合资公司，而中国的中信集团和日本的丸红株式会社也持有少量股份。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">The largest shareholder is a joint venture formed by Alcoa Corporation and Alox Company. CITIC Group from China and Marubeni Corporation from Japan also holds a small percentage of the shares.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">The largest shareholder in the plant is a joint venture between Alcoa and Alumina, while China's Citic Group and Japan's Marunouchi company also hold a small stake.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The largest shareholder in the plant is a joint venture between Alcoa and Alumina, while China's Citic Group and Japan's Marubeni Corporation also hold small stakes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>该合资公司表示：“AGL预计波特兰工厂将继续运营，也就是说这座冶炼厂将继续产生电力需求。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">The joint venture expressed: “AGL expects the Portland facility to continue operations. In other words, this smelting plant shall continue to demand electrical power.”</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">"AGL expects the Portland plant to continue operating, which means the smelter will continue to generate electricity demand," the joint venture said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">"AGL expects the Portland plant to continue operating, meaning the smelter will continue to generate electricity demand," the joint venture said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>AGL表示这些合同是本来应该自2016年11月起生效的“对冲合同”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">AGL said that these contracts were “hedging contracts” that should have become effective on November 2016.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">AGL said the contracts were "hedging contracts" that should have been in force since November 2016.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">AGL said the contracts were "hedging contracts" that should have been in effect since November 2016.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>合同的终止期为12个月，因此它们将在2017年终止。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">The contract has a termination period of 12 months, and thus will be terminated in 2017.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">The termination period of the contract is 12 months, so they will terminate in 2017.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The contract was terminated for 12 months, so they will be terminated in 2017.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>该电力公司表示：“因此，AGL仍预测这些合同将在2017财年继续产生收入。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">The power company said, “As such, AGL still predicts these contracts to continue to produce revenue in fiscal year 2017.”</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">"Therefore, AGL still predicts that these contracts will continue to generate revenue in fiscal year 2017," the power company said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">"As a result, AGL still predicts that these contracts will continue to generate revenue in fiscal 2017," the power company said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>自2018财年起对AGL可能产生的任何收入影响目前都受到期货市场对于批发电价的乐观展望。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">For the fiscal year of 2018, any impact to revenue that may be generated for AGL is currently affected by the optimistic prospects held by the futures market regarding the prices of wholesale electricity.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">Any revenue impact on AGL from the fiscal year 2018 is now a bullish outlook for wholesale electricity prices in the futures market.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">Any potential revenue impact on AGL from FY2018 is currently subject to the futures market's optimistic outlook for wholesale electricity prices.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>AGL表示，公司已在“终止活动预期”中减记了1.87亿美元的合同价值。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">AGL expressed that the company has down-written a contract value of 187 million USD for “expected event of termination”.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">AGL said the company had reduced its contract value by $187 million in "ending activity expectations".</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">AGL said the company had written down the contract value of $187 million in "termination activity expectations."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>美铝公司表示，决定终止这些合同“不会影响美铝公司经营该冶炼厂或保证该冶炼厂电力供应的能力”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">Alcoa said that the decision to terminate the contracts ”does not affect Alcoa’s ability to operate the smelter or secure electricity supply to the smelter”.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">Alcoa said the decision to terminate the contracts "will not affect Alcoa's ability to operate the smelter or to guarantee the smelter's power supply."</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">Alcoa said the decision to terminate the contracts "will not affect Alcoa's ability to operate the smelter or guarantee the smelter's electricity supply."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>这家美国公司表示其在2010年与老埃杨签署了一份为期20年的合同，该合同本来将在今年11月生效，但该公司没有解释为何退出该合同。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">This American company expressed that they have signed a 20-year contract with Loy Yang in 2010. This contract was supposed to enter into force in November this year, but this company did not explain why it chose to withdraw.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">The US company said it signed a 20-year contract with old Eyang in 2010, which would have come into effect in November this year, but the company did not explain why the contract was withdrawn.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">The US company said it signed a 20-year contract with Mr Eyang in 2010, which would have taken effect in November, but did not explain why it had withdrawn from the contract.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>分析家对于位于维多利亚的波特兰冶炼厂以及位于纽卡斯尔附近的托马戈工厂是否会因为行业糟糕的经济形势而关闭持谨慎态度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">Analysts remain circumspect with respect to the closure of the Portland Foundry at Victoria and Tomago plant in Newcastle as a result of the bad economy.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">Analysts caution about whether the Tomago plant in Victoria's Portland smelter and near NKSR will be closed because of the industry's dire economic situation.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">Analysts are cautious about whether the Portland smelter in Victoria and the Tomago plant near Newcastle will close because of the industry's poor economic conditions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>针对分析师在本周早些时候发表的评论，AGL运营主管史蒂芬·米克尔森表示波特兰每年的用电量达到约600兆瓦，托马戈工厂达到约900兆瓦。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">According to comments published earlier this week by analysts, AGL’s head of operations Stephen Mikkelsen expressed that annual power consumption of the Portland plant amounted to about 600 megawatt, while that of the Tomago plant was at about 900 megawatt.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">In response to analysts ' comments earlier this week, AGL operations director 史蒂芬·米克尔森 said Portland's electricity consumption reached about 600 megawatts a year, and the Tomago plant reached about 900 megawatts.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">In response to comments from analysts earlier this week, AGL operations chief Stephen Mickelson said Portland uses about 600 megawatts of electricity a year and the Tomago plant about 900 megawatts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>如果两家工厂关闭，则电力市场的需求量会大大减少。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">If two factories close down, demand in the electricity market will fall significantly.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">If two factories shut down, the demand for electricity market will be greatly reduced.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">If the two factories shut down, the demand for electricity in the market would be greatly reduced.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.sl">
    <source>他表示：“作为一家电力公司，这对于我们来说可不是一个好消息”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.ht">He expressed that: “As a power company, this is not good news to us.”</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.gg">"It's not good news for us as a power company," he says.</translation>
    <translation system="144_smh.com.au.191308_en.c6">"This is not good news for us as an electricity company," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
