<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>戴图理凭借 Predilection 在纽马基特的成功取得职业3,000胜</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Victory of Dettori and Predilection providing the 3,000th career win</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Daituri with the success of predilection in Newmarket career 3,000 win</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Dettori wins 3,000 career wins with Predilection's success at Newmarket</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>纽马基特的两场胜利助力戴图理取得职业3,000胜，之后他喷香槟庆祝</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">2 wins at Newmarket allow Dettori to reach 3,000 career wins and hold a champagne party afterwards</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Newmarket's two victories helped Daituri get a career 3,000 victory, after which he sprayed champagne to celebrate</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Newmarket's two victories helped Dayturi to 3,000 career wins before he sprayed champagne to celebrate</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>周五，职业赛马骑师戴图理 (Frankie Dettori) 在纽马基特 (Newmarket) 取得了他的第3,000场胜利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">On Friday, professional jockey Frankie Dettori achieved his 3,000th career win at Newmarket.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">In Friday, professional jockey Daituri (Frankie Dettori) made his 3rd, 000 victory in Newmarket (Newmarket).</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Professional jockey Frankie Dettori had his 3,000 win at Newmarket on Friday.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他策着出自练马师高仕登 (John Gosden) 之手的 Predilection 在马道上急驰，于当晚收获两场胜利，也借此实现了职业3,000胜。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Mounting Predilection, the horse trained by the famous John Gosden, he raced down the tracks and achieved two victories at that night which helped him achieve 3,000 career wins.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">He took the Gollsden (John Gosden) 's hand predilection on the road, the two victories in the evening, also to achieve a career 3,000 win.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">He raced down the track with Predilection, written by trainer John Gosden, to two victories that night and a career-high 3,000.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>这位现年45岁的意大利人是第六位在平地赛领域取得这一里程碑的职业赛马骑师。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">This 45-year old Italian is the sixth professional jockey to achieve this milestone in flat racing.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">The 45-year-old Italian is the sixth professional jockey who has achieved this milestone in the field.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">The 45-year-old Italian is the sixth professional jockey to reach this milestone in the field.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>前五位分别是：哥顿·李察 (Gordon Richards) 爵士、道格·史密斯 (Doug Smith)、柏葛 (Lester Piggott)、魏德礼 (Pat Eddery) 和嘉逊 (Willie Carson)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">The first five are: Sir Gordon Richards, Doug Smith, Lester Piggott, Pat Eddery, and Willie Carson.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">The first five were: Gordon Richard (Gordon Richards), Doug (Doug Smith), Berge (Lester Piggott), Weideley (Pat eddery) and Jason (Willie Carson).</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">The top five are: Sir Gordon Richards, Doug Smith, Lester Piggott, Pat Eddery and Willie Carson.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>早前在 Ghayyar 获胜的三届冠军骑师戴图理说：“这很特别。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Dettori, three-time champion and winner of the Ghayyar races, said: “This is very special.”</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">"This is special," said Daituri, a three-year champion jockey who won the Ghayyar earlier. ”</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">"It's pretty special," said Dai Tully, a three-time champion jockey who won earlier at Ghayyyar.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>我很激动，因为我的家人也在现场</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">I’m excited because my family was there at the site</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">I'm excited because my family is on the scene.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">I was thrilled because my family were there</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>我对自己在纽马基特取得的成绩感到高兴，因为30年前我就是从这里起步的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">I am happy about what I’ve achieved at Newmarket because this is the place where I started 30 years ago.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">I am pleased with what I have achieved in Newmarket because I started here 30 years ago.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">I'm happy with what I've achieved at Newmarket, because that's where I started 30 years ago.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>这不是一场大规模的赛马会，也不是英国皇家爱斯科赛马会 (Royal Ascot)，这只是一个有着20,000名观众的普通的周五晚上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">This is not a large scale horse racing event nor the Royal Ascot. This is just a normal Friday night with 20,000 members in the audience.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">This is not a large-scale Jockey club, nor is it the Royal Ascot, which is just an ordinary Friday night with 20,000 spectators.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">It's not a massive race or the Royal Ascot, it's just an ordinary Friday night with 20,000 spectators.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>我很欣慰，也很谦恭。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">I am very pleased and very humbled.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">I am gratified and humble.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">I'm relieved and humbled.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>戴图理在获胜后牵来了 Predilection，引起了全场欢呼</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Crowd cheered as Dettori brought in Predilection after claiming victory</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Daituri in the victory after the predilection, causing the audience cheers</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">The crowd cheered when Dettori brought Predilation after his victory</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>在障碍赛领域，有两名骑师取得了这一成就，他们分别是冠军骑师理查德·约翰逊 (Richard Johnson) 和现已退役的20届冠军麦考伊 (Anthony McCoy) 爵士，其中麦考伊爵士在其破纪录的职业生涯中取得了超过4,300场胜利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Two equestrians have made this achievement in the cross-country event, namely champion rider Richard Johnson and 20-times world champion who has retired, Sir Anthony McCoy. Sir McCoy has broke the record by achieving more than 4,300 victories in his entire career.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">In the area of the barrier, two jockeys have made this achievement, respectively the champion jockey 理查德·约翰逊 (Richard Johnson) and now retired 20 champion McCoy (Anthony McCoy) jazz, of which Sir McCoy has scored more than 4 in his record-breaking career, 300 victories.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">The achievement was made by two jockeys in the obstacle course, champion jockey Richard Johnson and now retired 20-time champion Sir Anthony McCoy, who has won more than 4,300 in his record-breaking career.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>柏葛是九届德比赛冠军，在其职业生涯中共取得了4,493场胜利</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Piggott is a nine-times derby champion and has achieved 4,493 wins throughout his career.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Berge, a nine-year-German champion, won 4,493 victories in his career.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Berger is a nine-time German champion with 4,493 victories in his career</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>戴图理是当代最棒的骑师之一，所以他取得这一里程碑式成就也就不足为奇了，在他之前取得这一成就的人不多。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Dettori is one of the best jockey of this time. It is not surprising that he will be able to make it to this milestone achievement. Not many people before him could claim to have reached this step.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Daituri is one of the best jockeys in the contemporary era, so it is not surprising that he has achieved this milestone, not many people have achieved it before.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Dettori is one of the best jockeys of his generation, so it's no surprise that he achieved this milestone, not many before him.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他时尚而健硕，但是真正让他在称重室中脱颖而出的却是他在战术上的理性。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">He is fashionable and has a well-built figure. However, the reason that he was able to stand out from the through the weighing station was his rational use of tactics.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">He is fashionable and robust, but what really makes him stand out in the weighing room is his tactical rationality.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">He's stylish and robust, but it's his tactical rationality that really makes him stand out in the weighing room.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他是一位了不起的马术大使，多年来，他的热情和魅力为这项运动吸引了大量粉丝。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">He is an impressive equestrian and its representative. For many years, his passion and charms have attracted a large number of fans to the sport.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">He is a great equestrian ambassador, and over the years his enthusiasm and charisma have attracted a lot of fans for the sport.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">He is an amazing equestrian ambassador whose enthusiasm and charisma have attracted a large number of fans to the sport over the years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>几周前，我在 Epsom 跟戴图理说，如果他不仅仅是一个周末与大赛骑师，他应该已经能取得6,000场胜利了！</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">A few weeks ago, I told Dettori at Epsom that if he wasn’t a jockey merely during weekends and at major races, he would already have won 6,000 victories!</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">A few weeks ago, I told Daituri in Epsom that if he wasn't just a weekend and a big-game jockey, he should have won 6,000 victories!</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">A few weeks ago, I told Dettori at Epsom that if he had been more than a weekend with a competition jockey, he should have been able to claim 6,000 wins!</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>说真的，戴图理堪称英国三十年来最好的马术获胜者，这一点太重要了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">In truth, Dettori is the jockey with the best record of riding winners that Britain has seen in 30 years. This is something extremely important.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Seriously, Daituri is the best equestrian winner in 30 years in Britain.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Seriously, it's so important that he's Britain's best equestrian winner in three decades.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他性格活泼，这对英国赛马来说是好事，但是除此之外，他还是一位不可思议的骑师。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">He has a lively personality, which is good news for the British horse racing society. In addition to that, he is an astounding jockey.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">He was lively, and that was a good thing for the British horse race, but beyond that he was an incredible jockey.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">He has a lively personality, which is good for British horse racing, but beyond that, he's an incredible jockey.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>戴图理以其标志性的跳跃下马动作庆祝这一里程碑</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Dettori celebrates milestone with signature flying dismount</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Daituri celebrates the milestone with its iconic jump-dismount action</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Dettori celebrates this milestone with his signature jump and dismount.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>从跳跃冲线到跳跃下马，二十年来，戴图理一直是英国平地赛领域的典型代表。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Dettori has always been a classic representative for the British sport of flat racing for over 20 years with his distinctive flying finish and flying dismount.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">For 20 years, Daituri has been a typical representative of the British Land race field, from jumping lines to jumping off the ground.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">From jumping the line to jumping off the horse, Dettori has been a typical representative of the field of flat racing in Britain for two decades.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他的职业生涯如过山车一般。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">His career is like a roller coaster.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">His career is like a roller coaster.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">His career has been a rollercoaster ride.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他获得了多场大赛的冠军，其中包括1996年在英国皇家爱斯科赛马会取得的著名的“七连胜”，但是，他也遭遇了坠机事件，还因服用禁药遭到禁赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">He is a champion of many competitions, and have achieved the famous “7 consecutive victories” in the 1996 Royal Ascot horse races. However, he was also affected by a plane crash and barred from the races due to use of prohibited substances.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">He won several championships, including the famous "Seven winning streak" in 1996 at the Royal Love Club, but he also suffered a crash and was banned for taking the banned drugs.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">He won several tournaments, including the famous "seven wins" at the Royal Ascot in 1996, but he also suffered a plane crash and was banned for taking drugs.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>三年前，当他在六个月禁期结束后重回赛场时，曾一度很吃力。但是，他表现出了惊人的性格优势，并终于重回巅峰，给那些持怀疑态度的人当头一棒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Three years ago, he found it taxing when he first returned to the game after a six-month suspension, but he showed amazing strength of character, and finally returned to his peak form, defying doubters.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">Three years ago, when he returned to the game after the end of the six-month cut-off period, he struggled. However, he showed an astonishing character advantage and finally returned to the top, giving blow to those who were skeptical.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">Three years ago, when he returned to the game after a six-month ban, it was a struggle, but he showed amazing character strengths and finally returned to the top, giving skeptics a beating.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="090_bbc.242418_en.sl">
    <source>他或许做不了太长时间了——戴图理之前曾说过，他希望至少能参赛到50岁前。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.ht">Dettori once said that he probably doesn’t have much time left, but hope that he can participate in the games before he reaches 50 years of age.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.gg">He may not be able to do it for a long time-Daituri has said before that he wants to be at least 50 years old.</translation>
    <translation system="090_bbc.242418_en.c6">He may not be able to do it for too long - Dayturi has said before that he wants to compete until he is at least 50.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
