<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>西蒙·拜尔斯摘得女子体操全能冠军</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Simon Biles acquires women's individual all-around champion</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">西蒙·拜尔斯 Picks Women gymnastics all-around champion</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Simon Byers wins women's gymnastics all-around title</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>忘掉压力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Forget about stress.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Forget about stress.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Forget about the pressure.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>忘掉炒作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Forget about speculation.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Forget about hype.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Forget the hype.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>西蒙·拜尔斯 (Simone Biles) 不受这一切的影响。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Simone Biles was unaffected by all this.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">西蒙·拜尔斯 (Simone Biles) is not affected by all this.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Simone Biles is unaffected by all this.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>跳马时充满活力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Energetic performance on the pummel horse.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The vault was full of vigor.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">The vault is full of energy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>平衡木上游刃有余。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Performing with ease on the balance beam.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">On the balance beam.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">the balance beam.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>自由体操动作惊艳。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Astounding gymnastic routines in the floor event.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The floor exercises are stunning.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">The floor exercise is amazing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>整体表现非常精彩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">The entire performance was extremely exciting.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The overall performance is excellent.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">The overall performance was excellent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>现在，终于成为了奥运冠军。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Finally, an Olympic champion.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Now, finally, became the Olympic champion.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Now, finally, an Olympic champion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>这位19岁的美国体操运动员周四摘得了全能冠军，充分在奥运赛场上展示了她在体操方面领先世界的天赋。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">This 19-year-old American gymnast took the all-around gold medal on Thursday, fully displaying her unparalleled gift in gymnastics at the Olympic Games.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The 19-year-old American gymnast picked up all-around in Thursday and showcased her talent for the world in gymnastics in the Olympic arena.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">The 19-year-old American gymnast took the all-around title Thursday to fully showcase her talent for leading the world in gymnastics at the Olympic Stadium.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>她以62.198的总分远超银牌得主、“终极五人组”(Final Five) 队员莱斯曼 (Aly Raisman) 和铜牌得主俄罗斯选手穆斯塔芬娜 (Aliya Mustafina)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">She won the gold by a total of 62.198, much higher than the score of the Silver winner Aly Raisman from the Final Five and Bronze Aliya Mustafina from Russia.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">She has a 62.198 overall score far beyond the silver medalist, the "Ultimate Five" (final Five) player Lesman (Aly Raisman) and bronze medalist Mustafina (Aliya Mustafina).</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">She topped silver medalist Aly Raisman, a member of the Final Five, and bronze medalist Aliya Mustafina of Russia with a combined score of 62.198.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>来自美国的西蒙-拜尔斯于周四在巴西里约热内卢举的2016年夏季奥运会的艺术体操女子个人全能决赛上进行了平衡木表演。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">On Thursday, American Simone Biles performed on the balance beam for the women’s individual all-around gymnastic event at the 2016 Summer Olympic Games held at Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Simon Byers, from the United States, performed the balance beam on the women's personal all-around finals at the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, in Thursday.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Simon Byers from the United States performs on the balance beam during the artistic gymnastics women's individual all-around final at the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, on Thursday.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯帮助美国队在奥运会女子体操个人全能上实现了四连冠，她个人在本届奥运会上共夺得五枚奖牌，进一步印证了她是这一代，也可能是有史以来，最优秀的体操队员。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Biles helped the US women’s gymnastic team realize four consecutive individual all-around championships at the Olympic Games. She won five medals in total at this Olympic Games, further confirming that she is the best gymnast of her generation, and perhaps even in history.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Byers to help the United States team in the Olympic Games women's gymnastics to achieve four consecutive championships, she personally in the Olympic Games won five medals, further confirmed that she is this generation, also may be history, the best gymnasts.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers helped the U.S. team achieve a four-game winning streak in the women's individual all-around gymnastics at the Olympics, where she personally won five medals, further confirming that she is the best gymnast of her generation and probably of all time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>当看到自己总分的那一刻，拜尔斯忍不住流下泪水。她终于结束了这一漫长的旅程。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Once she saw her final score, Biles couldn’t hold back her tears. She has finally completed this long journey.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">When see oneself total score of that moment, Byers can't help shed tears. She finally ended the long journey.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers couldn't hold back her tears when she saw her total score. She finally ended the long journey.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯因此跻身像迈克尔-菲尔普斯 (Michael Phelps) 一样的“几十年一遇运动员”的行列，他们将各自领域的体育项目提升到新高度：</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Like Michael Phelps, Biles has made it to the list of “rare athletes” who have driven their respective athletic sport to greater heights.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Byers is thus among the "athletes of the past decades", like Michael Phelps, who have promoted their sports to new heights:</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers thus ranks among the "once-in-a-decade athletes" like Michael Phelps, who take sports to new heights in their respective fields:</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯最近三年一直称霸赛场，共夺得15枚世界锦标赛奖牌，其中包括十枚金牌。怀揣志向的她每日刻苦训练，以达到更高的精确度。1984年奥运冠军玛莉·卢·雷顿 (Mary Lou Retton) 称：“拜尔斯是我见过的最棒的体操运动员。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Biles has dominated the sport for the last 3 years, and have won a total of 15 World Championship medals, including 10 golds. Biles has set high goals for herself and trains hard everyday to reach higher levels of precision. Mary Lou Retton, Olympics champion of 1984, said: “Biles is the best gymnast I've ever seen.”</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Byers has been dominating the tournament for the last three years, winning 15 world championships, including 10 gold medals. She trained hard every day to achieve higher accuracy. "Byers is the best gymnast I've ever seen," said Mary Lou Retton, 1984 Olympic champion 玛莉·卢·雷顿. ”</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">"Byers is the best gymnast I've ever seen," said 1984 Olympic champion Mary Lou Retton, who has dominated the competition for the last three years, winning 15 World Championship medals, including 10 golds.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>在巴西还有最后一场比赛，但这场比赛与其说是拜尔斯与其他体操选手的竞争，不如说是她自己与巨大期望压力之间的较量。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">There is a final competition in Brazil, but instead of being a competition between Biles and other gymnasts, it should be regarded as a personal struggle of Biles against the stress generated by the massive expectations of her.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">There is still one last game in Brazil, but it is not so much a contest as Byers and other gymnasts, but a contest between herself and the pressure of great expectations.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">There's one final race in Brazil, but it's not so much Byers' rivalry with the other gymnasts as her own battle with the pressure of great expectations.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>如果拜尔斯没有满载金牌回到她位于德克萨斯州斯普林的家，大家一定会非常失望。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Everyone will be disappointed if Biles fail to return with a load of gold medals to her native home at Spring, Texas.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">If Byers does not have a full gold medal back at her home in Texas Springs, everyone will be very disappointed.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">If Byers hadn't returned to her home in Springs, Texas, loaded with gold medals, everyone would have been very disappointed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>来自美国的西蒙·拜尔斯（左）与莱斯曼相互拥抱，她们在8月份（周四）巴西里约热内卢举办的2016年夏季奥运会的艺术体操女子个人全能决赛上分别获得金牌与银牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Simone Biles (left) and Laurie from the United States hugging each other. They respectively won the gold and silver in the women's artistic individual all-around during the 2016 Summer Olympics at Rio, Brazil, during August (Thursday).</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">西蒙·拜尔斯 (left) and Lesman, from the United States, embraced each other in August (Thursday) at the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, for the women's individual all-around finals with gold and silver medals respectively.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Simon Byers (left), from the United States, hugged Lesman as they won gold and silver in the women's artistic gymnastics individual all-around final at the 2016 Summer Olympics in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, on Thursday, August.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯于周二斩获第一枚金牌，给即将退役的国家队教练卡罗利 (Martha Karolyi) 的欢送会奉上一份惊喜的厚礼。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Biles took her first gold medal on Tuesday, and will be delivering a surprising gift to Martha Karolyi, the coach of the national team who will be retiring soon.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Byers won the first gold medal in Tuesday, giving the retiring national coach Caroli (Martha Karolyi) a surprise farewell gift.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers won his first gold medal on Tuesday, a surprise gift to retiring national coach Martha Karolyi.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>尽管拜尔斯坚称自己在常年占据冠军宝座的过程中并没有计划未来，但事实不完全是这样的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Although Biles insisted that she has not planned for the future while dominating the world championships, the truth seems to suggest otherwise.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Although Bairstine says he has no plans for the future in the course of the perennial title, it is not entirely true.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Although Byers insists he has no plans for the future as he takes over the title all year round, it's not quite the case.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯自由体操当中的一段——包括她标志性的翻腾串连的那一段，配的是拉丁音乐，而这段音乐正是她在与里约奥运会场馆仅有一街之隔住所里常听的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">A segment of Biles’ floor exercise - including her marquee tumbling pass - was accompanied by Latin music, and this piece of music was precisely that which she listened to all the time at her lodging just a street away from the Arena Olímpica do Rio.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The part of Byers's floor exercise--including her iconic, Rolling series, was accompanied by Latin music, which she heard in the middle of a street from the Rio Olympic Stadium.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">A section of Byers' floor exercise - including her iconic somersault - is accompanied by Latin music, which she often listens to in her residence just across the street from Rio's Olympic venues.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>这绝非巧合。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">This is not a coincidence.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">This is no coincidence.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">This is no coincidence.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>这个在婴儿时期被祖父母收养，并在一次体育馆实地考察旅行时被教练艾米·伯尔曼 (Aimee Boorman) 的母亲发现的女孩现已成长为中坚力量。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">She was raised by her grandparents when she was a young child, and was eventually found to have great potential by the motherly coach Aimee Boorman who was conducting a inspection tour of the gym.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The girl who was adopted by his grandparents during his infancy and was found by the mother of Coach 艾米·伯尔曼 (Aimee Boorman) during a field trip to the stadium has now grown into a backbone.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">The girl, who was adopted as a baby by her grandparents and discovered by coach Amy Boorman's mother during a field trip to the gym, has now grown into a backbone.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>自从2013年夏季以来，拜尔斯就没有在全能比赛中失手过，只要想赢，她就一定会赢。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Since the summer of 2013, Biles had never failed in the all-around competition. As long as she wanted to, she would win.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Since the summer of 2013, Byers has not lost in the all-around game, if want to win, she will definitely win.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers hasn't lost an all-around game since the summer of 2013, and she's sure to win if she wants to.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>穆斯塔芬娜两次旋转后的稍稍领先只是一个幻觉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">It seems that Mustafina slight lead after her two spins is only illusory.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Mustafina a slight lead after two rotations is just an illusion.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Mustafina's slight lead after two turnovers was an illusion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>平衡木与自由体操两个项目的卫冕世界冠军拜尔斯埋伏以待。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Simone Biles, reigning world champion of the balance beam and floor exercise, lay in wait.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">The balance beam and floor exercise two-item defending world champion Byers ambush to wait.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers, the reigning world champion in both the balance beam and floor exercise events, is waiting in the wings.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>她的平衡木得分15.433，自由体操得分15.933。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">She scored 15.433 on the balance beam, and 15.933 in the floor exercise.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Her balance beam scored 15.433 and the floor was 15.933.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">She scored 15.433 on the balance beam and 15.933 in the floor exercise.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>在等待最后比分出来的时候，莱斯曼轻轻抱了一下拜尔斯。当拜尔斯得知自己取得梦寐以求的成绩后，顿时留下了眼泪。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">After waiting for the final score to be provided, Raisman gave Biles a gentle hug. Biles cried when she knew she had achieved the score that she had dreamed for.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">While waiting for the final score to come out, Lesman gently hugged Byers. When Byers learned of his dream to achieve the results, immediately left tears.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">While waiting for the final score, Leseman gave Byers a gentle hug. Byers burst into tears when he learned that he had achieved his dream.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>莱斯曼的表现有点像是对四年前的复仇，当时她并列第三，但在决胜局中输给了穆斯塔芬娜。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Raisman’s performance seems to be an act of vengeance for four years ago when she lost to Mustafina, who was then ranked third, during the finals game.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Lesman's performance was a bit like revenge for four years ago, when she tied third, but lost to Mustafina in the winning innings.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Leslman's performance was a bit like revenge for four years ago, when she tied for third but lost to Mustafina in the decider.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>但这一次，这位被美国人戏称为“奶奶”的22岁队长遥遥领先。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">But this time, the 22-year old captain who has been laughably called “grandmother” by the Americans have gained a massive lead.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">But this time, the 22-year-old captain, nicknamed "Granny" by the Americans, is far ahead.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">But this time, the 22-year-old captain, nicknamed "Grandma" by the Americans, was well ahead.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>她在自由体操结束后向人群飞吻，宣告回归，但这样的回归以前有时却看起来存在疑问。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">After the floor event, she blew a kiss to the crowd to announce her return. However, such a return look rather doubtful sometimes in the past.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">She blew kisses at the end of the floor and declared her return, but the return sometimes seemed questionable.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">She blew kisses to the crowd after the floor exercise to announce her return, but such a return has sometimes seemed questionable before.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="143_cbsnews.146232_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯才19岁。从本周早些时候起，其消息就在推特上病毒般传播开来。就拜尔斯而言，其人生已被赋予了全新意义。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.ht">Biles is just 19 years old. Since earlier this week, the news has gone viral on Twitter. For Biles, her life has taken on a whole new meaning.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.gg">Byers is only 19 years old. From earlier this week, the news spread viral on Twitter. In the case of Byron, his life has been endowed with new meaning.</translation>
    <translation system="143_cbsnews.146232_en.c6">Byers, who is just 19 years old, has been viral on Twitter since earlier this week. For his part, his life has taken on a whole new meaning.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
