<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>CBC 奥运会解说员就中国游泳运动员“像猪一样慢”的评论道歉</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">The Olympic commentator of CBS apologized for the expression that Chinese swimmers are "died like a pig".</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">CBC Olympic commentator apologizes for Chinese swimmer's "slow like a pig" comment</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">CBC Olympics commentator apologises for Chinese swimmer's' slow as a pig 'comment</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>周三，拜伦·麦克唐纳 (Byron MacDonald) 对14岁小将艾衍含获得女子4x200米自由泳接力赛第四名的评论惹怒了收看加拿大广播公司 (CBC) 奥运现场直播的观众</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">On Wednesday, a comment made by Byron MacDonald on 14-year-old Ai Yanhan, whose team placed 4th in the women’s 4x200 meter freestyle relay angered viewers who were watching the live broadcast of the Olympic Games on Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (CBC)</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Wednesday, 拜伦·麦克唐纳 (Byron MacDonald) to the 14-year-old teenager Ai Ying with the fourth place of the female 4x200 rice freestyle relay race angered by watching the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (CBC) Olympic live broadcast audience</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Byron MacDonald's comments Wednesday about 14-year-old Ai Yanhan's fourth-place finish in the women's 4x200m freestyle relay infuriated viewers who watched the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation's live Olympic broadcast</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>加拿大广播公司 CBC 的一名解说员说14岁的中国游泳小将在比赛中“出发时游得比臭气散发还快”，最后“却像猪一样慢”，之后 CBC 被迫对此道歉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">A commentator from the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (CBC) described a 14-year old Chinese swimmer as having “went out like stink” and finally “died like a pig”. CBC was later forced to apologize for this.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">An announcer at the Canadian Broadcasting company CBC said the 14-year-old Chinese swimmer was forced to apologize after the "start of a race that was faster than the stench" and ended "as slow as a pig".</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">CBC was forced to apologise after a commentator for the Canadian broadcaster CBC said the 14-year-old Chinese swimmer "started off faster than the stench" and ended up "as slow as a pig."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>解说员拜伦·麦克唐纳在女子4x200米自由泳接力赛决赛结束时，发表了一些自己的看法，当时他以为自己的麦克风已经关掉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">The commentator Byron MacDonald expressed his opinions after the completion of the 4 x 200 women’s freestyle relay, and said that he thought his microphone has already been switched off.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Narrator 拜伦·麦克唐纳 at the end of the women's 4x200 freestyle relay finals when he thought his microphone had been turned off.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Commentator Byron McDonnell made some comments at the end of the women's 4x200m freestyle relay final when he thought his microphone had been turned off.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>观众听到 CBC 解说员团队这位戴“有色眼镜”评论选手的拜伦说：“那名14岁的中国小姑娘犯了个愚蠢的错误。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Viewers heard Byron, a member of the CBC team of commentators, who wore “tinted glasses” comment, “The little 14-year-old from China dropped the ball, baby.”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">"The 14-year-old Chinese girl made a stupid mistake," said Byron, who was told by the CBC commentator team, who wore the "tinted glasses" commentary. ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">"The 14-year-old Chinese girl made a stupid mistake," said Byron, who was a "tinted" commentator on the CBC's team of commentators.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>由于太激动了，开始出发时游得比臭气散发还快，但后来像头猪一样慢。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Too excited, went out like stink and died like a pig.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Being so excited, I began to travel faster than the stench, but later I was as slow as a pig.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Being so excited, he started to swim faster than the stench, but then he was as slow as a pig.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>还真是多亏她了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">She really did a lot.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Thanks to her.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Thanks to her.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>现年14岁的中国游泳选手艾衍含游的是第二棒，用时1分57秒79——落后加拿大的泰勒·拉克 (Taylor Ruck) 1.61秒，继而使得加拿大队缩小了与中国的差距。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Ai Yanhan, the 14-year old Chinese swimmer, took the second leg of the relay which she completed in 1 minute 57.59 seconds, a full 1.61 seconds behind the Canadian swimmer Taylor Ruck, allowing the Canadian team to shorten their gap with the Chinese team.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">The 14-year-old Chinese swimmer, Ai Ying, has a second-best tour, with 1 minutes and 57 seconds 79--泰勒·拉克 (Taylor ruck) 1.61 seconds behind Canada, which narrows the gap with China.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Ai Yan, a 14-year-old Chinese swimmer, finished second in 1: 57.79 - 1.61 seconds behind Canada's Taylor Ruck, which helped the Canadian team close the gap with China.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>整个加拿大的观众都被这位解说员的语气及措辞给惊到了，之后他们很快在网络上做出了反应</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Every audience in Canada was shocked by the tone and language used by the commentator. They quickly responded to this on the Internet.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">The entire Canadian audience was surprised by the narrator's tone and wording, and they quickly reacted on the internet.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Viewers across Canada were taken aback by the narrator's tone and phrasing, and they were quick to react online</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>Emmett Macfarlane 推送道：“那位 CBC解说员说中国14岁的游泳运动员‘慢得像猪一样’？？？”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Emmett Macfarlane twitted: “Did the CBC commentator say that the 14-year old Chinese swimmer was as slow as a pig?”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Emmett Macfarlane, the CBC commentator, said that China's 14-year-old swimmer was ' slow as a pig '??? ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Emmett Macfarlane tweeted: "The CBC commentator said China's 14-year-old swimmer was' slow as a pig '??"</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>这个白痴没有意识到是在直播。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">This idiot was not aware that he was live on air.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">The idiot didn't realize it was on the live.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">The idiot didn't realise it was live.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>参加女子4x200米自由泳接力赛决赛的中国小将艾衍含被这样描述：“那名14岁的中国小姑娘犯了个愚蠢的错误。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Ai Yanhan, the Chinese swimmer participating in the 4x200 m freestyle relay finals, was described: “That 14-year old Chinese girl made a foolish mistake.”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">"The 14-year-old Chinese girl made a stupid mistake," the Chinese teenager Ai Ying, who participated in the final of the women's 4x200 freestyle relay race, included this description. ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">"That 14-year-old Chinese girl made a stupid mistake," said Ai Yanhan, a Chinese teenager who competed in the final of the women's 4x200m freestyle relay.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>推特上对拜伦·麦克唐纳的批评迅速在推特上铺天盖地地袭来，很多人要求其退出解说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">The criticisms leveled at Byron MacDonald quickly spread throughout Twitter. Many people asked Byron to resign from his job as commentator.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Twitter's criticisms of 拜伦·麦克唐纳 have been sweeping over Twitter, and many have asked them to withdraw from the commentary.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Twitter's criticism of Byron McDonnell quickly spread across the tweets, with many calling for it to drop out of the commentary.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>当推特用户听说拜伦·麦克唐纳对此反应迟钝时，他们并未就此打住。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Twitter users did not stop there when they heard that Byron MacDonald has responded slowly over this incident.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">When Twitter users heard that 拜伦·麦克唐纳 was unresponsive, they didn't stop there.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">When Twitter users heard that Byron McDonnell was slow to respond, they didn't stop there.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>另一位推特用户 Sarah Paradis 写道：“哇#拜伦·麦克唐纳。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Sarah Paradis, another Twitter user, wrote: “Wow! #Byron MacDonald.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Another Twitter user, Sarah Paradis, wrote, "Wow, 拜伦·麦克唐纳."</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Another Twitter user, Sarah Paradis, wrote: 'Wow # Byron MacDonald.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>你代表的是 CBC 和加拿大，你的言行使得我们大家听起来都像一群种族主义者。#真令人讨厌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">You represent CBC and Canada. Your words and actions make us all sound like racists.# How disgusting.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">You represent CBC and Canada, and your words and deeds make us all sound like a bunch of racist people. #真令人讨厌.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">You're representing CBC and Canada, and your words and actions make us all sound like a bunch of racists. # That's disgusting.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>不久后，CBC 广播主持人 Scott Russel 就拜伦的言论在直播中道歉，他说：“我们对直播游泳选手表现的评论而道歉。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Not long after, CBC broadcaster Scott Russel apologized for Byron’s words, saying: “We apologize for the comments made about the swimmers during the live stream.”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Soon after, CBC radio host Scott Russell apologized for his comments in the broadcast, saying: "We apologize for the commentary on the performance of the live swimmer." ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Shortly afterwards, CBC radio host Scott Russel apologised on air for Byron's comments, saying: "We apologise for the comments we made about the performance of the live swimmers."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>“我们很抱歉出现这种不合时宜的措辞。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">“We are very sorry for the inappropriate and unfortunate choice of words.”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">"We are sorry for the untimely wording." ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">"We're sorry for the inappropriate language."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>CBC 向那些对该言论有所回应的推特用户道歉90多次</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">CBS has been apologized 90 times to the twitter users replied to the post.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">CBC apologizes to Twitter users who responded to the comments more than 90 times</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">CBC apologized more than 90 times to those Twitter users who responded to the comment</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>另一名解说员 Scott Russel 也代表拜伦致歉</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Another commentator, Scott Russel, also apologized on behalf of Byron</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Another commentator, Scott Russell, also apologized to Byron.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Another commentator, Scott Russel, also apologized on behalf of Byron</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>CBC 之后将他们的道歉复制粘贴给了其他90多位抗议拜伦解说的推特用户</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">CBC later copied and duplicated its apology to over 90 Twitter users who protested Byron’s explanations.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">CBC then copied their apology to the other 90 Twitter users who protested the Byron commentary.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">CBC later copied and pasted their apology to more than 90 other Twitter users protesting Byron's comments</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>该频道也很快做出了道歉并发布了声明。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">This channel quickly apologized and issued an official statement.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">The channel also quickly apologized and issued a statement.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">The channel also quickly apologized and released a statement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>我们对说出这样的话并将之直播出去感到无比抱歉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">We are extremely sorry for what was said and that it was broadcast live.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">We are very sorry to say this and live out the broadcast.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">We are extremely sorry to say this and broadcast it live.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>昨晚，我们迅速采取行动，向收看我们直播的观众以及在社交媒体上关注我们的观众道歉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">We took action swiftly last night, and apologized to viewers who were watching our live broadcast as well as those who were following us on social media.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">Last night, we took swift action to apologize to viewers who watched our live audience and to our audience in social media.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">Last night, we moved quickly to apologise to viewers who tuned in to watch us live, as well as those who followed us on social media.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>需要说明的是，拜伦的解说针对的是游泳选手的表现，但是并不是针对她个人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">It should be noted that Byron’s commentary was aimed at the performance of the swimmer rather than swimmer herself.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">It should be explained that Byron's explanation is for swimmers, but not for her personally.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">It should be noted that Byron's commentary was aimed at the swimmer's performance, but not at her personally.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>就是说，措辞确实不恰当，拜伦对此深感抱歉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">So the choice of words was inappropriate. Byron felt deeply sorry about this.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">That is to say, the wording is indeed inappropriate, and Byron is deeply sorry.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">That said, the wording was really inappropriate, and Byron was deeply sorry about that.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>周四下午，麦克唐纳在直播中道歉，他说自己的言语没有半点人身攻击的意思，并企图借此为自己的言论开脱。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">Mike Donald tried to excuse himself by apologizing in the live show on the Thursday afternoon, saying he had zero intention of personal attack.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">In the afternoon of Thursday, MacDonald apologized on the live, saying that his words did not mean any personal attack, and tried to justify his remarks.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">On Thursday afternoon, McDonnell apologized during a live broadcast, saying there was nothing personal about his words and attempting to use them to excuse his remarks.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>“我想花点时间为自己昨天晚上在女子接力赛结束后发表的言论道歉，”他在 CBC 奥运转播上如是说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">“I wanted to spend some time to apologize for what I said after the end of the women's relay,” he said during the CBC Olympics broadcast.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">"I'd like to take some time to apologize for what I said last night in the end of the women's relay race," he says on the CBC Olympic relay.</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">"I want to take a moment to apologize for the comments I made last night after the women's relay race," he said on the CBC Olympics broadcast.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>“我只是评论游泳选手的表现，而不是针对其个人。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">“I was merely commenting on the performance of swimmer rather than the particular individual.”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">"I'm just commenting on swimmers ' performance, not personal." ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">"I'm just commenting on the swimmer's performance, not the individual."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.sl">
    <source>“当然，我没有不尊重的意思，我很抱歉。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.ht">“Sorry. I mean no disrespect. I’m sorry.”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.gg">"Of course, I have no disrespect for the meaning, I am sorry. ”</translation>
    <translation system="001_dailymail.co.uk.170717_en.c6">"Of course, I didn't mean to be disrespectful, I'm sorry."</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
