<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>Primark 顾客对一名厚颜无耻地在店中央试穿内裤的女子表示愤怒</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">Primark customer outraged at woman who had the cheek to try on underwear in the middle of the store</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">Primark customer expressed anger at a woman who brazenly tried to wear underwear in the center of the shop</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">Primark customers have expressed outrage at a woman who brazenly tried on her underwear in the middle of the store</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>一名女子在一间 Primark 的店中央当场脱衣试内裤，店内顾客不知该朝哪里看。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">A woman stripped down to try on undergarments in the middle of a store at Primark. Shocked customers don’t know where to look.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">A woman in a Primark shop in the central spot strip test underwear, the shop customers do not know where to look.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">A woman takes off her underwear on the spot in the middle of a Primark store where customers don't know where to look.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>更糟糕的是，她还打量自己穿上后看起来如何，然后将内裤脱下又放回货架。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">The worst part is that she even checked how she looked after wearing the underwear before taking them off and putting them back on the shelves.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">To make things worse, she looked at how she looked when she put it on, then took her panties off and put it back on the shelf.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">To make matters worse, she also looked at how she looked when she put it on, before taking her underwear off and putting it back on the shelf.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>她继续浏览货架，并最终在位于 Folkestone 的 Bouverie Place 购物中心的这家店内试穿了四条内裤。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">She continued to peruse the shelves, and finally tried on four pieces of underwear in this store at Bouverie Place Shopping Mall in Folkestone.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">She went on to browse the shelves and eventually tried on four underpants in the store at the Bouverie Place Mall in Folkestone.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">She continued to browse the shelves and eventually tried on four pairs of underwear inside the store at the Bouverie Place shopping centre in Folkestone.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>这名女子在位于 Folkestone 的 Bouverie Place 购物中心的这家 Primark 店内不断试穿内裤，然后又放回货架</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">The woman kept trying panties one after another without buying in the Primark shop at the Bouverie Place Shopping Center, Folkestone.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">The woman tried to wear underwear in the Primark store at the Bouverie Place Mall in Folkestone and put it back on the shelves.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">The woman kept trying on her underwear inside the Primark store at the Bouverie Place shopping centre in Folkestone before putting it back on the shelves</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>当时也在店内的 Jenny Davidson（两个孩子的母亲）说，试穿内衣后，这名神秘女子“再次穿好衣服，然后就走出了商店，什么都没买。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">Jenny Davidson (a mother of two) was also in the shop at the time. After trying on the underwear, this mysterious woman “put on her clothes again and left the shop. She didn’t buy anything.”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">Jenny Davidson (two children's mother), who was also in the store, said that after trying on her underwear, the mysterious woman "dressed again and went out of the store and bought nothing." ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">Jenny Davidson, a mother of two who was also at the store at the time, said that after trying on her underwear, the mystery woman "got dressed again and walked out of the store without buying anything."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>她说：“大家都不敢相信自己所看到的。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">She said: “Nobody believed what they just saw.”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">"No one can believe what they have seen," she said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">"People couldn't believe what they were seeing," she said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>她就站在店中央，从货架上取下一条内裤，脱掉自己的紧身裤和内裤，然后就这样穿上了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">She stood in the middle of the store, took the next underwear from the store shelf, took off her own tights and underwear, and then tried on the store underwear.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">She was standing in the middle of the store, taking a pair of panties off the shelves, stripping off her tights and panties, and then putting them on.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">She just stood in the middle of the store, took a pair of panties off the shelf, took off her tights and underwear, and put them on.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>“她没有试着去找隐蔽的地方去试穿——她只是站在那里，真是厚颜无耻。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">“She did not attempt to find a secluded area to try on her clothes - she just stood there; how shameless!”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">"She didn't try to find a hidden place to try on--she just stood there, really cheeky. ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">"She didn't try to find a secluded place to try it on - she just stood there, it was cheeky."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>“当她把内裤再次脱下来的时候，所有人都被惊得目瞪口呆。显然，她还是不满意，因为她把内裤放回了货架。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">"Everyone was shocked when she took off the panties again. Obviously she was not happy with it because she put it back on the shelve.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">When she took off her panties again, everyone was stunned. Apparently, she was still dissatisfied because she put her panties back on the shelves. ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">"Everyone was stunned when she took her underwear off again. Obviously, she was still not satisfied because she put it back on the shelf."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>之后，她又像这样试了三条，最后发现都不是自己喜欢的，然后再次穿好衣服，走出店去。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">She then repeated this for three more pieces of underwear and found that none of them were to her liking. She then wore her clothes and left the store.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">After that, she tried three like this, and finally found out that she didn't like it, then dressed again and went out of the shop.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">After that, she tried three more like this, only to find that none of them were her favorite, then dressed again and walked out of the store.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>“她看似并不在意有人在看她——或者也没有想过谁会最终买走她试穿过的内裤。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">“She didn’t seem to mind if someone was watching her - nor think about the person who might eventually buy the piece of underwear that she had tried on.”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">"She doesn't seem to care that someone is looking at her--or that she's not going to end up buying the panties she's trying to get through," she said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">"She didn't seem to care that someone was looking at her - or wondering who would end up buying the underwear she was trying on."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>居住在 Kent 镇的 Davidson 女士（33岁）说：“一想到有人会买走其他人穿过且没被清洗过的内裤，就觉得恶心。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">Ms Davidson (33 years old), a resident of Kent, said, “The thought of someone buying another person’s worn but unwashed underwear makes me sick.”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">Ms. Davidson, who lives in Kent town (33 years old), said: "It's disgusting to think that someone will buy underwear that other people have walked through and have not been washed." ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">Ms Davidson (33), who lives in Kent, said: "It's disgusting to think that someone will buy someone else's underwear that hasn't been cleaned."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>这件事发生在周二下午。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">This incident occurred in a Tuesday afternoon.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">It happened in the afternoon of Tuesday.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">The incident happened on Tuesday afternoon.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>Davidson 女士补充说：“待她离开后，店员显然要对这些内裤做下架处理，幸好如此。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">Davidson added: “When she left, the store assistant seems to be taking the underwear off the shelf for subsequent handling, and it was fortunate that it happened.”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">Ms. Davidson added: "After she left, it was obvious that the clerk had to deal with the underwear." ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">Ms Davidson added: "When she left, the shop assistant obviously had to take the underwear off the shelves, but fortunately that was the case."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>“我讨厌买回家一条新内裤，却发现有另一个女人试穿过并且没有被清洗过。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">“I hate it when I buy a supposedly new underwear home and found that another woman has worn it and did not wash it.”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">"I hate to buy a new pair of underwear and find another woman trying to cross it and not being washed." ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">"I hate to go home and buy a new pair of underwear, only to find another woman trying them on and not being cleaned."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>Primark 的一位发言人说：“Primark 已经知道了8月9日（周二）发生在我们 Folkestone 店内的事情。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">Primark spokesperson said: “Primark is aware of the incident that occurred at the Folkestone storefront on August 9 (Tuesday).”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">"Primark already knows what happened in our Folkestone shop August 9 (Tuesday)," said a spokesman for Primark. ”</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">A spokesman for Primark said: "Primark has been made aware of what happened inside our Folkestone store on Tuesday, August 9."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.sl">
    <source>所有有问题商品均已下架。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.ht">All contaminated products have been removed from the shelves.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.gg">All the problematic goods have been under the shelves.</translation>
    <translation system="086_dailymail.co.uk.170730_en.c6">All the items in question have been removed from the shelves.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
