<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>补齐公共体育设施短板</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">Making up for shortcomings of public sporting facilities</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">Short board for public sports facilities</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">Completing short boards of public sports facilities</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>黑乎乎的煤场仓库，变成“绿草如茵”的足球场；红砖尖顶的厂房，变成现代化的运动馆。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">The dark and sooty warehouse of the coal mine has become a “verdant’ soccer field, and the red brick factory with the pointed top, a modern gymnasium.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">Black Coal yard warehouse, turned into "Green grass" football field, red brick spire of the plant, into a modern sports hall.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">Black coal warehouse, into a "green grass" football field; red brick spire of the plant, into a modern sports hall.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>在全民健身日，杭州望江门外的南落马营体育文化公园，揭开了神秘的面纱。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">The mysterious veil over the Nanluomaying Sports Cultural Park outside Wangjiang Gate of Hangzhou was lifted on National Fitness Day.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">In the National Fitness Day, Hangzhou Wangjiang outside the South Lok Ma Ying Sports Cultural Park, unveiled a mysterious veil.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">On National Fitness Day, the South Losing Horse Camp Sports and Cultural Park outside the Wangjiang River in Hangzhou, unveiled the mystery.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>这里曾是煤场，十多年前关闭后一直闲置，留下了大量的违法建筑和生活垃圾。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">This used to be a coal mine, and was left idle after it closed down more than 10 years ago. What remained were numerous illegal buildings and domestic waste.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">This used to be a coal field, more than 10 years ago closed after the idle, leaving a large number of illegal construction and living garbage.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">It used to be a coal mine and has been idle since it closed more than a decade ago, leaving behind a large amount of illegal construction and domestic waste.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>这里经过整治后，成了体育文化公园，并将于11月正式对外开放，向市民免费提供运动场所，也无疑为全民体育开辟了全新的沃土。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">Renovations created the athletic cultural park that will be  formally opened to public visitors in November, providing fellow citizens with a place to exercise. This has undoubtedly heralded a new place for total public participation in athleticism.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">Here after the renovation, became a sports cultural park, and will be open to the public in November, to provide free sports venues, and no doubt for the national sports opened up a new fertile ground.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">After its renovation, it has become a sports and cultural park and will officially open to the public in November, providing sports venues free of charge to the public and undoubtedly opening up a whole new fertile ground for sport for all.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>这不禁让人想起杭州陈经纶体校，这座中国泳坛的“黄埔军校”游出了多名世界冠军。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">One could not help but recall Hangzhou Chen Jinglun Sport School. This “Huangpu Military Academy” of the Chinese swimming world has produced many world champions.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">This makes people think of Hangzhou Chen Economy Sports School, the Chinese swimming "Huangpu Military Academy" swam out of many world champions.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">This is reminiscent of Hangzhou Chenjinglun Sports School, the "Huangpu Military Academy" in Chinese swimming, which has won several world championships.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>泳坛名将源源不断地产生，生动地诠释了竞技体育与全民体育之间的关系——丰厚的群众基础为选拔专业选手提供了良好的条件。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">New famous athletes are constantly generated in the swimming pool, providing a lively demonstration of the relationship between the competitive sport and public athleticism. A large base of participating public provide an excellent condition for selecting professional athletes.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">The swimming is constantly produced, vivid interpretation of the relationship between competitive sports and national sports-rich mass base for the selection of professional players to provide a good condition.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">Swimming stars are constantly emerging, vividly illustrating the relationship between competitive sports and national sports - the rich mass base provides good conditions for the selection of professional athletes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>竞技体育的水平与全民体育的基础密切相关，竞技体育在一定意义上取决于全民体育，而全民体育又取决于场地条件。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">The level of competitive sports is closely linked to public athleticism. Competitive sports, to some degree, is determined by public athleticism, and public athleticism is itself determined by the quality of sporting venues.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">The level of competitive sports is closely related to the foundation of the national sports, and the Athletics sports depends on the national sports in a certain sense, and the national sports depends on the site conditions.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">The level of competitive sports is closely related to the foundation of national sports. Competitive sports in a certain sense depends on national sports, which in turn depends on the conditions of the venue.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>据报道，截至2015年，我国的人均体育场地面积虽然已是新中国成立时的150倍，但仍远远落后于体育强国。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">According to reports, although the average sports venue area per capita in our country as of the end of 2015 was 150 times of that at the founding of the New China, the current figure is still way behind leading athletic nations.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">It is reported that as of 2015, China's per capita stadium area, although it is 150 times times the establishment of new China, but still far behind the sports power.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">It is reported that as of 2015, China's per capita sports ground area, although it has been 150 times that of the founding of New China, still lags far behind the sports powerhouse.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>今年6月，国务院印发了《全民健身计划（2016-2020年）》，将发展群众体育作为重点内容。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">In June this year, the State Council of the People's Republic of China released the National Fitness Program (2016-2020) to establish the development of public athleticism as a priority.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">In June this year, the State Council issued the National Fitness Program (2016-2020), the development of mass sports as a key content.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">In June this year, the State Council issued the National Fitness Plan (2016-2020), with the development of mass sports as a key element.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>为了补齐这块短板，一方面，相关部门在进行城市规划时要充分考虑到体育场馆的布局。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">To compensate for this defect, relevant departments must fully consider the layout of the sports hall during urban planning.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">In order to complete this short board, on the one hand, the relevant departments in the city planning should take fully into account the stadium layout.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">In order to make up for this shortcoming, on the one hand, the relevant departments in urban planning to take full account of the layout of the sports venues.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>另一方面，已建成的公共体育场馆，包括学校等单位里的体育场馆，应尽量扩大开放范围，尽可能地提高使用效率。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">On the one hand, the public sports stadium has been built, including sports stadiums in entities such as schools. The scope should be expanded to the fullest extent possible, and utilization rates raised as much as possible.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">On the other hand, the established public sports venues, including schools and other units in the sports venues, should maximize the open scope, as far as possible to improve the efficiency of use.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">On the other hand, completed public sports stadiums, including those in institutions such as schools, should be as open as possible and used as efficiently as possible.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.sl">
    <source>目前正如火如荼进行着的里约奥运会，激发着人们的运动热情，也唤醒了大家的参与意识。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.ht">The Rio Olympics is currently all the rage, and has inspired public passion for sports as well as awakened the people’s desire to participate in athletic activities.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.gg">Currently in full swing of the Rio Olympic Games, inspire people's sports enthusiasm, but also awakened everyone's sense of participation.</translation>
    <translation system="037_peopledaily0812.zj.c187006-28823926_zh.c6">The Rio Olympics, now in full swing, have inspired enthusiasm for the sport and awakened a sense of participation.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
