<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>唐纳德·特朗普竞选团队因工作人员拔枪而被起诉</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Donald Trump’s election campaign official sued for gun threat</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Donald Trump's campaign team is being sued for pulling guns</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Donald Trump campaign charged over staff member's draw</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>纽约：特朗普的竞选团队因其北加利福尼亚洲负责人于2月份驾驶一辆吉普车时拔枪指向一名工作人员后不作为而被起诉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">New York: The head of the Northern California Asia section of Trump’s presidential campaign staff was charged in February for driving a jeep and pulling a gun at another personnel as well as subsequent inaction</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">NEW York: Trump's campaign team was charged with pulling a gun at a worker when he was driving a Jeep in February.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">New York: Trump's campaign has been sued for inaction after its Northern California chief pulled a gun and pointed it at a staff member while driving a jeep in February.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>该州竞选团队的前软件培训师文森特·博迪尼于周三在位于夏洛特的州法庭上描述了该事件。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Former software instructor Vincent Bordini of the election team of the state described the incident at the State Court in Charlotte on Wednesday.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">文森特·博迪尼, a former software trainer for the state's campaign team, described the incident in a state court in Charlotte in Wednesday.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Vincent Bodini, a former software trainer for the state's campaign, described the incident in a state court in Charlotte on Wednesday.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>博迪尼表示，之前他希望这件事情能够在内部解决，但在等待了数月后他意识到“这不可能发生”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Bodini said that he had hoped that this would be resolved internally, but a few months later, he realized that it “was not going to happen”.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Mr. Bodini said he had hoped the affair would be resolved internally, but he realised "it is not likely to happen" after months of waiting.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Mr Bodini said he had previously hoped the matter would be resolved internally, but after months of waiting he realised "this can't happen."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>根据博迪尼的描述，这位名叫厄尔·菲利普的负责人“拔出了一把手枪，将右手食指放在板机上，并且将枪口对准文森特的膝盖骨。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Descriptions by Bordini, the person in charge named Earl Phillip “pulled out a pistol and placed the index finger of his right hand on the trigger, and pointed the gun at Vincent’s knee cap.”</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">According to Bodini's description, the person named 厄尔·菲利普 "pulled out a pistol, put his right forefinger on the board and pointed the muzzle at Vincent's knee bone." ”</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">According to Bodini, the man in charge, Earl Phillips, "pulled out a pistol, placed his right index finger on the board, and pointed the gun at Vincent's kneecap."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>在向当地和地区竞选团队领导层投诉后，博迪尼从卷宗中了解到至少还有四个人经历了相同的事情。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">After complaining to the leaders of parties running for the local and district elections, Bordini learned from the letter of complaint that at least 4 other individuals have experienced the same.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">After complaining to the local and regional campaign leadership, Bodini learned from the file that at least four other people had gone through the same thing.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">After complaining to the local and regional campaign leadership, Bodini learned from the dossier that at least four other people had gone through the same thing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>博迪尼在投诉中表示：“没有开枪不代表不会造成伤害。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Bordini expressed in the complaint: “No shots fired does not mean that no injury is caused.”</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Bodini said in a complaint: "No shooting does not mean that it will not cause harm." ”</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">"Failure to shoot does not mean no harm will be done," Mr Bodini said in the complaint.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>就在该案件发生两天前，这位共和党总统候选人在北卡罗来纳州告诉群众，如果他的对手希拉里·克林顿当选并且挑选她所喜爱的法官，那么“支持第二修正案的人”，也就是枪支持有人和枪支爱好者可能会采取行动，这一发言引发了众怒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Two days before the case occurred, this Republican presidential nominee told the crowd at North Carolina that if his rival Hillary Clinton were to be elected and get to pick her favorite judge, then “the people who support the Second Amendment”, that is, people who own guns and gun lowers may take action. This statement led to public outrage.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Just two days before the case, the Republican presidential candidate told the crowd in North Carolina State that if his rival Hillary Clinton was elected and chose her favourite judge, the "people who support the Second Amendment", the gun holder and gun enthusiast, might act, sparking outrage.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">The case comes just two days after the Republican presidential nominee sparked outrage in North Carolina when he told a crowd that "people who support the Second Amendment," gun owners and gun enthusiasts, could take action if his opponent Hillary Clinton was elected and picked her favorite judge.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>特朗普的竞选团队表示，媒体对他的话断章取义，他并没有提倡暴力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Trump’s election team said that the media has taken his comments out of context. He did not advocate violence.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Trump's campaign team said the media had taken the word out of his words and he did not advocate violence.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Trump's campaign said the media had taken his words out of context and that he was not advocating violence.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>博迪尼在投诉中要求竞选团队为自己的疏于监督进行赔偿，同时也要求菲利普为自己的袭击、殴打和精神伤害进行赔偿。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">In the complaint, Bordini demanded the campaign staff to provide compensation for their lack of supervision, and also demanded Phillip to compensate his injuries caused by his attack, battery, and psychological attack.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">In a complaint, Bodini asked the campaign team to compensate for his oversight, while also demanding that Philip compensate for his attacks, beatings and mental injuries.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">In his complaint, Bodini demanded compensation from the campaign for his neglect of supervision, as well as from Phillip for his assault, assault and mental injury.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>特朗普发言人霍普·希克斯未立即对这一消息予以回应。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Trump’s spokesperson Hope Hicks did not give an immediate response to this news.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Trump spokesman 霍普·希克斯 did not immediately respond to the news.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Trump spokeswoman Hope Hicks did not immediately respond to the news.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>无法联系到菲利普。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Philip cannot be contacted.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Could not reach Philip.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Philip could not be reached for comment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>据夏洛特当地的一家新闻社WCCB报道，菲利普于近期离开了竞选团队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">WCCB, a local news company at Charlotte, reported that Phillipp has recently left the campaign staff.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Philip recently left the campaign team, according to WCCB, a local news agency in Charlotte.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Phillip recently left the campaign, according to a local news agency WCCB in Charlotte.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>他的咨询公司 Innovative Consulting Services 未对来电立刻进行回复。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">His consultation company, Innovative Consulting Services, did not immediately respond to incoming calls.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">His consulting firm Innovative Consulting Services did not immediately respond to calls.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">His consulting firm, Innovative Consulting Services, did not immediately respond to the call.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>共和党总统候选人唐纳德·特朗普的竞选团队饱受争议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">Republican Party presidential candidate Donald Trump’s campaign staff has been hit by a series of controversies.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump's campaign team is under controversy.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump's campaign has been dogged by controversy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.sl">
    <source>本案双方为博迪尼与特朗普总统竞选公司，16-CS-14300，梅克伦堡县 （夏洛特）高等法院普通庭。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.ht">The case refers to Bordini v. Donald J. Trump For President Inc., 16-CS-14300, General Court of Justice, Superior Court Division County of Mecklenburg (Charlotte).</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.gg">Both sides of the case are Bodini and Trump presidential campaign company, 16-cs-14300, Mecklenburg County (Charlotte) High Court general Chamber.</translation>
    <translation system="105_smh.com.au.191331_en.c6">The parties in this case are Bodini and Trump Presidential Campaign, 16-CS-14300, General Division of the High Court of Mecklenburg County (Charlotte).</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
