<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>英国队在七人制橄榄球赛中获得银牌，斐济队夺得金牌</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">The UK team won a silver medal while the Fijian team won the gold medal in rugby sevens.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The British won the silver medal in the seven-man rugby game and Fiji won the gold medal.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Great Britain won the silver medal in the sevens rugby match and Fiji won the gold medal</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>在周四晚上的七人制橄榄球赛决赛中，英国队未能在斐济队面前延续之前的出色表现，被斐济队以43比7在里约蒂奥多罗体育场击败。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">During the final game of rugby sevens in Thursday evening, the UK team was unable to sustain their outstanding performance before the Fijians and was defeated by the Fijian team at the Rio Deodoro Stadium with a score of 43 to 7.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">In the final of the seven-man rugby game in the evening of Thursday, the British team was defeated by Fiji in 43:7 at the Riotio Doro Stadium after failing to perform well before Fiji.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">The British team failed to extend their previous outstanding performance in front of Fiji in Thursday night's sevens rugby final, which was beaten 43-7 by Fiji at Riyotiodoro Stadium.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>斐济队凭借在控球、抢断、回避、配合、跑动和力量方面无懈可击的表现夺得金牌，这也是该国有史以来的首块奥运会奖牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">The Fijian team demonstrated impeccable performance in ball control, interception, dodging, teamwork, running, and power, taking the gold medal they deserve. This is also the country’s first Olympic gold in history.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Fiji won the gold medal for its impeccable performance in possession, interception, avoidance, co-ordination, running and strength, the first Olympic medal in the country's history.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Fiji won gold with an unassailable performance in possession, steals, avoidance, coordination, running and strength, the country's first ever Olympic medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>银牌对于被击败的英国队而言也算是一个不小的安慰，这块银牌是英国代表团当天获得的第三块银牌。这一成绩足以让英国橄榄球队感到骄傲：他们在首次进入奥运会的七人制橄榄球赛上一路击败了新西兰、阿根廷和南非。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">For the defeated British team, the silver medal offered some consolation. This silver medal was the third silver medal received by the British team that day. This accomplishment was enough to make the British rugby team feel proud: The first time they took part in the rugby sevens at the Olympic Games, they defeated New Zealand, Argentina and South Africa.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The silver medal was a great consolation to the defeated British team, which was the third silver medal The British delegation had won that day. The score was enough to make the English Olive team proud: They beat New Zealand, Argentina and South Africa in the first seven-man rugby game.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">The silver medal was also a small consolation to the defeated British team, which won its third silver medal of the day, a feat that was enough to make the British rugby team proud: they beat New Zealand, Argentina and South Africa all the way to their first rugby sevens tournament at the Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>当天早些时候，英国队以7比5险胜南非队，这可能影响了他们在决赛中状态。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Earlier that day, the UK team defeated the South African team with a slight margin of 7 to 5. This may affect their status in the finals.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Earlier in the day, the British team narrowly defeated South Africa by 7:5, which could affect their status in the final.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Earlier in the day, the British team narrowly beat South Africa 7-5, which may have affected their form in the final.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>但无论如何，现在的斐济队足以击败一支精神饱满的15人球队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Regardless, the current Fijian team is capable of defeating any 15-member rugby team with high morale.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">But in any case, Fiji is now enough to beat a 15-person team with a full spirit.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">But in any case, the current Fijian team is good enough to beat a spirited 15-a-side team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>明天，至少有一个英国人将戴上一块金牌，这对于英国队而言可能是一种安慰，但也可能不是。这个英国人就是来自温布尔顿的斐济队主教练本·瑞恩，他曾担任英国队的主教练。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Tomorrow, at least one British national will be wearing a gold medal. This may or may not be a form of consolation for the UK team. This British national is the head coach of the Fijian team, Ben Ryan. He was once the head coach of the British team.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Tomorrow, at least one Englishman will wear a gold medal, which may be a consolation to the British team, but it may not be. The Englishman, the head of the Fiji team from Wimbledon, was coach 本·瑞恩, who served as England's coach.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Tomorrow, at least one Briton will wear a gold medal, which may or may not be a consolation to the British team, namely Wimbledon's Fiji coach Ben Ryan, who was head coach of the British team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>英国队能取得今天的成绩实属不易。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">The results Britain obtained today was not easy.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">It is not easy for the British team to achieve today's results.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">It wasn't easy for the British team to get where they are today.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>八年前，在瑞恩的执教下，他们在阿德莱得国际七人制橄榄球赛上未尝胜果。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Eight years ago, coached by Ryan, they failed to win at the Adelaide IRB Sevens World Series.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Eight years ago, under the coaching of Ryan, they had no victory at the international rugby Sevens game.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Eight years ago, under Ryan's tutelage, they were undefeated at the Adelaide International Sevens Rugby Tournament.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>而现在，他们离冠军仅一步之遥。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Now they are only one step to champion.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Now they are only one step away from the championship.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">And now, they're just one step away from the title.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>虽然他们受到了巨大的打击，但也取得了十分惊人的进步。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Despite being severely affected, they managed to achieve surprising improvements.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Although they were hit hard, they made remarkable progress.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">While they have been hit hard, they have made remarkable progress.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>斐济开场就占据优势，使英国队毫无招架之力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Fiji dominated from the very beginning; the British team could barely hold its own.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Fiji took advantage of the opening, making the British team defenseless.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Fiji dominated the opening session, leaving the British team defenceless.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>对于汤姆·米切尔和他的队友而言，这就像撞上了一连串正在行驶的公共汽车。当欧西·科林尼索冲入角旗区时，这支世界系列赛冠军球队已经以5比0的比分遥遥领先了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">For Tom Mitchell and his teammates, it was like hitting a row of buses on the move. When Osea Kolinisau rushed into the corner flag section, this world series champion was already leading comfortably at 5-0.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">For Mitchell and his teammates, it's like hitting a series of buses that are moving. The World Series champions have been far ahead of the 5:0 score when 欧西·科林尼索 stormed into the corner flag.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">For Tom Mitchell and his teammates, it was like crashing into a string of moving buss.By the time Ossie Colliniseau slammed into the corner flag zone, the World Series champions were well ahead 5-0.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>比赛仅仅过了四分钟，杰瑞·图怀又在右翼触地得分。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Jerry Tuwai scored a touch down on the right wing just 4 minutes into the match.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Only four minutes after the game, 杰瑞·图怀 again scored on the right.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Just four minutes into the game, Jerry Toowey scored another touchdown on the right wing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>12比0，英国队几乎没有碰到过球。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">12 to 0. The UK team almost didn’t touch the ball at all.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">12:0, the British team has barely touched the ball.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">At 12-0, the British team had barely touched the ball.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>米切尔的强力阻截让巨人一般的里昂•那卡拉瓦没有第三次得分，但这仅仅是延缓了斐济得分的速度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Michael’s powerful tackle prevented the colossal Leone Nakarawa from making his third point. However, this only delayed the Fijian’s speed in scoring another goal.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Mitchell's strong interdiction made the giant Lyon Nakarava not score a third time, but it just slowed Fiji's score.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Mitchell's powerful interception kept the Giants' Lyon Nakalava from scoring a third time, but that only slowed Fiji's scoring.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>在7分钟时，亚萨·卫莱马鲁在右角触地。17比0，英国队雪上加霜。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">At the 7th minute, Jasa Veremalua touched down in the right corner. 17=0; it was one disaster after another for the British team.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">In 7 minutes, 亚萨·卫莱马鲁 in the right corner. 17:0, the British team to the worse.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Yassa Willemaru touched down in the right corner on seven minutes. 17-0, to add insult to injury for the British team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>那卡拉瓦又得一分，而比赛……的上半场还剩1分钟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Nacarava scored another point, and there was still 1 minute left in the first half of the match ........</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">That Caravaggio another point, and the game ... 1 minutes left in the first half.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Carrava scored another point with one minute left in the first half of the match.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>然后，瓦特莫·拉沃沃冲破英国队的防守，直达得分线。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Then Vatemo Ravouvou broke through the England defense, and scored.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Then, 瓦特莫·拉沃沃 broke through the English team's defense, straight to the scoring line.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Then Watmore LaVovo broke through the English defence and went straight to the scoring line.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>中场休息时，比分已经是29比0。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">During half-time, the score is already 29 to 0.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">At Half-time, the score was 29:0.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">By halftime, the score was already 29-0.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>斐济人就好像生来就是打7人制橄榄球的，而英国队仍是初出茅庐。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Playing Rugby Sevens seemed second nature to Fijians. The British team, on the other hand, are still fledglings.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The Fijians were born to play 7-man football, and the British team was still a rookie.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">The Fijians seem to have been born to play rugby sevens, while the British team is still in its infancy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>情况就是这样。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Such is the situation.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">This is the case.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">That's the way it is.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>英国队在下半场作出了巨大的改变并且在整整四分钟里冲击着斐济人的防线，就上半场而言，这一表现已经很好了。但之后斐济队打出精彩的配合，由乔舒亚·图埃索瓦再次得分。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">The UK team made drastic changes for the second half of the game and hurled themselves at the Fijian defenses for four minutes. This performance was, when compared to the first half, rather impressive. However, the Fujian team demonstrated fantastic teamwork, with Josua Tuisova scoring another touchdown.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The British team made a big change in the second half and hit the Fijian line for four minutes, which was good for the first half. But after the Fiji team played a wonderful match, the 乔舒亚·图埃索瓦 scored again.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Great Britain made a huge change in the second half and stormed the Fijians' defence for a full four minutes, which was fine in the first half, but then the Fijian team played well and scored again with Joshua Tuesova.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>丹·诺顿为英国队创造了得分的机会，他在左角触地，将比分更改为36比7，但比赛早已在南海岛国的掌控中，他们的球迷在站台上高声歌唱、挥舞旗帜、载歌载舞。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Dan Norton created a scoring opportunity for Great Britain. He touched own on the left corner and changed the score to 36-7, but the match had long been within the control of the South Sea Island nation. Their fans were signing, waving flags, and dancing in the stands.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">丹·诺顿 for the British team to create a scoring opportunity, he touched the ground in the left corner, the score changed to 36:7, but the game has long been in the South China Sea Island control, their fans on the platform singing loudly, waving flags, singing and dancing.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Dan Norton created a scoring opportunity for the British team by touching the ground in the left corner and changing the score to 36-7, but the game was already in the hands of the South China Sea island nation, whose fans were singing loudly, waving flags and singing and dancing on the platform.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>斐济队的精彩表现令人不得不拍手称快。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">The exciting performance given by the Fijian team was to be applauded.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The Fiji team's wonderful performance had to be applaud.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">The wonderful performance of the Fiji team had to be applauded.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>马塔·威廉在最后时刻阻止了斐济队的一次无所谓的进攻。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Mata Viliame prevented an indifferent attack by the Fiji team at the last moment.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">马塔·威廉 at the last minute stopped the Fiji team from an indifferent attack.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Mata William stopped an indifferent Fiji attack in the final minute.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>终场哨声响起，斐济人拥抱在一起，而完败的英国队只能遗憾退场。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">When the final whistle was blown, the Fijians got together in a big hug while the UK team left the field in defeat.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The final whistle sounded, the Fijian embraced together, and the defeated British team can only regret the exit.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">The final whistle sounded, the Fijians hugged each other, while the defeated British team could only regret leaving the game.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>当天早些时候，斐济队在半决赛中以20比5击败了日本队，而英国对在一场激烈的半决赛对决中险胜南非队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Earlier today, the Fijian team defeated the Japanese team in the semi-finals with a score of 20 to 5. The UK, on the other hand, won a victory by a very slim margin after a grueling semi-finals game.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Earlier in the day, Fiji defeated the Japanese team in 20:5 in the semi-final, while Britain narrowly edged out South Africa in a fierce semi-final clash.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Earlier in the day, Fiji beat Japan 20-5 in the semifinals, while Britain edged South Africa in a close semi-final clash.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>上半场凯尔·布朗帮助南非队取得领先，但丹·诺顿在下半场凭借出色的脚法破门得分。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">In the first half of the game, Kyle Brown helped the South African team achieve a lead, but Dan Norton and his impressive footwork managed to break through the defenses to score a point in the second half.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">The first half Brown helped South Africa to get ahead, but 丹·诺顿 scored in the second half with a good footwork.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">Kyle Brown helped South Africa take the lead in the first half, but Dan Norton scored in the second half with excellent footwork.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="152_independent.142372_en.sl">
    <source>之后，英格兰队安东尼的兄弟马库斯·沃森用精彩的拦截确保了球队的胜利，最终英国队夺得银牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.ht">Afterwards, Marcus Watson, a brother of Anthony, of the UK team secured the team’s victory with an impressive interception, allowing the UK to win the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.gg">Then England's Anthony's brother, 马库斯·沃森, ensured the team's victory with a brilliant intercept and eventually the British team won the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="152_independent.142372_en.c6">After that, England's Anthony's brother Marcus Watson secured the team's victory with a brilliant interception that ended with the British team winning the silver medal.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
