<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>俄罗斯总统普京解除谢尔盖·伊万诺夫办公厅主任职务</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">President of Russia, Putin, has relieved Sergei Ivanov of his position as the Chief of Staff of the Presidential Executive Office.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Russian President Vladimir Putin relieves Sergei Office director</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Russian President Vladimir Putin removes Sergei Ivanov as chief of staff</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>俄罗斯总统弗拉基米尔·普京 (Vladimir Putin) 出乎意料地解除了谢尔盖·伊万诺夫 (Sergei Ivanov) 的总统办公厅主任职务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Russian President Vladimir Putin dismissed Sergei Ivanov as Chief of Staff of the Presidential executive Office unexpectedly.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Vladimir Putin, Russia's president, unexpectedly relieved Sergei (Sergei Ivanov) of the presidency of the Office of the Chief of staff.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Vladimir Putin, Russia's president, unexpectedly sacked Sergei Ivanov as chief of staff to the president.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>多年来，伊万诺夫先生一直是深得普京先生信任的核心集团的一分子。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">For many years, Ivanov has always been a member of a core group of individuals deeply trusted by Putin.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr Ivanov has been a member of the core group that Mr Putin has trusted for years.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">For years, Mr. Ivanov has been part of a core group that has won Mr. Putin's trust.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>现年63岁的伊万诺夫如今已被任命为环境与交通问题特别代表。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Ivanov, now 63 years old, has been appointed as a special representative for environment and transportation issues.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr Ivanov, now 63, has been appointed Special Representative on environment and transport.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Ivanov, 63, has now been appointed special representative for the environment and transport.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>克里姆林宫的一份声明称，普京先生已“宣布解除伊万诺夫的俄罗斯总统办公厅主任一职，”但是没有给出原因。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">A statement from the Kremlin said that Mr Putin had “decreed to relieve Ivanov of his duties as head of the Russian presidential administration", but gave no reason.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">A statement from the Kremlin said Mr. Putin had "announced the release of the Office of the Chief of the Russian president of Ivanov," but gave no reason.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">A Kremlin statement said Mr. Putin had "announced the dismissal of Ivanov as chief of staff of the Russian president," without giving a reason.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>2012年开始担任伊万诺夫先生副手的安东·瓦伊诺 (Anton Vaino) 已获任命为他的接任者。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Anton Vaino, who has served as Ivanov’s assistant since 2012, has been appointed as his successor.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">安东·瓦伊诺 (Anton Vaino), who became deputy to Mr. Ivanov in 2012, has been appointed as his successor.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Anton Vaino, who began serving as Mr Ivanov's deputy in 2012, has been appointed as his replacement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>瓦伊诺先生现年44岁，是一名前外交官。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Mr Ivanov, 44, was a former diplomat.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr. Vaino, 44 years old, is a former diplomat.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Mr Vaino, 44, is a former diplomat.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>他1972年出生在爱沙尼亚首都塔林，毕业于著名的莫斯科国立国际关系学院 (MGIMO)，在东京大使馆工作过。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">He was born in Tallinn, the capital of Estonia, in 1972, and graduated from the famous Moscow State Institute of International Relations (MGIMO) and previously worked at the embassy at Tokyo.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Born in 1972 in Tallinn, the capital of Estonia, he graduated from the prestigious Moscow State Institute for International Relations (MGIMO) and worked at the embassy in Tokyo.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Born in 1972 in the Estonian capital Tallinn, he graduated from the prestigious Moscow State Institute of International Relations (MGIMO) and worked at the embassy in Tokyo.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>后来，他管理总统草案和政府员工，克里姆林宫网站（使用俄语）如是说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">According to the official website of the Kremlin (in Russian), he was in charge of managing presidential proposals and government officials.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Later, he managed the presidential draft and government employees, the Kremlin's website (using Russian) said.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">He later managed the presidential draft and government employees, according to the Kremlin's website (in Russian).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>获任命后，他对普京先生说：“谢谢您的信任。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">After receiving his appointment, he said to Mr Putin, “Thank you for your trust.”</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">After his appointment, he said to Mr Putin: "Thank you for your trust." ”</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">"Thank you for your trust," he told Mr. Putin after his appointment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>我认为本政府最重要的任务就是支持国家元首起草法律和控制指令实施。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">I believe the most important job of this government is to support laws drafted by the leader of our country and implement administrative directives.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">I think the government's most important task is to support the heads of State in drafting laws and controlling the implementation of directives.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">I believe that the most important task of this Government is to support the Head of State in the drafting of laws and the implementation of control orders.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>普京先生周五告诉俄罗斯电视台说，伊万诺夫先生自己要求辞职并推荐了瓦伊诺先生来接任自己。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Putin told Russian television channels on Friday that Ivanov has resigned on his own request, and recommended Ivanov to succeed him as well.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr. Putin told Russian television in Friday that Mr. Ivanov himself had asked to resign and recommended Mr. Vaino to take over.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Mr. Putin told Russian television on Friday that Mr. Ivanov himself had called for his resignation and recommended Mr. Vaino to take over.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>这样的笑容令人信服吗？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Can this smile convince anyone?</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Is such a smile convincing?</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Is this a convincing smile?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>莫斯科对此举感到不解。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Moscow is still confused about this act.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Moscow was puzzled by the move.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Moscow was puzzled by the move.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>长期以来，谢尔盖·伊万诺夫一直是普京最亲密的助手之一，跟普京一样，也在苏联安全局（克格勃）工作过。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Sergei Ivanov has long been one of Vladimir Putin's closest allies and, like him, served in the Soviet security service (KGB).</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Sergei has long been one of Mr Putin's closest aides, working for the Soviet Security Service (KGB), as did Mr Putin.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Sergei Ivanov has long been one of Putin's closest aides and, like Putin, has worked for the Soviet Security Service (KGB).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>作为办公厅主任，他曾是该国最具影响力的人士之一。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">As the Chief of Staff, he was once one of the most influential persons in the country.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">As Director of the office, he was one of the most influential people in the country.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">As chief of staff, he had been one of the country's most influential figures.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>在国家电视台播出的一次与普京总统的会面上，两人均称是这位办公厅主任自己要求辞职的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">At a meeting with President Putin broadcast by State television, the two men said that it was the Chief of Staff himself who tendered the resignation.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">At a meeting with President Putin on state television, both men said the chief executive himself had asked to resign.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">In a meeting with President Vladimir Putin broadcast on state television, both said the chief of staff had called for his resignation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>尽管在镜头前满面笑容，可是几乎没人信服——特别是在议会选举之前的这个时候。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">The candidate may be smiling in front of the camera, but no one is buying it, especially on the eve of local elections.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Although smiling in front of the camera, few people are convinced-especially before the parliamentary elections.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Despite the smiles on camera, few were convinced - especially at this time before the parliamentary elections.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>所以，这是在某种权力争夺中落败导致的吗？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">So, is this the result of having been defeated amid some sort of power struggle?</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">So, is this the result of a defeat in some sort of power struggle?</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">So is this the result of a defeat in some kind of power struggle?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>尚无从得知。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">There is no way of knowing anything from this.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">It is not yet known.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">It is not yet known.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>但是，官方说法——一个曾被视为总统候选人的人选突然间选择执掌俄罗斯的环境政策——引来了众多怀疑。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">The official narrative however - a candidate who was previously regarded as a presidential candidate would suddenly choose to preside over Russia’s environmental policy - caused much suspicion.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">But the official claim that a man who was once seen as a candidate for the presidency suddenly chose to take charge of the environmental policy of Russia has aroused much scepticism.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">But the official narrative - that a candidate once seen as a presidential candidate suddenly chose to take charge of Russia's environmental policy - has attracted a lot of skepticism.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>克里姆林宫网站上引述了伊万诺夫先生与普京先生的对话，他说："是的，2012年初，我曾在一次对话中请求你予以我这个难做的职位，甚至可以说是麻烦的职位，四年的任期。"</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">The Kremlin website cited a conversation between Mr Ivanoc and Mr Putin. He said, “Yes, at the beginning of 2012, I did, in a conversation, ask you to appoint me to this difficult post, or you could even say, troublesome post, for a four-year period.”</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">The Kremlin website quotes Mr. Ivanov's dialogue with Mr Putin, saying: "Yes, at the beginning of 2012, I asked you to give me this difficult position in a conversation, even a troublesome position, a four-year term." "</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Quoting Mr. Ivanov's conversation with Mr. Putin on the Kremlin's website, he said: "Yes, in early 2012, I asked you in a conversation to give me this difficult position, or even a troublesome position, for a four-year term."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>"结果是，我已担任总统办公厅主任四年八个月啦。"</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">“The result is that I've been the Chief of Staff of the Presidential Executive Office for 4 years and 8 months.”</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">"As a result, I have served as director of the president's Office for 4 years and eight months. "</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">"As a result, I've been the president's chief of staff for four years and eight months."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>伊万诺夫先生于2011年12月担任此职。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Mr Ivanov assumed this position in December 2011.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr. Ivanov held the post in December 2011.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Mr. Ivanov assumed the post in December 2011.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>在此之前，他担任副总理和国防部长。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Prior to that, he served as the deputy prime minister and defense minister.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Prior to that, he served as Deputy Prime Minister and Secretary of Defense.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Prior to that, he served as Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of Defence.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>他是俄罗斯安全委员会的一员，还跟普京先生一样，也是国家安全局前成员。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">He was a member of the Russian Security Council, and like Putin, was a former  member of the National Security Agency.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">He is a member of the Russian Security Council, as well as former members of the National Security Service, like Mr Putin.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">He is a member of the Russian Security Council and, like Mr. Putin, a former member of the National Security Agency.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>20世纪90年代末，当普京先生出任联邦安全局（FSB，前身为国家安全局）局长时，伊万诺夫先生被任命为他的副手。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">At the end of the 1990s, when Mr Putin was the director of the Federal Security Service (FSB, formerly the National Security Agency). Mr Ivanov was appointed his deputy.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr. Ivanov was appointed as his deputy in the late 1990s when Mr. Putin served as director of the Federal Security Service (FSB, formerly the National Security Agency).</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">When Mr. Putin became head of the Federal Security Service (FSB, formerly the National Security Agency) in the late 1990s, Mr. Ivanov was appointed his deputy.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>普京先生上台后，他又指定伊万诺夫先生为他最信任的五人之一。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">After Mr Putin came into power, he designated Mr Ivanov as one of five persons in his trusted inner circle.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">After Mr Putin came to power, he appointed Mr. Ivanov one of the five most trusted.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">When Mr. Putin came to power, he designated Mr. Ivanov as one of his five most trusted people.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>外界曾一度认为伊万诺夫先生可能会在普京先生第二任期结束后出任俄罗斯总统，因为三连任是违反宪法的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Other people thought that Ivanov may be able to become the President of Russia after Putin, because it is illegal in Russia to serve three consecutive terms as President.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">It was once thought that Mr Ivanov might be the president of Russia after Mr Putin's second term, since the third term is unconstitutional.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Mr Ivanov was once thought likely to become Russia's president after Mr Putin's second term, because a third term would be unconstitutional.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>但是这一职位最终归属于普京的另一位亲密助手德米特里·梅德韦杰夫 (Dmitry Medvedev)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">However, the position finally went to another trusted Putin aid, Dmitry Medvedev.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">But the position is ultimately vested in Mr Putin's other close aide, Dmitry Dmitry.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">But the job ultimately went to Dmitry Medvedev, Mr Putin's other close aide.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="087_bbc.242436_en.sl">
    <source>在三年半后重新任职总统之前，普京先生担任俄罗斯总理一职。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.ht">Prior to taking office as President again three and a half years later, Mr Putin served as Prime Minister of Russia.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.gg">Mr Putin served as Russia's prime minister before he was back in office after 3.5.</translation>
    <translation system="087_bbc.242436_en.c6">Mr. Putin served as Russia's prime minister until he returned to the presidency in three and a half years.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
