<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>2015年4月27日，美国和日本在纽约联合发表新版《美日防卫合作指针》，允许日本武装力量在全球扮演更具进攻性的角色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">On April 27, 2015, the US and Japan jointly announced the new Guidelines for U.S.-Japan Defense Cooperation in New York, allowing Japan’s defense forces to play a more offensive role in the world.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">April 27, 2015, the United States and Japan in New York jointly issued a new version of the U.S.-Japan Defense cooperation guidelines, allowing the Japanese armed forces to play a more offensive role in the world.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">On April 27, 2015, the United States and Japan jointly released a new edition of the U.S.-Japan Defense Cooperation Guidelines in New York, allowing Japan's armed forces to play a more offensive role around the world.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>这是当日美国国防部长卡特、美国国务卿克里、日本外务大臣岸田文雄和日本防卫大臣中谷元在纽约出席新闻发布会。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">This was US Secretary of Defense Ash Carter, US Secretary of State John Kerry, Japanese Minister for Foreign Affairs Fumio Kishida, and Japanese Defense Minister Gen Nakatani attending a press conference in New York.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">This is the day when U.S. Defense Secretary Jimmy Carter, U.S. Secretary of State John Kerry, Japanese Foreign Minister Kishida and Japanese Defense Minister Zhong in New York to attend a press conference.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">US Defense Secretary Ash Carter, US Secretary of State John Kerry, Japanese Foreign Minister Fumio Kishida and Japanese Defense Minister Nakatani attended a press conference in New York on the same day.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>这是中国民间智库第五次发表日本军力评估报告，也是第四次推出英文版。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">This is the fifth evaluation report released by a private think tank in China on Japanese military power, and the fourth report released in the English language.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">This is the fifth time the Chinese folk think-tank to publish the Japanese military Assessment Report, is also the fourth launch of the English version.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">This is the fifth time that a Chinese nongovernmental think tank has published an assessment of Japan's military strength, and the fourth time it has launched an English version.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>报告分9章，包括总体政策调整、军事实力、国防预算、军事部署、武器装备、体制编制改革、军事训演、对外军事安全合作、对华军事安全关系等内容。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">The report is divided into 9 chapters, comprising: overall policy adjustments, military power, national defense budget, military deployment, weapons and equipment, organizational reforms, military exercises, security partnerships with other countries, and military security relations with China.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">The report is divided into 9 chapters, including overall policy adjustment, military strength, defense budget, military deployment, weapons and equipment, system reform, military training, foreign military security cooperation and military security relations with China.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">The report is divided into nine chapters, including general policy adjustment, military strength, national defense budget, military deployment, weapons and equipment, institutional reform, military training and exercises, foreign military security cooperation, and military security relations with China.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>报告称，2015年是安倍政府在安全领域连续数年推进重大政策调整的阶段性收官之年。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">The report claimed that 2015 was the final year in the process of major policy adjustments in national security of Abe’s government.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">The report said 2015 was the year in which Abe's government had been in the security field for several consecutive years to advance major policy adjustments.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">According to the report, 2015 marked the end of a period in which the Abe administration pushed through several years of major policy adjustments in the security sector.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>此后，日本在安全领域的举措将主要是在法制运用、战略贯彻、政策落实等操作层面，而不是框架、机制和政策的大幅调整和变动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">Since then, Japan’s measures in security primarily focus on the operational level such as using the law, realizing their strategies, and enforcing their policies, and does not include large scale adjustments or changes to their framework, mechanism, or policy.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">Since then, Japan's security efforts will be mainly in the legal application, strategic implementation, policy implementation and other operational aspects, rather than the framework, mechanisms and policies of the drastic adjustment and change.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">Since then, Japan's initiatives in the area of security will be mainly at the operational level of the application of the rule of law, the implementation of strategies and the implementation of policies, rather than major adjustments and changes in frameworks, mechanisms and policies.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>报告强调，安倍内阁试图通过以上三点突破，达到推动日本“正常国家化”、自卫队走出去介入国际安全事务、强化日美同盟、防华制华的多重目的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">The report emphasized that with the three breakthroughs,  Abe cabinet attempted to driving the " Normal-nationalized"  of Japan, enabling the JSDF to be involved in international security affairs, enhancing Japan-U.S alliances to prevent against and restrict China.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">The report stressed that Abe's cabinet tried to achieve the multiple purposes of promoting Japan's "normal country" and the self-defense team to intervene in international security affairs, strengthen the Alliance of Japan and the United States and prevent China from making breakthroughs above three points.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">The report stressed that Abe ’ s cabinet is trying to achieve the multiple goals of promoting Japan ’ s “normal nationalization, ” stepping out of the Self-Defense Forces to intervene in international security affairs, strengthening the Japan-US alliance, and preventing China from dominating China through the three breakthroughs mentioned above.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.sl">
    <source>此前，中国战略文化促进会先后于2012年6月5日、2013年7月19日、2014年7月23日、2015年6月30日发布过日本军力评估报告。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.ht">The China Strategy Culture Promotion Association have published Japanese military force assessment reports on June 5th 2012, July 19th 2013, July 23rd 2014, and June 30th 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.gg">Earlier, the China Strategic Culture Promotion Association in June 5, 2012, July 19, 2013, July 23, 2014, June 30, 2015 issued a Japanese Military assessment report.</translation>
    <translation system="033_peopledaily0812.world.c1002-28631539_zh.c6">Previously, the China Council for the Promotion of Strategic Culture issued Japan's military assessment reports on June 5, 2012, July 19, 2013, July 23, 2014, and June 30, 2015, respectively.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
