<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在老宅新生和成功乡创的案例中，何培均做了很好的示范：传承一间百年古宅，同时也讲述一块土地的传承故事。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.ht">In the revival of old residences and successful village entrepreneurship cases, He Peijun gave a very good demonstration: Inheritance of a century-old home and the telling of a story on the inheritance of a piece of land.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.gg">In the old residence and success of the case, He Pei have done a good demonstration: The inheritance of a century old curtilage, but also tells a piece of land inheritance story.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.c6">In the case of the rebirth of the old house and the successful township creation, He Peijun has done a good demonstration: Inherit a century-old house, but also tell the story of the inheritance of a piece of land at the same time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.sl">
    <source>如今，每年平均有10万人次会聚到竹山，或是带来各种各样的创意，或是寻求内心的宁静。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.ht">To date, about 100,000 people will visit Zhushan every year, some bring various kinds of creativity, while others seek inner solace.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.gg">Today, an average of 100,000 people converge to Zhushan each year, either to bring in a variety of ideas or to seek inner peace.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.c6">Today, an average of 100,000 people gather in Takeyama each year, either to bring a variety of ideas, or to seek inner peace.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.sl">
    <source>其实，乡村和城市的关系应该是相互陪伴，就像母亲和孩子一样，没有强弱之分，没有需要谁来统治谁，应该是很温暖的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.ht">In fact, the rural-urban relationship should be one of companionship, like mother and child, without the difference between strong and weak, without requiring who was to govern whom; it should be very warm.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.gg">In fact, the relationship between the country and the city should be accompanied by each other, just like mother and child, there is no strong and weak points, no need who to rule who, should be very warm.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.c6">In fact, the relationship between the country and the city should be accompanied by each other, just like the mother and child, there is no distinction between strong and weak, there is no need to rule who, it should be very warm.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.sl">
    <source>乡村开发没有什么固定的模式，但靠乡村自发的改变难乎其难，最重要的一点应该是让对的人到乡村去。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.ht">There are no fixed model for rural development, but it is extremely difficult for a village to achieve changes on its own. The most important point is to ensure that the right people is sent to the villages.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.gg">There is no fixed model for rural development, but it is difficult to change spontaneously in rural areas, and the most important thing is to let the right people go to the countryside.</translation>
    <translation system="145_ifeng0812.news.49764567_0_zh.c6">There is no fixed pattern of rural development, but it is extremely difficult to rely on rural spontaneous change, the most important point should be to let the right people to go to the countryside.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
