<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰皇家银行将不再为苏格兰以外客户服务</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The Royal Bank of Scotland will no longer serve customers outside Scotland</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">Royal Bank of Scotland will no longer serve customers outside Scotland</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">Royal Bank of Scotland will no longer serve customers outside Scotland</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>据苏格兰皇家银行首席执行官透露，银行将简化为一个后勤部门。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">According to the CEO of Royal Bank of Scotland, the bank will be reduced into a logistic department.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">According to RBS's chief executive, the bank will be reduced to a logistics unit.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">The bank will be reduced to a logistics arm, according to the chief executive of RBS.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰皇家银行将不再为苏格兰以外的客户服务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The Royal Bank of Scotland will no longer service customers outside of Scotland.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">Royal Bank of Scotland will no longer serve customers outside Scotland.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">Royal Bank of Scotland will no longer serve customers outside of Scotland.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>罗斯·麦克尤恩告诉英国广播公司苏格兰分部，苏格兰皇家银行品牌曾经致力于其全球雄心壮志。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">Rose McEwan shared with the Scotland branch of BBC about how devoted the Royal Bank of Scotland in their global ambition.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">罗斯·麦克尤恩 told the BBC Scottish division that the Royal Bank of Scotland brand was committed to its global ambitions.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">Ross McEwan told BBC Scotland that the Royal Bank of Scotland brand was committed to its global ambitions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>但八年前濒临倒闭，不得不接受救助从那时开始便放弃了那样的追求。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">On the edge of bankruptcy some eight years ago, however, there was no choice but to accept a bailout. From then on, those pursuits were abandoned.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">But eight years ago, the brink of collapse, had to accept the rescue from then on to abandon the pursuit.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">But that pursuit was abandoned eight years ago when he was on the brink of bankruptcy and had to be bailed out.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>那段时间，品牌策略师使用‘RBS’来保护其它消费金融品牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">During this time, the brand building strategist used “RBS” to protect the other consumer finance brands.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">During that time, brand strategists used ' RBS ' to protect other consumer financial brands.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">During that time, brand strategists used 'RBS' to protect other consumer finance brands.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>集团曾耗费数百万英镑以赞助橄榄球六国赛和温布尔顿网球锦标赛冠军安迪·穆雷等方式赞助国际体育赛事。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The Group has spent millions of pounds to sponsor the Six Nations Championship in rugby and Andy Murray, winner of The Championships, Wimbledon to support international sports events.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">The group has spent £ millions of to sponsor international sporting events, including the rugby six-nation tournament and Wimbledon tennis Championship champion Andy.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">The group has spent millions of pounds sponsoring international sporting events such as the Rugby Six Nations and Wimbledon tennis champion Andy Murray.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>但是现在，正确的做法是让更多的国家品牌崭露头角。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">Currently, however, the correct measure is to provide national brands with opportunities of exposure.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">But now, the right thing to do is make more national brands emerge.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">But now, the right thing to do is to get more national brands to make their mark.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰皇家银行将为苏格兰客户所用，但不会回复原样。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The Royal Bank of Scotland will be used by Scottish clients but will not revert to its original form.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">RBS will be used for Scottish customers but will not revert to the original.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">RBS will be used by Scottish customers, but will not revert to its original form.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>在英格兰和威尔士，所有在总部及证券交易所以外的提法将更改为国民西敏寺银行。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">In England and Wales, all references apart from those at the headquarters and the stock exchange shall be changed to National Westminster Bank.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">In England and Wales, all references outside the headquarters and stock exchanges will be changed to the National Westminster Bank.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">In England and Wales, all references outside the head office and the stock exchange will be changed to National Westminster Bank.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>阿尔斯特银行品牌已用于爱尔兰共和国与北爱尔兰自治区的客户。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The brand of Ulster Bank is used by customers in the Republic of Ireland and the autonomous Northern Ireland.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">The Ulster Bank brand has been used to Ireland, Rep. Of customers in the Autonomous Region of Northern Ireland.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">The Ulster Bank brand has been used by customers in the Republic of Ireland and the Autonomous Region of Northern Ireland.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>还有一些其它更突出的较小私人银行品牌，例如顾资银行、Adam &amp; Co、 Drummond 与 Holt's Military Bank。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">There is also a number of smaller, private banks such as Coutts, Adam &amp; Co., Drummond, and Holt’s Military Bank.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">There are other, more prominent, smaller private banking brands, such as Guzi Bank, Adam &amp; Co, Drummond and Holt ' s military bank.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">There are other, more prominent, smaller private banking brands, such as Citi, Adam &amp; Co, Drummond and Holt's Military Bank.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>麦克尤恩先生曾在因弗内斯郡客户与员工的参观之旅中接受采访。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">Mr McEwan was interviewed during a trip to Inverness to visit customers and staff.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">Mr. McEwen was interviewed by clients and employees in Inverness County.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">Mr. McEwan was interviewed during a visit with customers and employees in Inverness County.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>他告诉英国广播公司苏格兰分部说：“苏格兰皇家银行品牌将最终成为我们的投资者品牌，同时也是员工受雇品牌之一，因为目前更大意义上我们已成为一个拥有众多品牌的银行。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">He told the BBC Scotland, “The RBS brand will end up becoming our investor brand and the one that our staff are employed with, because we are now becoming much more a bank of brands.”</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">He told the BBC's Scottish division: "The Royal Bank of Scotland brand will eventually become our investor brand and one of the employees ' hired brands because we have become a bank with many brands in the larger sense." ”</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">He told BBC Scotland: "The RBS brand will eventually become our investor brand as well as one of the employee hire brands, as we have become a bank with many brands in a larger sense at the moment."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>由于该银行本身成为一个国际品牌，RBS也成为全球品牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">As the bank itself became an international label, RBS thus became a global brand.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">As the bank itself becomes an international brand, RBS has become a global brand.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">As the bank itself became an international brand, RBS also became a global brand.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>目前，我要说的是，我们不再重点关注全球，我们已将目光转向本土。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">What I want to say is that our current priority is no longer the world; we have instead switched our focus to the domestic market.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">At present, I would like to say that we are no longer focused on the global, we have turned our eyes to the mainland.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">For now, I would say that we are no longer focusing on the global, we have turned our eyes to the local.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>每一个品牌代表着各自所在行业的不同，而我们的员工通过不同品牌为客户服务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">Every brand symbolized a specific field. Our staff serve the customers via different brands.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">Each brand represents a different industry, and our employees serve their customers through different brands.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">Each brand represents a difference in their respective industries, and our employees serve our customers through different brands.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰皇家银行已表明不会继续赞助六国锦标赛；同时，已努力提升不同品牌在体育赛事赞助的形象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The Royal Bank of Scotland has indicated that it would no longer sponsor the Six Nations Championship. At the same time, it is working diligently to raise the image of different brands by sponsoring sporting events.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">RBS has indicated it will not continue to sponsor the six-nation championships and has tried to raise the profile of different brands in sporting events.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">RBS has indicated that it will not continue to sponsor the Six Nations Championships; at the same time, it has worked to raise the profile of different brands in sponsoring sporting events.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>首席执行官表示：“现在到了成为一家多品牌银行的时候，因为私下我们一直在探求如何成为一家更好的服务于客户的银行。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">The CEO expressed: “Now we’ve become a bank of multiple brands because privately, we’ve been investigating the means by which we can become a bank that provides a better service to our customer.”</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">"It's time to become a multi-brand bank, because in private we have been exploring how to become a better bank to serve our customers," the chief executive said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">"It's time to become a multi-brand bank because privately we've been looking at ways to be a better customer service bank," the chief executive said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>如果三年前我们立志成为一家拥有众多品牌的大银行将备受嘲讽。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">If we claimed, 3 years ago, that we aim to become a giant bank of multiple brands, people will definitely be laughing at us.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">It would be ironic if we aspire to be a big bank with many brands three years ago.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">We would have been ridiculed if we had aspired three years ago to become a big bank with many brands.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>目前我们重点关注客户需求，并且我相信您已注意到了这些变化。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">Currently, we are prioritizing our focus on customer requirements, and I believe that you have noticed these changes.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">We are now focusing on customer needs and I believe you have noticed these changes.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">At the moment we are focusing on the needs of our customers and I am sure you are aware of these changes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="108_bbc.242405_en.sl">
    <source>我认为我们可以重新启动这些品牌，而且现在时间正合适。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.ht">I believe we can re-activate these brands. This seems to be the right time to do so.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.gg">I think we can restart these brands and the time is right.</translation>
    <translation system="108_bbc.242405_en.c6">I think we can relaunch these brands, and the time is right.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
