<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>每天2英镑的药物可降低心脏病发作威胁</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Drug that cost 2 pounds per day can reduce risks of heart attack incidence</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">2 pounds of drugs a day can reduce the risk of heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">£2-a-day drug could reduce heart attack threat</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>相关官员建议将一种每天2英镑的药物推广给更多患者并且要延长服药时间，之后数以千计的心脏病患者将从这种药物中受益。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Relevant officials recommended promoting a GBP2 per day drug to more patients, and extending the period of taking medication. Going forward, thousands of cardiovascular patients will benefit from this drug.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Officials suggest that a drug of 2 pounds a day be extended to more patients and to take longer, and thousands of heart patients will benefit from the drug.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">Thousands of heart patients will benefit from a £2 a day drug after officials suggest it should be rolled out to more patients and for longer periods of time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>抗凝血药替卡格雷 (ticagrelor) 可降低心脏病患者的心脏病复发风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Platelet aggregation inhibitor, ticagrelor, can lower the risk of a repeat heart attack among cardiac patients.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Anticoagulant drug Ticagrelor (ticagrelor) can reduce the risk of heart disease recurrence in patients with heart disease.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">The anticoagulant ticagrelor reduces the risk of heart disease recurrence in patients with heart disease.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>这种药物在心脏病发作后持续服用12个月，可降低中风或心脏病再次发作的风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Using this drug for 12 months after a heart attack episode can help reduce recurrence of stroke or heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">The drug, which lasts for 12 months after a heart attack, can reduce the risk of another stroke or heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">The drug is taken continuously for 12 months after a heart attack and can reduce the risk of a stroke or another heart attack.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>英国国家医疗服务体系 (NHS) 下属监管机构国家卫生与临床优化研究所 (NICE) 建议患者持续服药四年，以便进一步降低心脏血管疾病的风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">The National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE), an organization under the National Health Service (NHS) of the UK, recommended patients to keep using the drug for 4 years in order to further reduce risks of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">The National Institute of Health and Clinical optimization (NICE), a regulator of the NHS, advises patients to continue taking four years to further reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">The NHS watchdog, the National Institute for Health and Clinical Excellence (NICE), advises patients to take medication for four years in order to further reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>但是现在，NHS 监管机构 NICE 建议给患者持续服药四年，以便进一步降低心脏血管疾病的风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Now however, NHS regulator, NICE recommends that patients continue to take medication for four years so as to further lower the risk of cardiovascular diseases.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">But now, the NHS regulator, Nice, recommends that patients continue to take four years of medication to further reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">But now NICE, the NHS watchdog, recommends giving patients medication for four years to further reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>在英格兰，每年有大约140,000人罹患心脏病，其中有四分之一会继续遭遇心脏病复发或出现中风。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">In England, about 140,000 individuals suffer from cardiac diseases, and one out of four of these individuals will suffer from recurrence in heart attack or experience a stroke.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">In England, about 140,000 people suffer from heart disease each year, and One-fourth continue to suffer from heart attacks or strokes.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">About 140,000 people in England suffer a heart attack each year, and a quarter of them continue to suffer a heart attack or stroke.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>心脏病发作和中风是脂肪物质在动脉壁沉积形成斑块导致的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Heart attacks and strokes are caused by plaque from the buildup of fatty substances formed on the walls of arteries.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Heart attacks and strokes are caused by the accumulation of fatty matter in the arterial wall.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">Heart attacks and strokes are caused by fatty deposits forming plaques on the walls of the arteries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>如果斑块断开，就会导致血栓，进而阻碍血流入心脏，导致心脏病发作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">When the plaque breaks, it will induce a thrombus and obstruct blood flow into the heart, leading to a heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">If the plaque is broken, it can lead to thrombosis, which in turn hinders blood flow to the heart, leading to heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">If the plaque breaks, it can lead to a blood clot, which in turn can block blood flow to the heart, leading to a heart attack.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>如果血栓移动，就会进入血流，阻碍血流入大脑，导致中风。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">If the thrombus moves, it will enter the blood stream and prevent blood flow into the brain, leading to a stroke.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">If the thrombus moves, it enters the bloodstream, hindering blood flow to the brain and causing a stroke.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">If the clot moves, it can enter the bloodstream, blocking blood flow to the brain, leading to a stroke.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>已经经历过一次心脏病发作的患者，心脏病再次发作的风险更高。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">A patient who had suffered a heart attack has a higher risk of another attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Patients who have experienced a heart attack have a higher risk of heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">Patients who have already experienced a heart attack have a higher risk of another heart attack.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>替卡格雷由英国公司阿斯利康 (AstraZeneca) 制造，以倍林达 (Brilique) 为商品名进行销售，可通过减少血栓的形成来降低发病风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Ticagrelor (trade name Brilique) is a platelet aggregation inhibitor produced by AstraZeneca.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Ticagrelor is made by the British company AstraZeneca (AstraZeneca), which is marketed in the name of Linda (Brilique), which reduces the risk of developing the disease by reducing thrombosis.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">Made by the British company AstraZeneca and sold under the trade name Brilique, ticagrelor reduces the risk of developing disease by reducing the formation of blood clots.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>今日发布的 NICE 指导草案建议患者服用90 mg 的替卡格雷12个月时间，之后的三年每天服用60mg替卡格雷和两次阿斯匹林。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">The NICE guidance draft issued today recommended patients take 90mg of ticagrelor for 12 months, and in the subsequent three years, 60mg of ticagrelor and two aspirins should be taken each day.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">The nice draft guidelines, released today, recommend that patients take the ticagrelor for 12 months, taking 60mg Ticagrelor and two aspirin a day for three years.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">The draft NICE guidance, released today, advises patients to take 90 mg of ticagrelor for 12 months, and 60 mg of ticagrelor and two aspirin daily for the next three years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>NICE 卫生技术评估中心主任 Carole Longson 教授说：“尽管有有效的二级预防治疗，但是有多达四分之一有过心脏病发作史的患者会再次发病或中风，通常会造成严重后果。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Dr. Carole Longson, director of the NICE health technology assessment center, said: “Despite having a number of effective secondary preventive treatments, more than a quarter of patients who experienced heart attack will experience another episode of heart attack or stroke, leading to devastating results.”</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Professor Carole Longson, director of the Nice Health Technology Assessment Center, said: "Despite effective two-level preventive treatment, up to one-fourth patients with a history of heart attack relapse or stroke, often with serious consequences." ”</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">Professor Carole Longson, director of the NICE Centre for Health Technology Assessment, said: "Despite effective secondary prevention treatment, up to one in four people with a history of heart attack will suffer a second attack or stroke, often with serious consequences."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>对复发的恐惧会对一个人的生活品质造成很大的负面影响。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Fear of a relapse has a very negative impact on a person’s quality of life.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Fear of recurrence can have a great negative impact on a person's quality of life.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">The fear of recurrence can have a significant negative impact on a person's quality of life.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>证据表明，替卡格雷与阿司匹林一起服用可有效降低那些经历过心脏病发作之患者心脏病复发及中风的风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">Evidence suggest that ticagrelor and aspirin, when taken together, can effectively reduce recurrence of heart conditions and risks for stroke for patients who had experienced heart attacks before.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Evidence suggests that taking ticagrelor with aspirin can effectively reduce the risk of heart disease recurrence and stroke in patients who experience a heart attack.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">The evidence suggests that taking ticagrelor with aspirin can be effective in reducing the risk of heart attack recurrence and stroke in patients who have experienced a heart attack.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>替卡格雷的临时推荐将为成千上万受益的人们提供更多的治疗选择，对此我们深感欣慰。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">The temporary recommendation of ticagrelor will provide more treatment alternatives for thousands of beneficiaries; for this we are deeply gratified.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">We are pleased that the temporary recommendation for Ticagrelor will provide more treatment options for thousands of people who benefit.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">We are deeply relieved that Ticagrelle's interim recommendation will provide many more treatment options for the thousands of people who have benefited.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.sl">
    <source>由于有关替卡格雷在三年后的疗效及安全，特别是出血风险的信息很有限，该指导草案并不建议在这一期限之后继续用其治疗。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.ht">However, due to the limited information on the therapeutic efficacy and safety of ticagrelor, especially the risks of bleeding, this instruction proposal does not recommend continuous use of the drug for subsequent treatment.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.gg">Given the limited information about the efficacy and safety of Ticagrelor in three years, especially the risk of bleeding, the draft guidance does not recommend continuing treatment after that period.</translation>
    <translation system="099_dailymail.co.uk.170665_en.c6">Given the limited information available on the efficacy and safety of ticagrelor after three years, in particular the risk of bleeding, the draft guidance does not recommend its continued use beyond this period.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
