<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>冷战期间，苏联把导弹运进古巴，差点导致美苏发生核战争。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">During the Cold War, the Soviet Union deployed missiles to Cuba, and almost triggered a nuclear war with the US.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">During the Cold War, the Soviet Union brought missiles into Cuba, almost leading to a nuclear war between the United States and the USSR.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">During the Cold War, the Soviet Union brought missiles into Cuba, which almost led to a nuclear war between the United States and the Soviet Union.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>这一事件被看做冷战的顶峰，史称“古巴导弹危机”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">This event was regarded as the zenith of the Cold War, and was known in history as the “Cuban missile crisis”.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">The incident was seen as the pinnacle of the Cold War, known as the "Cuban Missile Crisis".</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">The event was seen as the culmination of the Cold War, known as the "Cuban Missile Crisis."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>但鲜为人知的是，同样是冷战期间，一场强烈的太阳风暴也曾险些导致美国对苏联发动核战争，这一事件直到8月9日才首次由研究人员对外公布。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">What was little known was that during the Cold War, a strong solar storm almost sparked a nuclear war between the US and the Soviet Union. This was only publicly disclosed by researchers for the first time on August 9.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">But it is little known that during the Cold War, too, a strong solar storm narrowly led to a nuclear war against the Soviet Union, which was not released for the first time by researchers until August 9.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">Little is known, however, that a strong solar storm, also during the Cold War, nearly led the United States to launch a nuclear war against the Soviet Union, an event that was first made public by researchers on August 9.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>1967年5月23日，一场强烈的太阳风暴对美国军方位于北极的雷达与无线电通信造成强烈干扰。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">On May 23, 1967, a powerful solar storm caused severe disruptions to a North Pole radar station and radio communications of the US military.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">May 23, 1967, a strong solar storm on the U.S. military in the Arctic radar and radio communications caused strong interference.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">On May 23, 1967, a powerful solar storm caused intense interference with the U.S. military's radar and radio communications in the Arctic.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>这些雷达是美国弹道导弹预警系统的一部分，用于监测苏联的导弹。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">This radar is part of the US ballistic missile early warning system, and is used to monitor Soviet missiles.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">These radars are part of the U.S. ballistic missile early warning system to monitor Soviet missiles.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">The radars are part of a U.S. ballistic missile early warning system used to monitor Soviet missiles.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>这篇由美国科罗拉多大学研究人员完成的论文采访了当时参与预报与分析太阳活动的美军方人员，并查阅了非保密文献。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">This thesis, completed by researchers at the University of Colorado, interviewed US military personnel who took part in forecasting and analyzing the sun’s activities at the time, as well as consulted unclassified documents.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">The paper, completed by researchers at the University of Colorado, interviewed U.S. personnel involved in the forecast and analysis of solar activity, and consulted unclassified documents.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">The paper, by researchers at the University of Colorado, interviewed U.S. military personnel involved in forecasting and analyzing solar activity at the time, and reviewed non-classified literature.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>论文写道，上世纪60年代，为防止苏联突然发动核战争，美国空军始终有一部分载有核弹头的战机飞在天上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">The article said the U.S. Air Force kept fighters loaded with nuclear warhead patrolling in the air in 1960s to prevent any sudden nuclear war waged by the U.S.S.R</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">In the 60 's, the United States Air Force has always had a part of a nuclear warhead flying in the sky to prevent the Soviet Union from suddenly waging a nuclear war, the paper wrote.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">In the 1960s, to prevent a sudden nuclear war by the Soviet Union, the US Air Force always had a portion of warplanes carrying nuclear warheads flying in the sky, the paper wrote.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>美军军方指挥官不知道这次干扰的罪魁祸首是太阳风暴而非苏联，于是下令使战机进入战斗准备状态。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">The US military commander was unaware that the interference was caused by a solar storm and not the Soviet Union, and thus gave orders for all military aircraft to enter combat status.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">The US military commanders were unaware that the main culprit of the disturbance was the solar storm, not the Soviet Union, and ordered the fighters to enter combat readiness.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">Unaware that the main culprit for the disturbance was a solar storm rather than the Soviet Union, the US military commander ordered that the warplanes be put into combat readiness.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>幸运的是，美国军方从上世纪50年代末就开始的太阳活动及其对地球电磁干扰的研究，最终阻止了这场潜在的军事冲突。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">Fortunately, the potential military conflict was avoided by the study of solar activity and its electromagnetic interference to earth conducted by U.S.army from the end of 1950s.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">Fortunately, the U.S. military's solar activity, which began in the late 50 and its study of Earth's electromagnetic interference, ultimately prevented the potential military conflict.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">Fortunately, the US military's research into solar activity and its electromagnetic interference with the Earth, which began in the late 1950s, eventually stopped this potential military conflict.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>稍后，他汇总美国空军航空气象处提供的信息，提交了一份详细报告。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">He then compiled the information provided by the US Air Force Air Weather Service and submitted a detailed report.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">Later, he summarized the information provided by the United States Air Force Aviation Meteorological Service and submitted a detailed report.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">Later, he compiled the information provided by the U.S. Air Force's Aviation Weather Service and submitted a detailed report.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.sl">
    <source>这场太阳风暴的直接后果是，美国军方从此把空间天气视为一项作战关切，并建立了一个更强大的空间天气预报系统。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.ht">The direct consequence of the solar storm is that the US military began viewing space weather as a key component of battle, and established a more powerful space weather early warning system.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.gg">The immediate consequence of this solar storm is that the U.S. military has since seen space weather as a combat concern and has built a more powerful space weather forecast system.</translation>
    <translation system="120_peopledaily0812.scitech.c1007-28631569_zh.c6">As a direct consequence of the solar storm, the United States military has since regarded space weather as an operational concern and has established a more robust space weather forecasting system.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
