<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>北京时间8月12日消息，2016年里约奥运会女子50米步枪三种姿势决赛战罢，中国老将杜丽获得铜牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">In August 12, Beijing time, the Chinese veteran Du Li won a bronze medal after completing 2016 Rio Olympics women’s 50 metre rifle three positions finals.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">Beijing Time August 12 News, 2016-year-old Olympic women's 50-metre rifle three posture finals, Chinese veteran Dorrit won the bronze medal.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">BEIJING, August 12 (Xinhua) -- Chinese veteran Du Li won a bronze medal in the women's 50-meter rifle three-position final at the Rio 2016 Olympic Games.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>杜丽成为奥运四朝元老，4次奥运共拿下2金1银1铜四块奖牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">Du Li has become a four Olympic Game veteran, having won a total of four medals - two gold, one silver and one bronze - in the four Games.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">Dorrit became the Olympic four-headed veteran, 4 Olympic Games won 2 Gold 1 silver 1 bronze four medals.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">Du Li became a veteran of the four Olympic dynasties, winning a total of two gold, one silver and four bronze medals in four Olympic Games.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>1998年，进入山东省射击队，跟随王德文教练进行专业的射击训练。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">In 1998, she joined the Shandong Province shooting team, and underwent professional training in shooting under the guidance of coach Wang Dewen.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">1998, into the Shandong province shooting team, followed Wang coaches to carry out professional shooting training.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">In 1998, entered the shooting team in Shandong Province, with coach Wang German professional shooting training.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2003年6月，参加射击世界杯克罗地亚站女子10米气步枪金牌并以504.9环打破世界纪录。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">In June 2003, she took part in the Shooting  World Cup women’s 10-meter air rifle standing event in Croatia, and set a world record of 504.9.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">June 2003, participated in the shooting World Cup Croatian station woman 10-metre gas rifle gold medal and broke the world record with 504.9 ring.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">In June 2003, she took part in the Women's 10m Air Rifle gold medal at the World Shooting Cup in Croatia and broke the world record with 504.9 rings.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2004年8月，获得女子10米气步枪金牌，为中国代表队在雅典奥运会夺得首金。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">In August 2004, she won the gold medal for the women’s 10-meter air rifle competition, and claimed the first gold medal for China at the Athens Olympic Games.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">August 2004, won the women's 10-metre gas rifle gold medal for the Chinese team in Athens Olympic Games won the first gold.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">In August 2004, she won the gold medal in the women's 10m air rifle, winning the first gold medal for the Chinese team at the Athens Olympic Games.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2008年8月，在50米运动步枪三姿的比赛中以总成绩690.3环破奥运会纪录夺得金牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">Won the Gold Metal by 690.3 total shots in the 50 meter rifle three positions.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">In August 2008, he won the gold medal in the 50-metre sports rifle three-posture race with a total 690.3-ring-breaking Olympic record.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">In August 2008, he won the gold medal in the 50-meter sport rifle three-position competition, breaking the Olympic record with a total score of 690.3.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2012年8月，折戟伦敦奥运会后，杜丽向国际射联申报了暂时退役申请。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">After experiencing a defeat at the London Olympics in August 2012, Du Li submitted a temporary resignation application to the International Shooting Sport Federation.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">After the London Olympic Games in August 2012, Dorrit filed a temporary retirement application with the International Union.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">In August 2012, after the London Olympics in Trident, Dooley filed an application for temporary retirement with the International Association of Shooters.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2015年1月，杜丽宣布重回国家队开始训练，备战里约奥运。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">In January 2015, Du Li announced that she will be reporting to the national team for training and prepare for the Rio Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">In January 2015, Dorrit announced a return to the national team to start training for the Rio Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">In January 2015, Dooley announced her return to the national team to start training in preparation for the Rio Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2016年3月，里约奥运选拔赛结束，时隔8年再次获得女子10米气步枪奥运会参赛资格。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">The qualifying rounds of the Rio Olympics were concluded in March 2016. After an eight-year hiatus, she regained the opportunity to join the women’s 10-metre air rifle event in the Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">March 2016, the Rio Olympic trials end, after a lapse of 8 years to obtain the women's 10-metre air rifle Olympic competition eligibility.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">Rio's Olympic trials ended in March 2016 and again qualified for the Women's 10m Air Rifle Olympic Games after eight years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2016年8月6日，在里约奥运会女子十米气步枪赛事中，杜丽以207环的成绩获得银牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">During the 10-meter air rifle competition at the Rio Olympics on August 6, 2016, Du Li won a silver medal with 207 points.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">August 6, 2016, in the Rio Olympic Games women's 10-metre air rifle competition, Dorrit with 207 ring results won the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">Dolly won a silver medal with 207 rings in the women's 10m air rifle event at the Rio Olympics on August 6, 2016.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.sl">
    <source>2016年8月12日，在里约奥运会女子50米步枪三种姿势比赛中，获得铜牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.ht">Won the Bronze Metal in the woman 50 meter rifle three positions in the Rio Olympic Games on Aug. 12, 2016</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.gg">August 12, 2016, in the Rio Olympic Games women's 50-metre rifle three posture competition, won the bronze medal.</translation>
    <translation system="110_peopledaily0812.henan.c356906-28822189_zh.c6">Bronze medal in the women's 50m rifle three-position competition at the Rio Olympics on August 12, 2016.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
