<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>乌鲁木齐规范旅游散客市场经营秩序旅行社必须与游客签合同</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">Urumqi standardizes FIT market order; travel agencies must sign contract with tourists</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">Urumqi standardize the business order of tourist market the travel agency must sign the contract with the visitor</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">Urumqi to regulate the operation of individual tourist market order travel agencies must sign a contract with tourists</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>眼下新疆已进入旅游旺季，为规范旅游散客市场经营秩序，乌鲁木齐市旅游执法支队联合市运管局执法支队昨天对散客市场存在的旅游用车不规范，旅行社与游客签订合同率低等问题进行查处。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">The peak season for travel in Xinjiang has arrived. For the purpose of standardizing the operating order of the FIT (Free Independent Traveler) market, the Urumqi tourism enforcement detachment joined forces with the City Transportation Authority enforcement detachment yesterday to investigate issues that exist in the FIT market such as non-compliant use of vehicles for travel, and the low rate of signed contracts between travel agencies and tourists.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">At present, Xinjiang has entered the tourist season, in order to standardize the operation of the tourist market, the law enforcement detachment of the URUMQI Tourism Law Enforcement detachment and the Joint City Transport Administration Bureau yesterday was not standardized for the tourist vehicles existing in the bulk guest market, and the travel agency and the tourists signed the low contract rate.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">At present, Xinjiang has entered the tourist season, in order to regulate the order of the tourism retail market, the Urumqi City Tourism Law Enforcement Detachment of the joint City Administration of Transportation Law Enforcement Detachment yesterday on the retail market in the presence of non-standard tourist vehicles, travel agencies and tourists signed a contract with the low rate and other issues were investigated and dealt with.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>昨天早上八点，在凯宾斯基酒店周围停了约10辆满载游客的大巴车，这些车辆大多都是前往天池一日游的散客团。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">At 8 AM in the morning of the previous day, about 10 large buses filled with tourists are parked around the Kempinski Hotel. Most of these buses are carrying visitors heading to the one-day tour to Tianchi Lake.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">At eight o ' clock yesterday morning, about 10 buses filled with tourists were parked around the Kempinski hotel, most of them a Tianchi tour.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">About 10 buses full of tourists were parked around the Kempinski Hotel at eight o'clock yesterday morning, most of them for a day trip to the Tianchi.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“你好，我是乌鲁木齐市旅游局的，你们跟这个旅行社签合同了嘛？”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">“Hello, I am from the Urumqi Travel Bureau. Have you signed a contract with this travel agency?”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">"Hello, I am URUMQI tourism Bureau, you and this travel agency signed a contract?" ”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">Hello, I'm from Urumqi Tourism Bureau, have you signed a contract with this travel agency?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>乌鲁木齐市运管局执法支队工作人员余斌介绍：“异地旅游车还有班线车在乌鲁木齐市场经营旅游客运项目，没有从业资格。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">Yu Bin, a staff member of the enforcement section of the Urumqi Road Transportation Administration said: “Tour vehicles from outside the region or route buses are not qualified to participate in developing tourism transportation projects in the Urumqi market.”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">Urumqi Yun Management Bureau of Law Enforcement Detachment staff Yu Bin Introduction: "The long-distance coach also has the class line vehicle in Urumqi market to operate the traveling passenger transport project, does not have the profession qualifications." ”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">Urumqi transportation bureau law enforcement detachment staff Yu Bin said: "off-site coach and bus line in the Urumqi market operating tourism passenger transport projects, without qualifications."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“超范围经营对这个处罚三到十万的罚款，驾驶员没有从业资格证是2000元的罚款。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">“The penalty for operating beyond scope is a fine of RMB30,000-100,000. Drivers without a practitioner’s certificate is a fine of RMB2,000.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">"Ultra-wide operation on this penalty of three to 100,000 of the fine, the driver does not have the qualification certificate is a fine of $2000." ”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">"The penalty for operating beyond the limits is a fine of three to one hundred thousand dollars, and a fine of 2,000 yuan for a driver who does not have a license to practise."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据了解，此前乌鲁木齐市旅游执法部门已对西公园、红山等旅游散客集中的地方进行了检查。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">From our understanding, the Urumqi tourism law enforcement department is currently carrying out inspections to Xigongyuan, Hongshan, and other destinations frequented by independent tourists.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">It is understood that the Urumqi tourism law Enforcement Department has been to the West Park, Hongshan and other tourist scattered places in the center of the inspection.</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">It is understood that the city of Urumqi tourism law enforcement authorities have previously checked the West Park, Red Hill and other places where tourists are concentrated.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>综合两次的检查情况，乌鲁木齐市旅游执法支队副支队长马琪说：“第一是安全，第二是规范，旅游车辆无小事，一旦出问题都是群伤群死。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">After reviewing conclusions of the two inspections, Ma Qi, vice captain of the Urumqi tourism law enforcement detachment, said: “Safety is the priority, followed by legal compliance. These are extremely important for tourism vehicles, because once an accident happens, many would be injured or killed.”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">Comprehensive two inspection situation, URUMQI Tourism law enforcement Detachment deputy team leader Mackinaw said: "The first is security, the second is norms, tourism vehicles no small matter, once the problem is a group of injured group died." ”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">"The first is safety, the second is regulation, the tourist vehicle is no small matter, once something goes wrong is a mass casualty," said Maggie, deputy head of the tourism law enforcement branch in Urumqi.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“我们和运管联合持续的对市场进行检查，规范旅行社用车行为保证游客安全。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.ht">“We are working with the Road Transportation Administration Bureau to continuously monitor the market and regulate tourism vehicle usage, to ensure tourist safety.”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.gg">We and the operation of the joint ongoing inspection of the market, standardize travel agents to ensure the safety of tourists. ”</translation>
    <translation system="070_ifeng0812.news.49765978_0_zh.c6">"We are working with the management to continuously check the market and regulate the use of cars by travel agencies to ensure the safety of tourists," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
