<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>10日下午，中国旅游警察在莫斯科红场一亮相，就立刻引起了人们的注意，中国游客怀着惊喜纷纷挥手致意，当地人和外国游客不禁驻足回望。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">In the afternoon of the 10th, the Chinese tourist police appeared on the Red Square of Moscow, attracting the attention of the public. Surprised Chinese tourists waved at them while locals and other foreign tourists stopped by to take a look.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">On the afternoon of 10th, the Chinese tourist police in Moscow Red Square appeared, immediately attracted attention, Chinese tourists with a surprise waving greetings, locals and foreign tourists can not help but look back.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">On the afternoon of October 10, when the Chinese tourist police made an appearance in Moscow's Red Square, they immediately caught people's attention. Chinese tourists waved with surprise. Locals and foreign tourists couldn't help but stop and look back.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>当天，中国首支专业旅游警察队伍——海南省三亚市公安局旅游警察支队的成员来到莫斯科红场，和当地执勤的旅游警察交流学习。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">The first tourist police squad from Shanya Police Department, Hainan Province arrived the Red Square of Moscow for exchange with the local tourist police.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">The same day, China's first professional tourism police team-Hainan Province Sanya Public Security Bureau members of the Tourism police detachment came to Moscow Red Square, and the Local on-duty tourism police Exchange study.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">On the same day, members of the Tourism Police Detachment of the Sanya Municipal Public Security Bureau, China's first professional tourism police force, came to Moscow's Red Square to exchange learning with the local tourist police on duty.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>莫斯科旅游警察在红场、尼科利斯基步行街、古姆百货商场等地分成三个小组执勤巡逻，中国旅游警察一起跟岗学习，整个过程持续了一个多小时。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">The Moscow tourist police is divided into 3 teams to patrol destinations such as the Red Square, Nikolsky Boulevard, and GUM department store. The Chinese tourist police follow them along these patrols to learn about their tasks and duties. The entire process continued for more than an hour.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">Moscow tourism Police in Red Square, Nikoliski Pedestrian street, GU department store and other places into three groups on duty patrol, the Chinese tourism police together with the post study, the whole process lasted one hours.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">Moscow tourist police patrol three groups in Red Square, Nikoliski Pedestrian Street, Gum Department Store and other places. Chinese tourist police study together with the post, the whole process lasted more than an hour.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>女警官柳希涅今年20多岁，通晓英语和西班牙语，她去年刚加入旅游警察队伍。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">Female police officer Liu Xinie is in her 20s, and fluent in English and Spanish. She joined the tourism police force least year.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">Female police officer Liuchinie, more than 20 years old, is fluent in English and Spanish, and has just joined the tourist police force last year.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">Liuchigne, a female police officer in her 20s and fluent in English and Spanish, joined the tourist police force just last year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>他一路上仔细观察俄罗斯同行的一言一行，并不时地与她进行交流。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">Along the way, he carefully observed every word and act of his Russian travel mate and held conversations with her every now and then.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">He looked closely at the Russian peers ' deeds and deeds, and exchanged them with her.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">He carefully observed the words and actions of his Russian counterpart along the way and communicated with her from time to time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>当遇到西班牙游客前来咨询时，莫斯科旅游警察用流利的西班牙语为对方进行了耐心讲解，这给王冰留下深刻印象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">What impressed Wang Bing the most was that the Moscow peers was able to respond in fluent Spanish to the inquired Spanish tourists.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">When the Spanish tourists came to consult, the Moscow tourist police in fluent Spanish to the other side of the patient to explain, which impressed Wang Bing.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">When encountering Spanish tourists coming for advice, the Moscow tourist police gave each other a patient explanation in fluent Spanish, which impressed Wang Bing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>“莫斯科旅游警察每个人都掌握外语，有的还会两门以上，这对我们触动非常大。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">“Every member of the Moscow tourism police is able to speak a foreign language, sometimes two. We are very impressed by this.”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">"The Moscow travel police each master a foreign language, and some will be more than two, which is very touching for us." ”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">"The fact that everyone in the Moscow tourist police knows a foreign language and some of them have more than two is very touching," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>“海南作为国际旅游岛，正在逐步重视吸引国际游客，我们希望提高自身能力来匹配国际旅游岛的地位。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">“As an International Tourism Island, Hainan is gradually prioritizing its focus es on attracting overseas tourists. We hope to improve our potential to match the status of an International Tourism Island.”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">As an international tourist island, Hainan is paying more attention to attract international tourists, and we hope to improve our ability to match the status of the international Tourism Island. ”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">"As an international tourist island, Hainan is gradually paying attention to attracting international tourists. We hope to improve our ability to match the status of an international tourist island," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>当天在跟岗学习前，中国旅游警察还到莫斯科市旅游警察大队驻地与他们的俄罗斯同行进行交流。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">Before initiating the shadow learning session, the Chinese tourist police also had a dialog with their Russian compatriots at the Moscow tourist police base.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">The same day, before studying with the post, the Chinese tourist police also went to the Moscow Tourism Police Brigade to communicate with their Russian counterparts.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">On the same day, before studying with the post, the Chinese tourist police also went to the Moscow city tourist police brigade station to communicate with their Russian counterparts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>“我常常与中国旅游者打交道，看到他们来到俄罗斯旅游非常高兴。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">“I often talk with Chinese tourists, and I feel very happy to see them visiting Russia.”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">"I often deal with Chinese tourists and see that they are very happy to travel to Russia," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">"I often deal with Chinese tourists and I'm very happy to see them coming to Russia."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>“他们通常求助的问题是：路怎么走，某个纪念碑在哪里，怎么打出租，怎么回到旅馆。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">“The most frequently asked questions are: How do you get there? Where is such and such a monument? How do you hail a cab? How do I return to the hotel?”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">"The question they usually ask for is: How to walk, where a monument is, how to taxi, how to get back to the hotel." ”</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">"The questions they usually ask for help are: how to get there, where is a monument, how to get a taxi, how to get back to the hotel," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>莫斯科市旅游警察大队大队长雷萨科夫说，近年来莫斯科的城市环境和旅游氛围变得越来越好，对外国游客的吸引力日益增加。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">Lysakov, the Capitan of Tourist Policy said, Moscow has been attracting more foreign tourists in recent years thanks to the improving urban environment and tourism condition.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">Moscow Tourism Police Brigade Captain Resakov said that in recent years, Moscow's urban environment and tourism atmosphere has become better and more attractive to foreign tourists.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">Moscow's urban environment and tourist atmosphere have become more and more attractive to foreign tourists in recent years, said Rysakov, head of Moscow's tourist police brigade.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>为适应旅游发展需要，2014年7月成立旅游警察队伍，负责在各大景点巡逻保卫，帮助和疏导游客。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">To meet the needs of tourism development, a tourist police team has been established in July 2014. The team shall patrol major destinations to provide assistance to tourists and provide crowd control.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">In order to meet the needs of tourism development, the establishment of the tourism police team in July 2014, responsible for patrolling the major attractions to protect, help and divert tourists.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">In order to meet the needs of tourism development, a tourism police force was set up in July 2014 to patrol and defend major attractions and help and channel tourists.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>目前，所有莫斯科旅游警察都熟练掌握英语，部分还掌握西班牙语和德语。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">Currently, all Moscow tourism police officers are fluent English speakers; some have even mastered Spanish and German.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">At present, all the Moscow tourist police are proficient in English, and partly in Spanish and German.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">Currently, all Moscow tourist police officers are fluent in English, and some also have Spanish and German.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>警察大队根据外语水平将他们分成9个小组，每周上2次课，学习自卫招式、法律法规和外语。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">Police headquarters divided them into nine teams according to their language skills. They attended two classes per week, and learned self-defense, the law, and foreign languages.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">According to the foreign language level, the police brigade divided them into 9 groups, 2 times a week to learn self-defense moves, laws and regulations and foreign languages.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">The police brigade divided them into nine groups, based on their foreign language level, and attended classes twice a week to learn self-defense techniques, laws and regulations and foreign languages.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>“目前有两名旅游警察开始学习汉语，已经说得不错了，我们还要继续提高他们的汉语水平，”雷萨科夫说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">“Currently, two tourism police officers have begun to learn Chinese, and are quite good at it. We still have to continue to raise their Chinese language standards,” said Lysakov.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">"There are two of tourist police who are starting to learn Chinese, and we have to continue to improve their Chinese," Resakov said.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">"At the moment there are two tourist police officers who are starting to learn Chinese and are already speaking well, and we're going to continue to improve their Chinese," Reysakov said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>雷萨科夫告诉记者，莫斯科旅游警察自组建以来，已经积累了一定的经验，希望能对三亚同行有所启发。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">lysakov told the reporter that since its establishment, the Moscow tourism police form has gained a certain degree of experience that may be useful for fellow police officers at Sanya.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">Resakov told reporters, the Moscow tourist Police since the formation, has accumulated a certain experience, hope to Sanya peer inspiration.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">Rysakov told reporters that since its establishment, the Moscow Tourism Police has accumulated some experience, hoping to inspire their counterparts in Sanya.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>他认为，俄中两国警察部门合作将提升本国公民到对方国家旅游的安全感。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">He believes that collaboration of Russian and Chinese police departments will help improve the sense of safety of citizens visiting the other country as tourists.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">He believed that the cooperation between the two countries ' police departments would enhance the security of their citizens to travel to each other's country.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">He believes that cooperation between the police departments of Russia and China will enhance the sense of security for their citizens to travel to each other's countries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.sl">
    <source>“莫斯科旅游警察的人员招录、警务模式、装备配备，以及与游客的良好互动给我们带来了很多启发，”陈晓昆说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.ht">“The staff recruitment, policing model and equipment of the Moscow tourism police, as well as the positive interaction with tourists have inspired us significantly,” said Chen Xiaokun.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.gg">"The staff recruitment, police mode, equipment and good interaction with tourists have brought us a lot of inspiration," Chen Xiaoqun said.</translation>
    <translation system="051_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnai9992792_zh.c6">"The recruitment of personnel, policing model, equipment and good interaction with tourists of the Moscow tourism police have given us a lot of inspiration," Chen said.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
