<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰自行车手卡尔姆·斯金纳夺得自行车金牌后载誉而归</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Scottish cyclist Callum Skinner returns in glory after clinching gold in cycling</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Scottish cyclist 卡尔姆·斯 Skinner wins his bicycle gold medal</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Scottish cyclist Callum Skinner returns with fame after winning cycling gold</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>苏格兰自行车手卡尔姆·斯金纳昨晚在里约自行车赛场男子团体竞速赛帮助英国三人组继2012年伦敦奥运会之后成功卫冕奥运会金牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Last night at the Rio Olympic Velodrome, the Scottish cyclist Callum Skinner helped the UK 3-men team successfully defend their Olympic gold medal in the men’s team sprint that they had achieved during the 2012 London Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">卡尔姆·斯 Skinner, a Scottish cyclist, last night at the Rio cycling Men's group race helped the trio to defend the Olympic gold medal after the 2012 London Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Scottish cyclist Callum Skinner last night helped the British trio successfully defend their Olympic gold medal following the 2012 London Games in the men's team race at the Rio Cycling Stadium.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>这位23岁的格拉斯哥自行车手代替了他的苏格兰同胞——克里斯·霍伊爵士，成为了队伍的中坚。当年轻的斯金纳击败夺冠热门新西兰队并载誉而归时，就连这位传奇自行车手也为他感到骄傲。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">This 23-year-old cyclist from Glasgow replaced his fellow Scot - Sir Chris Hoy - and anchored the team. When young Skinner defeated the New Zealand team, the top title contender, and returned victorious, even this cycling legend was proud of him.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The 23-year-old Glasgow cyclist replaced his Scottish compatriot, Sir 克里斯·霍伊, as the backbone of the team. Even the legendary cyclist was proud of the young Skinner who defeated the New Zealand team and returned with honors.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The 23-year-old Glasgow cyclist replaced his fellow Scot, Sir Chris Hoy, as the centrepiece of the team, and even the legendary cyclist was proud of him when the young Skinner beat title favourite New Zealand and returned home with a reputation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>四年前，英国队一鸣惊人，而霍伊夺得了个人六块奥运会金牌中的第五块。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Four years ago, the UK team achieved astounding performance with Hoy receiving the fifth gold medal in his personal collection of six Olympic golds.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Four years ago, the British team blockbuster, and Hoy won a personal six Olympic gold medal in the fifth piece.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Four years ago, the British team made a splash, while Hoy won the fifth of the individual's six Olympic gold medals.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>英国队在三月伦敦的世界单车场地锦标赛上仅名列第六，霍伊自此退役。然后，英国队再创辉煌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">The UK team only placed sixth at the UCI Track Cycling World Championships held in London in March. Hoy retired after that. The UK team has since regained glory.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The British team ranked sixth in London's World Cycling Championships in March, and Hoy has since retired. Then, the British team to create brilliant.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Hoey retired after finishing sixth at the World Cycling Championships in London in March.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>在北京奥运会到伦敦奥运会期间，英国队的问题在于换掉了“第一圈专家”杰米·斯塔夫。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Between the Beijing Olympic Games and the London Olympic Games, the problem with the Great Britain team was in replacing Jamie Staff, the “first lap expert”.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">During the Beijing Olympics to the London Olympics, the British team's problem was to replace the "first circle of Experts" 杰米·斯塔夫.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The problem for the British team between the Beijing and London Games was to replace "first lap expert" Jamie Staff.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>车队正是在辛德斯出现时才这么做的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">The motorcade started doing so when Hinds appeared.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">That's what the team did when be appeared.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The team did just that when Sinders showed up.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>霍伊的退役也留下了一个空白，而奇恩·伊玛迪和马特·克兰普顿都想来填补这个空白。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Hoy’s retirement also left a vacuum which Kian Emadi and Matt Crampton would like to fill.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Hoy's retirement also left a blank, and 奇恩·伊玛迪 and 马特·克兰普顿 all wanted to fill the void.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Hoy's retirement also left a void that Chin Emadi and Matt Clapton both wanted to fill.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>在看到斯金纳的潜力后，英国男队教练组坚持让他入选国家队，而斯金纳最终也不负众望。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">After witnessing Skinner’s potential, the coach of the men’s team of the UK insisted upon making him a part of the national team. Skinner also lived up to the expectations.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">After seeing the potential of Skinner, the British men's team insisted that he be selected for the national team, and Skinner was not in the end.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">After seeing Skinner's potential, the British men's coaching staff insisted that he be selected for the national team, and Skinner eventually lived up to expectations.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>斯金纳的搭档是四年前与霍伊一同夺得金牌的辛德斯和肯尼。三人在资格赛中刷新了奥运会纪录，但这一成绩在第一轮被新西兰队所超越。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Skinner’s partners are Hindes and Kenny who won the gold medal 4 years ago with Hoy. The 3 men broke the Olympic record in the qualifiers, but the achievement was surpassed in the first round by the New Zealand team.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Skinner's partner is be and Kenny, who won the gold medal with Hoy four years ago. The trio have refreshed the Olympic record in qualifying, but the result was overtaken by New Zealand in the first round.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Skinner's partner, Hindes and Kenny, who won gold with Hoy four years ago, set an Olympic record in qualifying but was overtaken by New Zealand in the first round.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>而这三位英国自行车赛最终击败对手，夺得金牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">These three English cyclists defeated their opponents ultimately and won the gold medal.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The three British Cycling championships eventually defeated their opponents and won the gold medal.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">And the three British cyclists eventually beat their rivals to win the gold medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>虽然辛德斯稍有落后，但肯尼为团队取得领先，斯金纳将这一领先优势保持到了最后。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Although Hinds is slightly behind, Kenny was able to help the team gain a lead. Skinner maintained the lead all the way till the end.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Although be is slightly behind, but Kenny is leading the team, Skinner has maintained this leading edge to the last.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">While Hindes was slightly behind, Kenny took the lead for the team and Skinner held that lead to the end.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>战略的改变是这一逆转的关键，辛德斯选择了较大的飞轮，因此速度较慢，而这让肯尼，尤其是斯金纳能够保持速度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">A change in strategy was key to this reversal. Hindes chose a larger flywheel so that he could slow down, thus enabling Kenny, and Skinner, in particular, to keep pace.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The change in strategy was the key to this reversal, and be chose a larger flywheel, so it was slower, which allowed Kenny, especially Skinner, to keep pace.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">A change in strategy was key to the turnaround, with Sinders opting for a larger flywheel and therefore slower, and that allowed Kenny, and Skinner in particular, to keep up the pace.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>霍伊以BBC评论员的身份观看了比赛。斯金纳、肯尼和辛德斯在登上领奖台时看到了他。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">When Hoey watched the game as the BBC commentator, Skinner, Kenny and Hindes saw him when ascending the podium.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Hoy watched the game as a BBC commentator. Skinner, Kenny and be saw him on the podium.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Hoey watched as a BBC commentator, and Skinner, Kenny and Hinders saw him on the podium.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>23岁的格拉斯哥自行车手斯金纳表示：“这让我受宠若惊。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">23-year-old Glasgow cyclist Skinner said, “I’m extremely flattered.”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">"I'm flattered," says Skinner, 23, a Glasgow cyclist. ”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">"I'm flattered," said Mr Skinner, a 23-year-old Glasgow cyclist.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>我只是尽我所能，让自己扬名立万而已。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">I’m doing what I can to establish my reputation.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">I just try my best to make my own fame.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">I'm just trying to do what I can to make a name for myself.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>我们在决赛中创造了奥运会纪录并且击败了世界冠军。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">We have set an Olympic record in the finals and defeated the world champions.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">We created the Olympic record in the final and defeated the world champion.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">We set an Olympic record in the final and beat the world champion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>这太令人难以置信了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">This is too unbelievable.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">It's unbelievable.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">This is unbelievable.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>没有什么比这场胜利更棒了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">There is nothing better than this victory.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Nothing is better than this victory.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">There's nothing better than this win.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>在2012年伦敦奥运会上与肯尼和霍伊夺得金牌后，辛德斯承认在起步不佳的情况下故意摔落在赛道上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">After Kenny and Hoy claimed gold medals at the 2012 London Olympic Games, Skinner admitted that he fell on the track on purpose because he started poorly.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">After winning gold medals with Kenny and Hoy at the 2012 London Olympics, be admits to falling deliberately on the track in a bad start.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">After winning gold medals with Kenny and Hoy at the 2012 London Olympics, Sinders admitted to falling deliberately onto the track after a poor start.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>后来，他撤回了这番评论，而英国队的对手们也无法上诉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">He later retracted these comments. The opponents of the UK team were unable to press any charges.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Later, he withdrew the comments, and British rivals were unable to appeal.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">He later withdrew the comment, while the British team's rivals were unable to appeal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>而这次的胜利没有任何此类问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">And this victory did not have any of these issues.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">This victory does not have any such problems.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">And there were no such problems with this victory.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>辛德斯表示：“这就像在伦敦，站台上都是英国的国旗。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Hindes said, “This is just like London. The podium was decked with Union Jacks.”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">"It's like London, the British flag on the platform," be says. ”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">"It's like being in London with the British flag all over the platform," Mr Sinders said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>我们在三个月前才刚刚组队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">We only began forming our team 3 months ago.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">We just got together three months ago.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">We only just formed a team three months ago.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>我们已经丢掉了很多世界冠军，所以能够卫冕奥运冠军太令人感到惊讶了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">We have already lost many world champions, so it is extremely surprising that we were able to defend this Olympic championship.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">We've lost a lot of world champions, so it's amazing to be able to defend the Olympic champions.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">We've lost a lot of world championships, so it's amazing to be able to defend an Olympic title.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>这对于在北京奥运会和伦敦奥运会上夺得10块场地自行车赛金牌中的7块的英国队而言只是一场比赛、一块金牌而已。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">To the UK team that has seized a total of 7 out of 10 gold medals in cycling at the Beijing Olympics and London Olympics, this is just another competition and another gold they won.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">It's just a game, a gold medal for the British team who won 7 of the 10 gold medals in the Beijing Olympics and the London Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">It's just one race, one gold medal for the British team that won seven of the 10 track cycling gold medals at the Beijing and London Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>如果这象征着过去五个月我们所取得进步，那么我们将在未来五天继续在自行车馆取得成功。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">If this symbolized the improvement we have gained over the last five months, then in the next five days, we will continue to achieve success in the velodrome.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">If this symbolizes the progress we have made over the past five months, we will continue to be successful at the bicycle museum in the next five days.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">If this symbolizes the progress we have made over the past five months, then we will continue to be successful in the Cycling Pavilion for the next five days.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>根据肯尼所展现的状态，他并非没有可能再现霍伊在一届奥运会上夺得三块金牌的壮举。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">According to the performance provided by Kenny, there is a still chance for him to win 3 golds in a single Olympics just as Hoy did previously.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">According to Kenny Dalglish, it is not impossible for him to recreate Hoy's feat of winning three gold medals at an Olympic Games.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Based on the form Kenny has shown, it's not impossible for him to recreate Hoy's feat of winning three gold medals at one Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>如果是这样的话，比霍伊年轻12岁并且同样在3月23日 （这一天似乎是英国体育界的神圣日子，史蒂夫·雷德格雷夫、莫·法拉和罗杰·班尼斯特也是在这一天出生的) 出生的肯尼将拥有6块金牌和1块银牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">If this is the case, Kenny, 12 years younger than Hoy, and born on the same day on March 23 (this day appears to be a sacred day for British sports as Steven Redgrave, Mo Farah and Roger Bannister were all born of the same day), will have six gold medals and one silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">If so, 12 years younger than Hoy and also on March 23 (a day that seems to be the holy day of British sports, 史蒂夫·雷德格雷夫, 莫·法拉 and Bannister were born on this day) Kenny will have 6 golds and 1 silver medals.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">If so, Kenny, who is 12 years younger than Hoy and also born on March 23, which seems to be a sacred day for British sport, when Steve Redgrave, Mo Farah and Roger Bannister were born, will have six gold medals and a silver medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>这一成绩与霍伊持平。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">This result equaled Hoy’s.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">This achievement is flat with Hoy.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The result was the same as Hoy's.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>肯尼接下来将出战于今天开始、为期三天的竞速赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Next, Kenny will take part in the 3-day sprint event which starts today.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Kenny is going to start the three-day race today.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Kenny is next in line for the three-day race, which starts today.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>这位28岁的博尔顿人表示：“我暂时会专注于这项比赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">This 28-year-old from Bolton said, “I will focus on this match for now.”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The 28-year-old Bolton said: "I will focus on this game for the time being."</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">"I'm going to focus on this game for the time being," said the 28-year-old Bolton man.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>团队赛始终是最棒的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Team competition is still the best.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Team games are always the best.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The team competition is always the best.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="34" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>你可以与队友一起赢得比赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">You can win this competition together with your teammate.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">You can win the game with your teammates.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">You can win games with your teammates.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="35" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>坦率地讲，一个人获胜有点孤独。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">To be honest, a one-man victory does seem a little lonely.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Frankly speaking, a person wins a little lonely.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Frankly speaking, it's a bit lonely for one person to win.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="36" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>辛德斯表示：“如果他能夺得另两块金牌，那么他应该会被授予爵士封号。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Hindes said, “If he can clinch the other two gold medals, he will be knighted.”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Be said: "If he can win another two gold medals, then he should be awarded the Jazz seal number." ”</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">"If he can win the other two gold medals, then he should be given a knighthood," Mr Sinders said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="37" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>这是当天唯一一场产生奖牌的比赛，但英国队收到了其他好消息。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">This is the only competition of the day where any medals could be won. However, the UK team received other good news.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">It was the only game to produce medals that day, but the British team received other good news.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">It was the only game of the day that produced a medal, but the British team received other good news.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="38" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>布拉德利·威金斯爵士、艾德·克兰西、史蒂文·伯克和欧文·杜尔以最快成绩晋级四人四公里团体追逐赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Sir Bradley Wiggins, Ed Clancy, Steven Burke, and Owain Doull successfully entered, with the fastest speeds, the four-men 4-kilometer team pursuit.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Sir Bradley, 艾德·克兰西, 史蒂文·伯克 and 欧文·杜尔 to the fastest score of four people four km group chase.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Sir Bradley Wiggins, Ed Clancy, Steven Burke and Owen Doyle advanced to the four-kilometre team pursuit with the fastest time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="39" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>他们的成绩是351.943。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Their score was 351.943.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Their grades were 351.943.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Their scores were 351.943.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="40" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>而2012年伦敦奥运会金牌获得者的世界纪录是351.659。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">For the 2012 London Olympics, the gold medalist established a world record of 351.659.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The world record for the 2012 London Olympic gold medalist was 351.659.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The world record for a gold medalist at the 2012 London Olympics is 351.659.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="41" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>第一轮和决赛 （晚上10点42分） 于今天第二比赛日举行，威金斯无疑将成为万众瞩目的焦点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Today as the second game day will witness the first round and the final ( 10:42pm) . Wiggins will no doubt be the focus in the field.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The first and final (10:42) in today's second match day, Wiggins will undoubtedly become the focus of the limelight.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The first round and final (10.42pm) take place on the second match day today and Wiggins will no doubt be in the limelight.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="42" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>昨天他在资格赛前与比赛官员发生了争执，当时比赛官员让他测量身高。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">He had an argument with a competition official during the qualifiers. The official had asked him to measure his height at that time.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Yesterday he had a dispute with the match officials before qualifying, when the match officials asked him to measure his height.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">He had an argument with match officials before qualifying yesterday when they asked him to measure his height.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="43" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>在将于明天结束的女子组比赛中，劳拉·特洛特、乔安娜·罗瑟尔·尚德、埃莉诺·巴克和来自米尔盖的凯特·阿奇博尔德以新的世界纪录413.260晋级。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">Laura Trott, Joanna Rowsell-Shand, Elinor Barker, and  Katie Archibald from Milngavie advanced in the women’s team event which will conclude tomorrow after setting a new world record of 413.260.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">劳拉·特洛特, 乔安娜·罗瑟尔·尚德, Eleanor 诺·巴克 and 凯特·阿奇博尔德 from Milngavie in a new world record 413.260 for the women's team, which will end tomorrow.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">Laura Trott, Joanna Rother-Shande, Eleanor Barker and Kate Archibald from Millgate advanced with a new world record of 413.260 in the women's competition, which ends tomorrow.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="44" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>英国队依靠强大的其场地自行车队在奥运会中期占据主动并且囊获多枚奖牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">The British team leveraged the dominance of its strong track cycling team in the middle of the Olympics, and bagged numerous medals.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The British team relied on a strong field bike team to take the initiative in the middle of the Olympic Games and get many medals.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">The British team relied on a strong track cycling team to take the lead in the middle of the Olympics and win a number of medals.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="45" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>在北京和伦敦奥运会上展现其绝对统治地位后，英国自行车队在前往里约的过程中让大家略感失望。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">After the dominating wins during the Beijing and London Olympics, the performance of British bicycle team was a little bit disappointing in their journey toward the Rio Olympic.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">The British Cycling team was a little disappointed when they went to Rio to show their absolute dominance in the Beijing and London Games.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">After showing its absolute dominance at the Beijing and London Olympics, the British cycling team was slightly disappointed on their way to Rio.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="46" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>期间发生了许多波折，包括四月技术总监肖恩·萨顿因性别歧视和欺凌指控而辞职以及霍伊、维多利亚·彭德尔顿等传奇人物的退役。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">A series of ups and downs occurred during this period, including the resignation of technical director Shane Sutton because of allegations of sexual discrimination and bullying, as well as the retirement of Hoy, Victoria Pendleton, and other legendary personalities.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">Many setbacks occurred during the period, including the resignation of April technical director 肖恩·萨顿 for sex discrimination and bullying, and the retirement of legendary figures such as Hoy and 维多利亚·彭德尔顿.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">There were many ups and downs during the period, including the resignation of technical director Sean Sutton in April over sexism and bullying allegations and the retirement of legends such as Hoy and Victoria Pendleton.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="47" doc-id="128_scotsman.82409_en.sl">
    <source>但自行车馆的首个比赛夜足以证明英国队将再度上演关键时刻达到巅峰状态的传奇。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.ht">However, the first evening of the competition at the bicycle stop demonstrated that the UK team will once again reach its legendary peak at the critical moment.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.gg">But the first game of the Bicycle Pavilion was enough to show that the British team will once again play a key moment to reach the pinnacle of the legend.</translation>
    <translation system="128_scotsman.82409_en.c6">But the first night at the Bicycle Pavilion is a testament to the fact that the British team will once again reach the pinnacle of form at the crucial moment.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
