<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>英国必须传递奥林匹克精神并且对希思罗机场进行扩建</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">Britain must channel the Olympic spirit and expand Heathrow Airport</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Britain must deliver Olympic spirit and expand Heathrow Airport</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">Britain must pass on the Olympic spirit and expand Heathrow</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>希思罗也将为我们的社区、伦敦以及整个国家带来活力与繁荣。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">Heathrow will also bring vitality and prosperity to our community, to London and to the whole country.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Heathrow will also bring dynamism and prosperity to our communities, London and the country as a whole.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">Heathrow will also bring energy and prosperity to our communities, London and the country as a whole.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>对于我而言，这是希思罗的魅力所在，正如在2012年伦敦奥运会时，我们竭尽全力保证我们的国家和地区能够从这些赛事中获益。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">To me personally, this is where the charms of Heathrow lies. During the 2012 London Olympics, we did our best to ensure that our country and local district are able to benefit from these competitions.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">For me, this is Heathrow's charm, just as we did our best to ensure that our country and region benefited from these events at the 2012 London Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">For me, that's the appeal of Heathrow, just as at the 2012 London Olympics we did everything we could to ensure our country and region could benefit from those events.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>奥运会使斯特拉特福德和东区受益匪浅。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">The Olympic Games benefited Stratford Upon Avon and the eastern regions significantly.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">The Olympics have benefited Stratford and the east side.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">The Olympics have benefited Stratford and the East End.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>并且我们将通过为希思罗附近的当地民众和企业创造机会再次造福这一地区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">In addition, we can benefit this region again by creating opportunities for local residents and enterprises near Heathrow.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">And we will create opportunities for the local people and businesses around Heathrow to benefit the region again.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">And we will once again benefit the region by creating opportunities for local people and businesses around Heathrow.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>仅就我们的本地社区而言，我们将创造10,000个新学徒岗位、40,000个新工作岗位并且让机场周围的年轻人摆脱失业困境。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">For just our local community, we will create 10,000 openings for apprentices and 40,000 new job opportunities, resolving the issue of unemployment for youths around the airport.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">As far as our local community is concerned, we will create 10,000 new apprenticeships, 40,000 new jobs and get the young people around the airport out of the unemployment trap.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">In our local communities alone, we will create 10,000 new apprenticeships, 40,000 new jobs and lift young people out of unemployment around the airport.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>正如2012年伦敦奥运会前，有些人认为希思罗的扩建工程过于庞大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">As was the case before the 2012 London Olympic Games, some people felt that the Heathrow expansion project was too big.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Just before the 2012 London Olympics, some people thought Heathrow's expansion was too big.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">As before the 2012 London Olympics, some people thought Heathrow's expansion was too big.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>我被告知英国将无法为奥运会做好准备，并且我们将在全世界面前丢脸。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">I've been told that the UK will not be able to prepare properly for the Olympics and that we will be shaming ourselves before the entire world.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">I was told that Britain would not be ready for the Olympics and that we would lose face all over the world.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">I was told that Britain would not be ready for the Olympics and that we would be humiliated in front of the whole world.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>质疑者对于2012年奥运会的怀疑是错误的，并且他们对于希思罗项目的怀疑也将被证明是错误的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">The doubts held by skeptics regarding the 2012 Olympics were misplaced. Also, their doubts regarding the Heathrow project will ultimate prove to be false.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Sceptics are wrong about the 2012 Olympics, and their suspicions of Heathrow will prove wrong.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">The doubters were wrong about the 2012 Olympics, and their doubts about the Heathrow project will be proved wrong.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>虽然总是会出现需要克服的障碍，但希思罗正在解决每一个所面临的问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">Although there are obstacles that must be overcome, Heathrow is addressing every problem that it faces.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">While there will always be hurdles to overcome, Heathrow is tackling every problem it faces.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">While there will always be obstacles to overcome, Heathrow is working through every one of the problems it faces.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>如同奥运会，希思罗是为大多数人而非少数人所开展的基础设施项目。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">Just like the Olympics, Heathrow is a infrastructure project initiated for the majority of the people, and not the minority.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Like the Olympics, Heathrow is a infrastructure project for most people rather than a few.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">Like the Olympics, Heathrow is an infrastructure project for the many, not the few.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>扩建工程将创造多达18万个新工作岗位、带来2110亿英镑的经济增长，为机场周围和全英国留下一笔技术与就业财富。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">The expansion project will create up to 180,000 new jobs, result in economic growth amounting to GBP211 billion, and provide a wealth of technology and employment opportunities to the areas around the airport and the entire UK.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">The expansion will create up to 180,000 new jobs and bring in 211 billion of pounds of economic growth, leaving a technology and employment fortune around the airport and across the UK.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">The expansion will create up to 180,000 new jobs and generate £211bn in economic growth, leaving a wealth of technology and jobs around the airport and across the UK.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>我们有一支出色的希思罗项目团队。该团队已准时并且在预算范围内完成了110亿英镑的基础设施投资项目，包括连续五年当选全球最佳机场航站楼的T5航站楼和位于全球最繁忙的两条跑道之间的T2航站楼。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">We have an outstanding Heathrow project team. The has completed this infrastructure investment project worth 11.0 billion pounds within schedule and budget. The project include completion of the T5 terminal that was ranked as the world’s best airport terminal for five consecutive years, and the T2 terminal located between the two of the world’s busiest runways.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">We have an excellent Heathrow project team. The team has completed a 11 billion-pound infrastructure investment project on time and within budget, including the T5 terminal, which has been elected to the world's best airport terminal for five consecutive years, and the T2 terminal between the two busiest runways in the world.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">We have an excellent Heathrow project team that has completed £11bn of infrastructure investment projects on time and within budget, including Terminal T5, which has been voted the best airport terminal in the world for five years in a row, and Terminal T2, which is located between two of the world's busiest runways.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>现在，他们准备以160亿英镑的私人投资建设第三条跑道。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">At this time, they are prepared to privately invest GBP16 billion to build the third runway.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Now they are preparing to build a third runway with a private investment of £ 16 billion.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">Now they are preparing to build a third runway with £16bn of private investment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>英国成功地举办了2012年伦敦奥运会，而我相信希思罗机场扩建项目也将取得巨大的成功。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">The UK successfully hosted the 2012 London Olympics, and I believe that the project to expand the Heathrow Airport will achieve resounding success as well.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Britain successfully hosted the 2012 London Olympics, and I believe the Heathrow Airport expansion will be a great success.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">The UK successfully hosted the 2012 London Olympics, and I am confident that the Heathrow expansion project will also be a huge success.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>现在正是我们传递奥林匹克精神并扩建希思罗机场的好时机，这样我们就能为我们的未来保驾护航并且创造一笔使全英国感到骄傲的技术与就业财富。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">This is a good time for us to convey the Olympic spirit and expand Heathrow Airport. This will allow us to safeguard our future and generate a wealth of technology and employment opportunities that the entirety of Britain can be proud of.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Now is the time for us to deliver the Olympic spirit and expand Heathrow, so that we can escort our future and create a wealth of technology and employment that prides the whole of Britain.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">Now is a good time for us to spread the Olympic spirit and expand Heathrow so that we can protect our future and create a wealth of technology and jobs that the UK can be proud of.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="118_telegraph.294676_en.sl">
    <source>保罗·戴顿勋爵是希思罗机场董事会主席和前英国财政部商务参赞</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.ht">Lord Paul Deighton is the chairperson of Heathrow Airport and former Commercial Secretary to HM Treasury of the UK.</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.gg">Lord 保罗·戴顿 is the chairman of the Heathrow Airport board and the former British Treasury commercial counsellor</translation>
    <translation system="118_telegraph.294676_en.c6">Lord Paul Dutton is chairman of the board of directors at Heathrow Airport and a former commercial counsellor to the UK Treasury</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
