<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>青岛是全国第12个也是山东省首个排污权有偿使用和交易试点城市。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Qingdao is the 12th city in the nation and the first in Shandong Province to implement the pilot program for paying for the use and trading of emissions rights.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Qingdao is the 12th country in Shandong Province is also the first to discharge the right to use and trade pilot city.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Qingdao is the 12th in China and the first pilot city of paid use and trading of emission rights in Shandong Province.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>11日,多家企业分别来到青岛市排污权交易中心提交排污权申购,申购受理后将缴纳有偿使用费。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">On the 11th, many companies submitted emission rights purchase applications at the Qingdao Emissions Trading Center. Those who successfully applied for the rights will start paying a usage fee.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">11th, a number of enterprises respectively came to Qingdao emissions Trading Center to submit the right to apply for discharge, the purchase will be paid after the payment of fees.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">11, a number of enterprises came to Qingdao Municipal Emission Trading Center to submit applications for the purchase of emission rights, purchase acceptance will pay a fee.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>此次即将完成的交易首单也预示着青岛排污权交易试点工作正式拉开序幕,这也将是全省排污权交易首单和全国城市级排污权交易首单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">The imminent completion of this first trade also marks the official launch of the pilot program for the trading of emission rights in Qingdao. This will also be the first emission rights trade in the Province as well as the first city-level  emission rights trade in the nation.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">This will be completed the first single transaction is also indicative of Qingdao emissions trading pilot work officially kicked off, which would also be the first single emissions trading in the province and the national city-level emissions trading first.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">The transaction is about to complete the first single also indicates that Qingdao emissions trading pilot work officially kicked off, which will be the province's emissions trading first single and the first nationwide city-level emissions trading.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>11日上午,青岛双桃精细化工(集团)有限公司总经理赵秀平来到青岛市排污权交易中心提交排污权申购。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">In the morning of the 11th, Zhao Xiuping, general manager of Qingdao Shuangtao Jingxi Chemical Industry (Group) came to the Qingdao City Emissions Trading Center to submit an application to purchase emission rights.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">11th morning, Qingdao Double Peach Fine Chemicals (Group) Co., Ltd. General manager Zhooping came to the Qingdao Emission Trading Center to submit the right to discharge the purchase.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">On the morning of November 11, Zhao Xiuping, general manager of Qingdao Shuangtao Fine Chemical Industry (Group) Co., Ltd. came to Qingdao Emission Trading Center to submit the application for emission rights.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>该企业位于青岛老城区的厂区去年年底全面停产,环保搬迁至平度的新厂区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">This corporation, situated in the factory area of Old Town of Qingdao, stopped its production lines at the end of last year, and was moved, using environment-friendly means, to a new plant area in Pingdu.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">The company is located in the old town of Qingdao factory last year, the end of a comprehensive shutdown, environmental relocation to the Pingdu of the plant.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">The enterprise is located in the old city of Qingdao plant at the end of last year to stop production, environmental protection moved to the new plant in Pingdu.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>赵秀平提交了申请表、建设项目环境影响报告书等材料后,青岛市排污权储备和交易服务中心开始对申请材料进行初审。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Zhao Xiuping submitted the application form, environmental impact report, and other materials for the construction project. The Qingdao City Emissions Reserve and Trading Service Center began preliminary reviews of the application materials.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Zhooping submitted the application form, the construction project environmental impact report, and other materials, Qingdao emission rights reserve and trading service Center began to the application materials first-instance.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">After Zhao Xiuping submitted the application form, the environmental impact statement of the construction project and other materials, the Qingdao Municipal Emission Right Reserve and Trading Service Center began the preliminary examination of the application materials.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>根据青岛市物价、财政等部门确定的征收标准,目前预估算的初始排污权使用费约为64.12万元,工作人员将在7个工作日内完成核定。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">According to the collection criteria determined by Qingdao’s pricing, finance and other departments, the  initial usage fee for emissions rights is currently estimated at approximately RMB641,200. Staff will complete checking and ratification within seven working days.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">According to the Qingdao city price, finance and other departments to determine the collection criteria, the current estimated initial sewage right to use about 641,200 yuan, staff will be within 7 working days to complete the approved.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">According to Qingdao prices, finance and other departments to determine the collection standards, the current estimated initial sewage right to use about 644.12 million yuan, staff will be completed within seven working days to verify.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>此次即将完成的交易首单也预示着青岛排污权交易试点工作正式拉开序幕,也将是全省排污权交易首单和全国城市级排污权交易首单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">The first transaction, which will be completed soon, also marks the formal initiation of the Qingdao Emissions Trading Pilot Project. This will also be the first emissions trading in the province and the first city-level emissions trading in the entire country.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">This will be completed the first single transaction is also indicative of Qingdao emissions trading pilot work officially kicked off, will also be the province's emissions trading first single and national city-level emissions trading first.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">The transaction is about to complete the first single also indicates that Qingdao emission trading pilot work officially kicked off, will also be the province's emission trading first single and the first national city-level emissions trading.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>赵秀平说,目前企业环保已投资达4个亿,表面上数额巨大,但对企业经营管理理念、社会效益都有很大影响,对企业创新管理也开辟了空间。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Zhao Xiuping said, “Presently, enterprises have invested RMB400 million in environmental protection. On the surface, this seems an enormous amount, but it has a profound impact on both the operational and management philosophy of enterprises as well as social benefit, and has provided room for innovative management by enterprises.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Zhooping said that the current enterprise environmental protection has been invested up to 400 million, the surface amount is huge, but the enterprise management philosophy, social benefits have a great impact on enterprise innovation management also opened up space.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Zhao Xiuping said: At present, enterprises have invested 400 million in environmental protection, a huge amount on the surface, but the concept of business management, social benefits have a great impact on the enterprise innovation and management has also opened up space.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>当天,青岛四方新诚志卓客车配件有限公司也来为年产4200件高铁及动车组内饰配件项目申购排污权。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">On that day, Qingdao Sifang Xincheng Zhizhuo Coach Components Co., Ltd. also came to apply for and purchase emission rights for the project to produce 4,200 pieces of interior accessories and components for high speed train and electric multiple units.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">The same day, Qingdao Sifang Xin Zhi Zhuo passenger car parts Co., Ltd. also to the annual output of 4,200 pieces of high-speed rail and EMU interior accessories project requisition pollution rights.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">On the same day, Qingdao Sifang Xinchengzhizhuo Bus Accessories Co., Ltd. has also come to the annual output of 4,200 high-speed rail and EMU interior accessories projects to purchase emission rights.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>该项目属于机械加工企业,申请的初始排污权为化学需氧量(COD)0.514吨/年、氨氮(NOX)0.052吨/年。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">This project is initiated by a mechanical processing company. The company is applying for an initial emissions as chemical oxygen demand (COD) of 0.514 tons/year and ammonia nitrogen (NOX) of 0.052 tons/year.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">The project is a mechanical processing enterprise, the initial discharge right of the application for chemical oxygen demand (COD) of 0.514 tons/year, ammonia nitrogen (NOX) 0.052 tons/year.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">The project belongs to the mechanical processing enterprises, the application for the initial emission of chemical oxygen demand (COD) 0.514 tons / year, ammonia nitrogen (NOX) 0.052 tons / year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>大气污染物排污权有偿使用和交易为全市电力、热力生产供应重点工业企业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Paying for the use and trading of air pollutant emissions rights is for the city’s key power and heat production and supply industrial enterprises.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">The pollutant emission right of air pollutants is paid use and transaction is the key industrial enterprise of power supply and thermal production.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Air pollutant emission rights paid use and trade for the city's electricity, thermal production and supply of key industrial enterprises.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2016年1月1日前已取得环评的现有排污单位,暂不征收有偿使用费。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Existing polluting companies that have received a bad rating prior to January 1, 2016 will be temporarily exempt from the usage fee.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Prior to January 1, 2016, the existing sewage disposal unit of EIA has not been levied for a fee.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Existing units that have obtained an EIA prior to January 1, 2016, will not be charged a toll fee for the time being.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“有偿获得排污权并不等于获得了违法排污的权力,并不能随意地排放污染物。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">“Paying for emission rights does not mean gaining the right to generate illegal emissions. The payer may not emit waste as they like.”</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">"The right to obtain pollution from the sewage is not equal to the right to the illegal discharge of pollutants. ”</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">"Paid access to emission permits is not the same as access to the power of illegal discharge of pollutants, and can not be arbitrarily discharged pollutants."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>青岛市环保局副局长汉红燕介绍,如果违法排污、超标排污仍然要按照相关的法规予以处罚,不可能允许违法企业通过购买排污权的方式来规避处罚。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Deputy Director Han Hongyan of the Qingdao Environmental Protection Bureau explained that illegal emissions or emissions that exceed specified limits shall be subject to penalties according to relevant laws. Violating companies will not be able to purchase emission rights to avoid punishments.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Qingdao Environmental Protection Bureau deputy director of the Han Red Yan introduced, if the illegal discharge, exceeding the sewage still should be punished according to the relevant regulations, it is impossible to allow illegal enterprises through the purchase of pollution right way to avoid punishment.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Han Hongyan, deputy director of Qingdao Municipal Environmental Protection Bureau, said that if illegal discharge, excessive discharge should still be punished in accordance with the relevant regulations, it is impossible to allow illegal enterprises through the purchase of pollution rights to avoid punishment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>也就是说,通过法律手段严厉打击环境违法行为,严惩企业的超标排污行为,从而保护环境,保障公众健康。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">In another word, we should fight against environmental offense and  excessive discharge by enterprises with serious legal action to protect our environment and public health.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">In other words, by means of legal measures to crack down on environmental violations, severely punish the excessive discharge of enterprises, thereby protecting the environment and safeguarding public health.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">In other words, through legal means to crack down on environmental violations, and severely punish enterprises for excessive pollution, so as to protect the environment and protect public health.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>现在企业为了自身的利益,提高了治污的积极性,珍惜有限的排污权,减少了污染物排放。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Enterprises are now more enthusiastic about pollution treatment because of their own interests; limited emission rights are valued, and emission of pollutants has decreased.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Now enterprises in order to their own interests, improve the enthusiasm of pollution control, cherish the limited emission rights, reduce pollutant emissions.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Now enterprises for their own interests, improve the enthusiasm of pollution control, cherish the limited emission rights, reducing the emission of pollutants.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>有了经济利益的驱动,减少污染物的排放就从政府的强制行为变为企业自觉的市场行为,从而真正达到保护环境、保护自然、保障公众健康的目的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Driven by economic interest, reducing emission of pollutants will shift from mandatory acts imposed by the government to conscious corporate market behavior. Thus, the goal of protecting the environment and nature as well as ensuring public health will be achieved.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">With the drive of economic benefits, reducing pollutant emissions from the government's compulsory behavior into the enterprise conscious market behavior, so as to really achieve the protection of the environment, protection of nature, the purpose of safeguarding public health.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Driven by the economic benefits, reducing the emission of pollutants will change from the government's compulsory behavior to the enterprise's conscious market behavior, so as to truly achieve the goal of protecting the environment, protecting nature and protecting public health.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>排污权又称“排放权”,是排放污染物的权利,指排放者在政府分配的额度内,依法享有的向环境排放污染物的权利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">The right to discharge pollutants, or “emission rights”, are a right to emit pollutants, i.e., polluters, within a quota allocated by the government, enjoy the right to discharge pollutants into the environment according to the law.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">The right to discharge is also called "emission right", which is the right to emit pollutants, which is the right to emit pollutants to the environment within the limits allocated by the Government.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Emission right, also known as "emission right", is the right to discharge pollutants, which refers to the right of the emitter to discharge pollutants into the environment within the quota allocated by the government according to law.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这种权利实质上是排污者对环境容量资源占有、使用和收益的权利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">This right is in essence, the right polluters have on the ownership, use and profit of existing resources in the environment.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">In essence, this right is the right of polluters to occupy, use and benefit the environmental capacity resources.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">This right is essentially the right of the polluter to possess, use and benefit from the environmental capacity resources.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>下一步,在污染物排放总量不超过允许排放量的前提下,内部各污染源之间通过货币交换的方式相互调剂排污量。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">In the next step, under the pretext of keeping total emissions within the allowable emission volume, various internal sources of pollution shall use currency exchange to modulate emissions.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Next, under the premise that the total pollutant emissions do not exceed allowable emissions, the internal pollution sources are exchanged with each other by means of currency exchange.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Next, under the premise that the total amount of pollutants discharged does not exceed the permitted amount, the amount of pollutants discharged is adjusted by means of currency exchange between the internal sources of pollution.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>排污权交易自1968年由美国经济学家戴尔斯提出以来,20世纪70年代开始美国将其应用于大气及河流污染源的管理。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Emissions trading was first proposed by the US economist Dales in 1968. In the 1970s, the US made use of this to manage sources of atmospheric and river pollution.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">Emissions trading since 1968 by American economist Dales, the United States in the 1970s began to apply it to the management of atmospheric and river pollution sources.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">Since the emission trading was put forward by American economist Dales in 1968, it has been applied to the management of air and river pollution sources in the United States since the 1970s.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.sl">
    <source>我国从2007年开始进行试点,目前已有浙江、江苏等14个省(区、市)在全面推行。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.ht">Pilot programs were initiated since 2007. Currently, the program is being fully implemented at Zhejiang, Jiangsu, and other 14 provinces (in districts and cities).</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.gg">China since 2007 to carry out pilot, now has Zhejiang, Jiangsu and other 14 provinces (regions, municipalities) in full implementation.</translation>
    <translation system="103_ifeng0812.news.49764500_0_zh.c6">China began to carry out pilot projects in 2007, and 14 provinces (autonomous regions and municipalities), including Zhejiang and Jiangsu, have been fully implemented.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
