<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“一定要把从国内学到的才艺在俄罗斯发扬开来”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">" We must promote the skills learned at home across Russia"</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">"Be sure to learn from the domestic talent in Russia to develop."</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">"Make sure the talent you learn from home is carried forward in Russia."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>当地时间12日，莫斯科华侨华人联合会主席黄静在看到中新网记者时激动的说道。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">On the 12th day, local time, Huang Jing, the chairperson of the Moscow Chinese Community Chinese Alliance Committee excitedly said these lines when meeting the China News Service reporter.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">12th local time, the chairman of the Moscow Overseas Chinese Federation Huang in the see Beijing reporter excitedly said.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">12 local time, Huang Jing, president of the Moscow Overseas Chinese Federation, said excitedly when he saw a reporter from China News.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>前不久，她在国内参加了由中国国务院侨务办公室主办、暨南大学承办的“海外华人文化社团中华才艺(书法、绘画)培训班”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">She recently attended a " Traditional Art(Calligraphy and Painting) Training for Overseas Chinese Art Communities" hosted by Overseas Chinese Affairs Office of the State Council.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">Not long ago, she participated in the National Chinese Affairs Office of the State Council of China, Jinan University sponsored by the "Overseas Chinese Cultural Community Chinese talent (calligraphy, painting) training courses."</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">Not long ago, she attended a training course on Chinese Talents (Calligraphy, Painting) organized by the Overseas Chinese Affairs Office of the State Council of China and sponsored by Jinan University.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刚刚参加培训班时，自己对于书画完全不知道从哪里下手，结果在培训班结束后，已经能画出和写出自己的作品。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">When I first joined the workshop, I didn’t know where to begin as far as calligraphy and painting was concerned. After the course ended, I was already able to paint and write my own works.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">Just take part in the training class, I do not know the painting from where to start, the result in the course of the end, already can draw and write their own works.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">Just attended the training course, their painting and calligraphy do not know where to start, the results at the end of the training course, has been able to draw and write their own work.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>自己回莫斯科后，一定要用所学到的知识和技能，为中华文化的传播和弘扬作出自己的贡献。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">Upon returning to Moscow, I shall use my acquired knowledge and skills in my contributions toward the spread and advocation of Chinese culture.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">When they return to Moscow, they must use the knowledge and skills they have learned to make their own contribution to the spread and promotion of Chinese culture.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">When you return to Moscow, you must use the knowledge and skills you have learned to make your own contribution to the dissemination and promotion of Chinese culture.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>同时参加这一培训班的俄罗斯中华文化促进会秘书长那延伟也有相同感觉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">Na Yanwei, the secretary general of the Russian Chinese Culture Promotion Society, participated in this training class and felt the same.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">Nayanwe, the Secretary-General of the Russian Association for the promotion of Chinese culture, also has the same feeling.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">Nayanwei, secretary-general of the Association for the Promotion of Chinese Culture in Russia, who also attended the course, felt the same way.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她说，自己在培训班老师的帮助下进步非常大，同时也感受到了作为“中华文化海外传播者”的重任。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">She said she achieved significant improvements with the coach’s help in the training class, and experienced the responsibilities of becoming an “overseas seed for spreading Chinese culture”.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">She said that she has made great progress with the help of the teachers in the training course, and also felt the heavy responsibility as "the overseas disseminator of Chinese culture".</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">She said she had made great progress with the help of her training class teacher, while also feeling the heavy responsibility of being an "overseas communicator of Chinese culture."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.sl">
    <source>那延伟说，自己回俄后定要把中华传统文化在华人和热爱中国文化的俄罗斯人中间传播和弘扬下去。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.ht">Na Yanwei said that after he returns to Russia, he will continue to spread and advocate traditional Chinese culture amongst the Chinese community and Russian people who love Chinese culture.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.gg">Nayanwe said that after returning to Russia, he must spread and promote the Chinese traditional culture among the Chinese and the Russians who love Chinese culture.</translation>
    <translation system="137_ifeng0812.news.49768396_0_zh.c6">After returning to Russia, he said, he will spread and carry forward the traditional Chinese culture among Chinese and Russians who love Chinese culture.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
