<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>Snapchat 的“动漫”效果被指讽刺亚洲人</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">The “anime” effect of Snapchat is being accused of making fun at Asians.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat's "anime" effect is meant to be ironic to Asians.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Snapchat's' anime 'effect accused of being sarcastic about Asians</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>Snapchat表示这一滤镜的灵感来自动漫，但一些观察者认为它带有种族色彩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Snapchat expressed that anime has served as an inspiration for this filter. Some observers, however, believe that it has racist undertones.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat said the filter was inspired by animation, but some observers thought it was racially colored.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Snapchat said the filter was inspired by anime, but some observers thought it had racial overtones.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>Snapchat的1.5亿名日常用户可以通过其滤镜工具改变现实并且将人像变得滑稽可笑。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">The 150 million active users of Snapchat can use the filter to change the real image into a hilarious and funny face.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat's 150 million of everyday users can change the reality through their filter tools and make the person funny.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Snapchat's 150 million everyday users can use its filter tools to change reality and make people look ridiculous.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>你可以把自己变成一颗菠萝、一只狗或一个罗伊·利希滕斯坦画中的角色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">You can turn yourself into a pineapple, dog, or a character in a Roy Lichtenstein painting.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">You can turn yourself into a pineapple, a dog, or a 罗伊·利希滕斯坦 painting role.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">You can turn yourself into a pineapple, a dog or a character in a Roy Lichtenstein painting.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>这些透镜具有钝化、弯曲特征的效果，每天产生3000多万张经过修饰的自拍。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">with a effects of passivation and curving, the filter was used by more than 30million selfies a day.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">These lenses have the effect of passivation and bending characteristics, resulting in more than 30 million modified self-portraits per day.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">These lenses have the effect of passivating, bending features, producing more than 30 million retouched selfies every day.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>任何失误都会立刻被公众所注意。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Any mistake will be a focal point for the general public.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Any mistake will be immediately noticed by the public.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Any mistakes will be noticed by the public immediately.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>Snapchat透镜曾受到批评，该应用被指鼓动扮演黑人或者以白色皮肤为美。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">The Snapchat filter was criticized before for encouraging blackface antiques or providing fairer skin for beauty effects.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat lenses have been criticized for being used to agitate to play black or white skin.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Snapchat lenses have been criticized, and the app has been accused of encouraging the play of black people or the beauty of white skin.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>因此，当该应用本周为一些用户提供了一个可以创造斜眼、怪牙和粉脸效果的滤镜时，一些评论家将其称为对亚洲“黄种人”的种族讽刺。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Therefore, when it was said that this week should be used to provide some users with filters that could create the effects of slanted eyes, buckteeth and pink face, some critics have called this a racist caricature of “yellow skinned” Asians.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">So, when the application this week provided a filter for some users to create a squint, a weird tooth, and a powder face effect, some commentators called it a racial satire on Asian "yellow people".</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">So when the app this week offered some users a filter that could create squint, grotesque teeth and pink face effects, some critics called it a racial satire on Asia's "yellow race."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>他们甚至认为这些反复出现的问题是否意味着该公司在多样性上存在较大的问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">They even believed that the recurrence of these events is a sign that there are major diversity issues within this company.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">They even think that these recurring problems mean that the company has big problems with diversity.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">They even wonder whether these recurring problems mean the company has bigger problems with diversity.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>在Snapchat表示其删除该功能后，周三The Verge and Motherboard的报道引发众怒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Snapchat expressed that after removing this function, the Wednesday report on The Verge and Motherboard has led to public fury.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">After Snapchat said it had removed the feature, The Verge and motherboard report sparked outrage in Wednesday.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Wednesday's report by The Verge and Motherboard sparked outrage after Snapchat said it had removed the feature.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>该公司的解释是：该滤镜是对动漫角色致敬，而非讽刺亚洲人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">The company’s explanation is: this filter is a tribute to anime characters, not a jibe at Asians.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">The company's explanation is that the filter is a tribute to the anime characters, not the irony of Asians.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">The company's explanation: The filter is a tribute to the anime characters, not a satire of Asians.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>但对于经历过种族主义的观察者而言，该滤镜让他们想起了现实中具有伤害性的刻板印象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">For an observer who has experienced racism, this filter reminded them of harmful stereotypes that occur in real life.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">But for those who have experienced racism, the filter reminds them of a real, hurtful stereotype.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">But for observers who have experienced racism, the filter reminds them of the damaging stereotypes of reality.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>其他人也坚决反对这些动漫形象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Others also firmly opposed these anime caricatures.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Others are adamantly opposed to these anime images.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Others are also adamantly opposed to these animated images.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>一名针对这些照片发表了推特并且被广泛分享的韩裔美国艺术生在一封电子邮件中表示，这些滤镜“至少是令人感到难受和不适的”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">With respect to the posting of these photographs on Twitter and repeated sharing, a Korean American art student expressed in an e-mail that these filters are: “Annoying and discomforting.”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">A Korean-American art student who published Twitter and was widely shared in the photos said the filters were "at least uncomfortable and uncomfortable".</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">A Korean-American art student, who tweeted about the photos and was widely shared, said in an email that the filters were "at least uncomfortable and uncomfortable."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>她还表示：“很难区分极度恶心的亚洲讽刺形象与滤镜的效果。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">She also said:" It is difficult to distinguish the extremely disgusting ironic image of Asian and the filter effect."</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">She added: "It is difficult to distinguish between the most disgusting Asian satirical images and the effects of filters." ”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">"It's hard to tell the difference between an extremely disgusting Asian satirical image and the effect of the filter," she added.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>虽然滤镜中不只是黄种人，但黄种人被极端贬低。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Although the filter does not just include East Asians, these people have been subject to extreme ridicule.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Although the filter is not only yellow people, but the yellow people are extremely degraded.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">While it's not just the yellow in the filter, the yellow is extremely devalued.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>Snapchat并不是唯一一家触及这些文化底线的公司。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Snapchat was not the only company to have tested the cultural bottom line.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat is not the only company that touches the bottom line of these cultures.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Snapchat isn't the only company that has touched the bottom line of these cultures.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>从公司董事会到好莱坞以及我们携带的设备，美国文化似乎一直在提倡多样性与包容性。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">From the company’s board meeting to Hollywood, and the equipment we brought, the American culture seems to promote diversity and tolerance.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">From corporate boardrooms to Hollywood and the equipment we carry, American culture seems to have been advocating diversity and inclusiveness.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">From corporate boards to Hollywood and the devices we carry, American culture seems to have been promoting diversity and inclusion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>Snapchat庞大的年轻群体由于比老一辈更加注重种族的多元化，因此可能会十分敏感。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Snapchat’s large population of young users are more focused on racial diversity compared to the older generation, and may be extremely sensitive to this.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat's vast young population is likely to be very sensitive because of its greater focus on ethnic diversity than the older generation.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Snapchat's large group of young people can be sensitive because they are more ethnically diverse than older generations.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>当Snapchat的一个滤镜产生了侮辱用户的形象时，25岁的朱凯蒂 （音译） 在周四的采访中表示：“相比以前，此类事物更难逃过人们的视线。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">When a Snapchat filter produced an image that insulted a user, 25-year-old Katie Zhu said in an interview on Thursday, “In the past, this sort of thing would not have easily eluded people.”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">When one of Snapchat's filters produced an insult to users, 25-year-old Juketi said in an interview in Thursday: "These things are harder to escape than they were before." ”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">When one of Snapchat's filters produced an insulting image for users, Zhu Katie, 25, said in an interview on Thursday: "It's harder than ever to escape the spotlight."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>周四，在Medium担任产品经理和工程师的朱女士决定删除她的Snapchat帐号并且鼓励他人也这么做。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">On Thursday, Madam Zhu, who is a product manager and engineer at Medium, decided to delete her Snapchat account and encouraged others to do so as well.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Ms Zhu, who acted as product manager and engineer at medium in Thursday, decided to delete her Snapchat account and encourage others to do the same.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">On Thursday, Ms. Zhu, a product manager and engineer at Medium, decided to delete her Snapchat account and encourage others to do the same.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>在一篇为Medium所写的文章和一次电话采访中，她表示自己认为种族方面的争议反映了Snapchat在招聘过程中缺乏种族多样性。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">In  an article for Medium and in a telephone interview, she said that she believed that the racial controversy reflected a lack of ethnic diversity in Snapchat’s hiring process.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">In an article written for medium and a telephone interview, she said she thought racial controversy reflected Snapchat's lack of racial diversity in the recruitment process.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">In an article for Medium and a telephone interview, she said she believes the racial controversy reflects Snapchat's lack of racial diversity in the hiring process.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>朱女士批评该公司的员工大多数为白人，领导层全部为男性并且在文章的最后加上了一个标签：#DeleteSnapchat。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Zhu criticized that most employees of this company are white men, that upper management are all men, and added a hashtag at the back of her post: #DeleteSnapchat.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Ms. Zhu criticized the company's employees for the majority of whites, and the leadership was all male and added a label at the end of the article: #DeleteSnapchat.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Ms. Chu criticized the company's mostly white employees, its all-male leadership, and added a tag at the end of the article: # DeleteSnapchat.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>作为一名华裔美国人，朱女士表示：“要么他们的员工中没有各色人种，所以才能作出这样的决定，要么他们的员工中有一些有色人种，但他们的职位无法让他们畅所欲言。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">As a Chinese American, Mdm Zhu expressed: “Either that they have no colored employees which made this decision possible, or that they have colored employees but their job titles prevent them from voicing their opinions.”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">As a Chinese-American, Ms Chu said: "Either they don't have a variety of people in their workforce, so they can make this decision, or there are some colored people in their staff, but their jobs won't let them speak freely." ”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">"Either they don't have people of all colors on their staff to make that decision, or they have people of color on their staff, but their position doesn't allow them to speak out," says Ms. Zhu, a Chinese-American.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>其他观察者分享了她没有被Snapchat回应的投诉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Other observers shared her complaint for not receiving a response from Snapchat</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Other observers shared complaints that she had not been Snapchat to respond to.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Other observers shared complaints that she had not received a response from Snapchat.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>该公司并未发布有关员工多样性的数据，并且表示自己是一家私人公司。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">This Company has yet to publish information on employee diversity, and expressed that they are a private company.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">The company did not release data on the diversity of its workforce and said it was a private company.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">The company does not release data on employee diversity and says it is a private company.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>周四，Snapchat拒绝讨论其员工的种族背景，但一名发言人称，该公司近期雇用了一名招聘人员专门负责关注内部比例较低的人群以及推动内部包容性方面的工作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">On Thursday, Snapchat refused to discuss the ethnic backgrounds of its staff, but a spokesperson said that the company had recently hired a recruiter to focus primarily on groups that comprise a lower proportion of the company, and to work on promoting inclusiveness within the company.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Snapchat declined to discuss the ethnic background of its employees in Thursday, but a spokeswoman said the company recently hired a recruiter to focus on the lower-level population and to promote internal inclusiveness.</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">On Thursday, Snapchat declined to discuss the racial background of its employees, but a spokesman said the company recently hired a recruiter to focus exclusively on the underrepresented internally and to promote internal inclusiveness.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="109_nytimes.69709_en.sl">
    <source>朱女士表示，她将关闭她的 Snapchat 帐号：“我想知道他们是否需要更多像我们这样反对这一行为的用户。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.ht">Madam Zhu said that she will close her Snapchat account, “I want to know if they need more users like us who oppose this sort of behavior.”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.gg">Ms Zhu said she would close her Snapchat account: "I wonder if they need more users like us to oppose this behavior." ”</translation>
    <translation system="109_nytimes.69709_en.c6">Ms Zhu said she would close her Snapchat account: "I wonder if they need more users like us who are against this."</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
