<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>驳回杰里米·亨特提议后，初级医生计划发起进一步罢工</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">Junior doctors plan more strikes after rejecting Jeremy Hunt’s proposal</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">After dismissing the Jeremy proposal, the junior doctors plan to initiate a further strike</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Junior doctors plan to launch further strikes after rejecting Jeremy Hunt's proposals</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>部长们起初希望通过接受英国医学协会 (BMA) 官员修改后的合同来结束这场由变化引发的纠纷，但是37,000名参与投票的初级医生中，有58%反对该合同。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">The ministers hope accepting the contract officially revised by the British Medical Association (BMA) will help end the disputes caused by the change. However, of the 37,000 junior doctors who participated in the vote, 58% opposed the contract.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">The ministers initially wanted to end the change-induced dispute by accepting a revised contract from the British Medical Association (BMA) officials, but 58% of the 37,000 junior doctors who voted were against the contract.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Ministers initially wanted to end the dispute over the changes by accepting a revised contract from British Medical Association (BMA) officials, but 58 per cent of the 37,000 junior doctors who took part in the vote opposed the contract.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>7月，亨特先生透露计划强制实行合同，他说英国国家医疗服务体系 (NHS) 目前处于“真空地带”，稍有延误便会损害员工和患者的利益。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">In July, Mr. Hunt disclosed a plan to enforce the contract, and said that the National Health Service (NHS) of the UK is currently “in limbo”. Any delay will harm the interests of the employees and patients.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">In July, Mr. Hunter revealed plans to enforce the contract, saying that the NHS is currently in a "vacuum zone" and that a slight delay would hurt the interests of employees and patients.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">In July, Mr Hunt revealed plans to force the contract, saying the NHS was in a "vacuum" and that a slight delay would hurt staff and patients.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>新合同首先提到修改初级医生通宵与周末工作惯例，以改善非正常工作时间的护理情况。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">The new contract first raised the issue of altering the overnight and weekend work routines of junior doctors so as to improve nursing conditions during unsocial hours.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">The new contract first mentions changes in the working practices of primary doctors overnight and weekend to improve the care of irregular working hours.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">The new contract begins with a reference to changes to junior doctors' overnight and weekend working practices to improve care during irregular working hours.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>昨天晚上，BMA 初级医生委员会主席 Ellen McCourt 博士在一份声明中说道：“初级医生对拟议的合同仍有着严重担忧，尤其担心它会加剧当前的劳动力危机，也未能公平地对待所有医生。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">In a statement last night, Dr Ellen McCourt, Chairperson of BMA’s junior doctors’ committee, said, “Junior doctors still have serious concerns about the proposed contract, particularly that it will fuel the current workforce crisis, and that it fails to treat all doctors fairly.”</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">In a statement last night, Dr. Ellen McCourt, chairman of the BMA Junior Physician Committee, said: "There is still serious concern among junior physicians about the proposed contract, especially in the interest that it will exacerbate the current labour crisis and not treat all doctors fairly." ”</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Dr Ellen McCourt, chair of the BMA's junior doctors committee, said in a statement last night: "Junior doctors still have serious concerns about the proposed contract, particularly that it will exacerbate the current workforce crisis and fail to treat all doctors fairly."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>距离首批医生签署新合同仅剩八周时间了，我们需要取得进展，时间不多了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">Only 8 weeks are left for the first batch of doctors to sign the new contract. There isn’t much time left. We must achieve progress.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">It's only eight weeks before the first doctor signs the new contract and we need to make progress.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">With just eight weeks to go before the first doctors sign a new contract, we need to make progress and time is running out.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>BMA 努力通过谈判解决纠纷，但是大家却不愿意参与，有时政府则以沉默应对。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">BMA is working hard to resolve the dispute through negotiations. However, nobody wished to participate. Sometimes, the government responded with silence.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">BMA tried to resolve the dispute through negotiations, but everyone was unwilling to participate, and sometimes the government responded with silence.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">The BMA has tried to resolve disputes through negotiation, but people have been reluctant to participate, and sometimes the government has responded with silence.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>尽管如此，就在上个月我们还是得到了杰里米·亨特的承诺，他说自己的大门始终敞开。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">Nevertheless, we’ve received a promise from Jeremy Hunt that he will keep his doors open.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">Still, last month, we got Jeremy's promise, saying that his door was always open.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">That said, just last month we received a commitment from Jeremy Hunt, who said his door was always open.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>“杰里米·亨特现在需要采取行动了，取消强制执行，解决初级医生”担心的问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">“Jeremy Hunt needs to take action now, cancel the forced implementation, and resolve the “issues of concern” of the junior doctors.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">"Jeremy now needs to take action to eliminate enforcement and address the concerns of junior doctors."</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">"Jeremy Hunt needs to take action now to remove enforcement and address junior doctors" concerns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>如果他不这样做，初级医生明确表示他们已经准备好采取进一步的劳工行动了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">If he failed to do that, the junior doctors clearly expressed that they have made the necessary preparations to take the next step of labor actions.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">If he does not, the junior doctors make it clear that they are ready to take further labor action.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">If he doesn't, junior doctors have made clear they are ready for further industrial action.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>上次罢工发生在4月底，导致近13,000台常规手术和100,000例预约延期，因为护士和会诊医生为纠察线上的医生打掩护。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">The previous strike occurred at late April, and delayed nearly 13,000 standard operations and 100,000 appointments as nurses and consulting physicians provided cover for doctors on the picket line.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">The last strike, which occurred at the end of April, resulted in nearly 13,000 routine surgeries and 100,000 appointment delays, as nurses and consultants covered the picket line for doctors.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">The last strike, at the end of April, led to the postponement of almost 13,000 routine operations and 100,000 appointments as nurses and consultant doctors covered for doctors on the picket line.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>部长们起初希望通过接受 BMA 修改后的合同来结束这场由变化引发的纠纷。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">The ministers hoped that the acceptance of the contract revised by the BMA will help resolve the dispute sparked by the changes.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">The ministers initially hoped to end the dispute caused by the change by accepting BMA's revised contract.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Ministers initially wanted to end the dispute over the changes by accepting the BMA's revised contract.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>BMA 希望为合同所涉及的54,000名初级医生争取更好的周末工资。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">BMA hopes to fight for better weekend wages for the 54,000 junior doctors concerned.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">BMA hopes to secure better weekend pay for the 54,000 junior doctors involved in the contract.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">The BMA wants to secure better weekend pay for the 54,000 junior doctors covered by the contract.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>NHS Employers 首席执行官 Daniel Mortimer 呼吁初级医生不要再上演任何罢工了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">Daniel Mortimer, Chief Executive Officer of NHS Employers, called upon the Junior Doctors to stop any protest.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">Daniel Mortimer, chief executive of NHS Employers, called on junior doctors to stop any further strikes.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Daniel Mortimer, chief executive of NHS Employees, has called on junior doctors not to stage any more strikes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>Mortimer 先生说：“劳工行动收效甚微，相反却会对已然倾注全力的队伍和服务造成压力，导致患者、护理人员及其家人的担心、忧虑及混乱。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">Mr. Mortimer said: “The effects of labor actions are extremely limited, and instead generate pressure on teams and services who are doing what they can, causing anxiety, worry, and confusion amongst patients, healthcare personnel, and their family members.”</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">Mr Mortimer said: "The effect of the labour action is minimal, but it will put pressure on the teams and services already devoted to them, causing worries, worries and confusion among patients, nursing staff and their families." ”</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Mr Mortimer said: "Labour action will have little effect, but instead will put pressure on already committed teams and services, causing fear, anxiety and confusion for patients, caregivers and their families."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>过去两个月里，我们不断与初级医生委员会进行谈判，并和卫生部及其他部门一起积极回应他们对监护人角色和举报揭发的担忧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">For the last two months, we have continuously tried to negotiate with the junior doctor association, and actively responded, together with the Department of Health and other departments, of their concerns relating to their role as supervisors and disclose information.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">Over the past two months, we have been negotiating with the junior doctors ' committee, and have been actively responding to their concerns about the role of guardians and the disclosure of their complaints with the Ministry of Health and other departments.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Over the past two months, we have been in ongoing negotiations with the junior doctors' committee and, together with the Department of Health and others, have responded positively to their concerns about the role of guardians and whistle-blowing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.sl">
    <source>雇主们希望继续积极探讨其他重要话题——如部署、培训的灵活性、针对那些在职业生涯中断后重上岗之人的其他培训、培训成本、对课程提纲的共同认知、进修假和医疗领域的性别工资差异，这些说明了雇主、英格兰健康教育组织 (Health Education England) 和卫生部对11月、2月及5月与 BMA 达成的协议很重视。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.ht">Employers hope to continue active investigations in other key issues such as flexibility in deployment and training, providing other form of training to people who have been re-employed after a hiatus from their professional career, training costs, joint consensus for the course outlines, training vacations, and gender pay gap in the medical profession. This means that the employers place great importance on the agreement reached between the employers, Health Education England, and Department of Health and the BMA in November, February, and May.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.gg">Employers want to continue to actively explore other important topics, such as deployment, the flexibility of training, the cost of other training, training, common recognition of curriculum outlines, continuing education leave and gender wage differentials in the medical field are illustrated by employers, the Health education organization of England (Health Education England and the Ministry of Health attached great importance to the agreements reached with BMA in November, February and May.</translation>
    <translation system="163_dailymail.co.uk.170661_en.c6">Employers' desire to continue to actively explore other important topics – such as deployment, flexibility in training, other training for those returning to work after a career break, training costs, a common understanding of the syllabus, further education leave and gender pay differentials in healthcare – illustrates the importance employers, Health Education England and the Department of Health attach to the agreements reached with the BMA in November, February and May.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
