<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>28岁厨师被发现死于旧金山一家商场</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">﻿28-year-old chef found dead in San Francisco mall</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">﻿28-year-old chef found dead in a shopping mall in San Francisco</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">﻿The 28-year-old chef was found dead at a San Francisco mall</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>近日刚搬至旧金山的一位28岁厨师本周被发现死于当地一家商场的楼梯间。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">A 28-year-old chef who recently moved to San Francisco was found dead in the stairwell of a local mall this week.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">A 28-year-old chef who recently moved to San Francisco was found dead in the stairwell of a local mall this week.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">A 28-year-old chef who recently moved to San Francisco was found dead in the stairwell of a local shopping mall this week.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>但受害人的哥哥表示想不出有谁会想要加害于他，并称“一切终于好起来了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">The older brother of the victim expressed that he could not think of anyone who would want to harm him, and said that “everything was finally getting better”.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">But the victim's brother said that he could not think of anyone who would want to harm him, and said, "It's finally all right." ”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">But the victim's brother said he could not think of anyone who would want to harm him, saying "everything is finally getting better."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>旧金山验尸官办公室表示，周三早上于西田购物中心发现的尸体确认为28岁旧金山居民 Frank Galicia。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">The Forensic Services of San Francisco expressed that they have verified the identity of the body found in Wednesday morning at Westfield shopping center as Frank Galicia, a 28-year old resident of San Francisco.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">The San Francisco Coroner's office said the body found at the Tian Mall in Wednesday was confirmed as the 28-year-old San Francisco resident Frank in.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">The San Francisco coroner's office said the body found at the Westfield Shopping Center on Wednesday morning was identified as Frank Galicia, a 28-year-old San Francisco resident.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>旧金山警察局称该起死亡案件被裁定为他杀，并正在进行调查。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">San Francisco police claimed that the death was ruled a homicide, and has commenced investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">The San Francisco Police Department said the death case was found to be homicide and is under investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">The San Francisco Police Department says the death was ruled a homicide and is under investigation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>受害人的哥哥 Louis Galicia 对美国广播公司位于旧金山的电台 KGO 表示，之前在波士顿做流水线厨师的Frank 于六个月前在旧金山的 Sons &amp; Daughters 餐馆找到一份流水线厨师的理想工作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">The victim’s brother, Louis Galicia, told San Francisco KGO-TV, owned by American Broadcasting Company, that Frank, who worked as a line chef in Boston, found his ideal job as a line chef at Sons &amp; Daughters restaurant in San Francisco six months ago.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">The victim's brother, Louis in, told ABC's Radio KGO in San Francisco that Frank, who worked as a line chef in Boston, found an ideal job as a line chef at Sons &amp; Daughters restaurant in San Francisco six months ago.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">The victim's brother, Louis Galicia, told ABC radio station KGO in San Francisco that Frank, who previously worked as a streaming chef in Boston, found an ideal job as a streaming chef at San Francisco's Sons &amp; Daughters restaurant six months ago.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Sons &amp; Daughters 餐馆的一位发言人表示，他们对于 Frank 的死感到“非常震惊”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Another spokesperson of Sons &amp; Daughters restaurant that they felt “extremely shocked” about Frank’s death.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">A spokesman for the Sons &amp; Daughters restaurant said they were "very shocked" at Frank's death.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">A spokeswoman for the Sons &amp; Daughters restaurant said they were "devastated" by Frank's death.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>该发言人称，“我们是相处得像亲密无间的一家人的一个小团队，我们将深深怀念他。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">The spokesperson said: “Our team is like a family. We shall miss him.”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">"We are a small team with a close family and we will miss him deeply," the spokeswoman said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">"We are a small group of people who get along like a close family, and we will miss him very much," the spokesman said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>在这个悲痛的时刻，我们向 Frank 的家人及朋友表达我们深切的同情与哀悼。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">In this painful times, let us express our deepest condolences and sorrow for Frank’s family and friends.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">At this sad moment, we express our deepest sympathy and condolences to Frank's family and friends.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">We extend our deepest sympathy and condolences to Frank's family and friends at this sad time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Louis Galicia 称 Frank 起初住在招待所里，但是最近“一切终于好起来了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Louis Galicia said that Frank initially lived at the guest house, but recently “everything finally got better”.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">Louis in said that Frank had initially lived in a guest house, but recently "everything has finally come to a good end." ”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">Louis Galicia said Frank initially stayed in a guest house, but recently "things are finally getting better."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Louis Galicia 告诉 KGO：“Frank找到一间公寓，同时在跟一个女孩交往。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Louis Galicia told KGO, “Frank found an apartment, and was also seeing someone.”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">Louis in told KGO: "Frank found an apartment and was in a relationship with a girl." ”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">"Frank found an apartment and was dating a girl at the same time," Louis Galicia told KGO.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Louis Galicia 表示，他想不出有谁会想要加害他的弟弟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Louis Galicia expressed that he could not think of anyone who would harm his younger brother.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">Louis in said he could not think of anyone who would want to harm his brother.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">Louis Galicia said he couldn't think of anyone who would want to hurt his brother.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Frank 拥有善良的心地及宽阔的胸怀。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Frank has a kind and open heart.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">Frank has a good heart and broad mind.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">Frank has a good heart and a big heart.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Louis Galicia 称：“Frank 经常为家人烹饪晚餐。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Louis Galicia said, “Frank often cooks dinner for the family.”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">"Frank often cooks dinner for his family," says Louis in. ”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">"Frank often cooks dinner for his family," said Louis Galicia.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>他从不愿意与家人争吵。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">He is unwilling to argue with family members.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">He never wants to quarrel with his family.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">He was never willing to quarrel with his family.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>他是一个随从大家意见的人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">He is a person who follows the opinions of others.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">He is a man of opinion.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">He is a man of everyone's opinion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>Louis Galicia 说：“世上的所有事物都有可能出错，但Frank 称得上是一个每天都发光的外粗内秀之人。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Louis Galicia said, "With everything else that's going wrong with the world, Frank was that diamond in the rough that was shining bright every day."</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">Louis in said: "Everything in the world can be wrong, but Frank is a diamond who shines every day." ”</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">"Everything in the world can go wrong," says Louis Galicia, "but Frank is something of an outsider who shines every day."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="127_abcnews.199762_en.sl">
    <source>有线索人士请拨打旧金山警察局举报电话415-575-4444。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.ht">Please call the San Francisco police at 415-575-4444 if you have any information.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.gg">For clues, please call the San Francisco police station to report 415-575-4444.</translation>
    <translation system="127_abcnews.199762_en.c6">Anyone with information should call the San Francisco Police Department at 415-575-4444.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
