<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.sl">
    <source>自iPhoneSE惊艳亮相之后，手机市场也迎来了小屏机的热潮。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.ht">Since it was first revealed, iPhoneSE has initiated a massive hype and a sudden trend for small screen devices for the cellphone market.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.gg">Since the Iphonese stunning debut, the handset market also ushered in the small screen machine craze.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.c6">The mobile phone market has also seen a boom in small screens since the stunning debut of the iPhone SE.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.sl">
    <source>前不久，努比亚也推出了其Z11系列的首款作品：nubiaZ11mini。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.ht">Not too long ago, Nubia also released its flagship product for the Z11 series: Nubia Z11 mini.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.gg">Shortly before, Nubian also launched its first work of the Z11 series: Nubiaz11mini.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.c6">Not long ago, Nubia also launched the first piece of its Z11 series: nubiaZ11mini.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.sl">
    <source>nubiaZ11mini延续了其一贯的卓越拍照基因，并配备了单手更易握持的5.0英寸屏幕、便捷易用的后置指纹识别，成就了其出众的使用体验。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.ht">The nubiaZ11min inherited its customary excellent photographic gene. Equipped with a single hand easy-to-hold 5-inch screen as well as a convenient and easy-to-use fingerprint identification setup at the back, its user experience is outstanding.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.gg">Nubiaz11mini continues its consistent and excellent photographic gene, and is equipped with a single hand easier to grip the 5.0-inch screen, easy and easy to use the back fingerprint recognition, the achievement of its outstanding experience.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.c6">The nubiaZ11mini continues its tradition of superior photography with a 5.0-inch screen that is easier to hold with one hand, and easy-to-use rear fingerprint recognition for a superior user experience.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.sl">
    <source>nubia旗下刚刚上市的小屏拍照手机Z11mini降价200元，即从原来的1499元降至1299元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.ht">The nubia Z11 mini, a small screen camera phone that has just been released, is provided with another 200 RMB discount, reducing its price from 1,499 RMB to 1,299 RMB.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.gg">Nubia's just-listed small-screen camera phone Z11mini 200 yuan, that is, from the original 1499 yuan to 1299 yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.c6">Nubia's newly listed small screen photo phone, the Z11mini, reduced its price by $200, or $1,299, from $1,499.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.sl">
    <source>在外观方面，nubiaZ11mini采用了一块5英寸的1080P屏幕，正面下方依旧是经典的“小红圈”设计。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.ht">For the exterior design, nubiaZ11mini has a 5'' 1080P screen with the signature small red ring at the front bottom.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.gg">In terms of appearance, Nubiaz11mini used a 5-inch 1080P screen, the front is still the classic "Small red circle" design.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.c6">In terms of appearance, the nubiaZ11mini features a 5-inch 1080P screen, with the classic "little red circle" design still underneath the front.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.sl">
    <source>中框为金属材质，底部采用对称式设计并配置了Type-C数据接口。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.ht">The middle axis is made of metal material. A symmetrical design is used for the bottom, and a Type-C data interface has been installed.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.gg">The middle frame is a metal material, and the bottom is symmetrically designed and configured with a TYPE-C data interface.</translation>
    <translation system="038_sina0812.tech.doc-ifxuxnai9861987-p3_zh.c6">The middle frame is made of metal, and the bottom is symmetrically designed and equipped with a Type-C data interface.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
