<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>《Treats》：裸体日历“男女都喜爱”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">Treats: A nude calendar “both men and women will love”</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">"Treats": Nude Calendar "men and women alike"</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">"Treats": Nude calendar "Favorite for both men and women"</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>《Treats》杂志将携手摄影师 David Bellemere 拍摄一组灵感源自20世纪70年代 Pirelli 的2017年日历。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">Treats magazine will be working with photographer David Bellemere to create a 2017 calendar inspired by Pirelli designs of 1970s.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">Treats magazine will join hands with photographer David Bellemere in a 2017-year calendar of inspiration from the the 1970s Pirelli.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">Treats Magazine will be working with photographer David Bellemere on a 2017 calendar inspired by Pirelli in the 1970s.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>此次，他们计划为其2017 NU Muses 日历寻找新一代顶级模特，而非著名的裸体人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">They plan to seek a new generation of top models for their 2017 NU Muses calendar rather than use famous nudes this time round.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">This time, they plan to find a new generation of top models for their 2017 NU muses calendar, rather than a famous nude person.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">This time, they plan to look for a new generation of top models for their 2017 NU Muses calendar, rather than the famous nude.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>《Treats》总裁 Steve Shaw 今年早些时候表示，他们以裸体为主的杂志不同于老派的《花花公子》，因为“后者面向男性。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">Treats magazine publisher Steve Shaw expressed earlier today that their magazine which features nudes primarily, is different from the old style Playboy magazine because “the latter is directed at men”.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">Steve Shaw, president of treats, said earlier this year that their nude magazines differed from the old-fashioned playboy, because "the latter is for men." ”</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">Treats president Steve Shaw said earlier this year that their mostly nude magazine was different from the old-school Playboy because "the latter is for men."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>而我们则面向女性。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">And we are facing the women.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">And we face women.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">And we're targeting women.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>显然，他认为这组日历也是这样。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">Apparently, he believes that these diaries are the same as well.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">Obviously, he thinks this group of calendars is the same.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">Obviously, he thinks the same is true of this set of calendars.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>“我们需要展示让女性和男性都感觉自在的永恒而经典的裸体，而这次正是受此启发，”Shaw 在一次日历推介发布会上如是说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">“We need to display lasting and classic nudes that make men and women feel comfortable, and it was precisely this that inspired us,” Shaw said at a briefing to promote the calendar.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">"We need to show the timeless, classic nudity that makes both women and men feel comfortable, and this is the inspiration," Shaw told a calendar presentation.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">"We need to show timeless and classic nudity that makes both women and men feel comfortable, and this time it's inspired by that," Shaw said at a calendar launch.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>女性会乐于参与此次拍摄，因为它是一个美丽的艺术品。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">Women enjoyed participating in this  shoot because it was a beautiful piece of artwork.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">Women will be happy to participate in this shoot because it is a beautiful artwork.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">Women will be happy to take part in the shoot because it's a beautiful work of art.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="106_foxnews.68215_en.sl">
    <source>模特们可在线提交照片应聘，也可亲自到洛杉矶和纽约的公开招募现场应聘。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.ht">Models may apply by submitting their photos online. They may also apply in person at the open recruitment centers in Los Angeles and New York.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.gg">Models can submit photos online and apply for public recruitment to Los Angeles and New York in person.</translation>
    <translation system="106_foxnews.68215_en.c6">Models can submit photo applications online or in person at public recruitment sites in Los Angeles and New York.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
