<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>一年以来，汇改成果显著，人民币汇率保持基本稳定，同时也为推动人民币国际化奠定了基础。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">Since a year ago, the results of the exchange rate reform have been significant. The RMB exchange rate has remained generally stable. The reform has also laid the foundation for advancing the internationalization of the RMB at the same time.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Over the past year, the results of the reform have been remarkable, the RMB exchange rate has remained basically stable, and it has laid a foundation for promoting RMB internationalization.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">Over the past year, the results of the exchange rate reform have been remarkable, and the RMB exchange rate has remained basically stable. At the same time, it has laid a foundation for promoting the internationalization of the renminbi.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从市场表现来看，一年来，人民币汇率双向浮动特征明显，汇率弹性增强，汇率预期总体平稳。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">In terms of market performance, the RMB exchange rate's characteristic of fluctuating both ways is apparent. The exchange rate’s elasticity has increased and is expected to remain generally stable.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">In terms of market performance, the two-way floating characteristics of RMB exchange rate are obvious, the exchange rate elasticity is enhanced and the exchange rate is expected to be stable.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">From the market performance point of view, over the past year, the two-way floating characteristics of the RMB exchange rate is obvious, the exchange rate flexibility increased, the exchange rate is expected to be generally stable.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>汇改至今，人民币对美元中间价超百点的上下波动屡屡出现，但过程升贬交替。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">To date, the exchange rate reform has seen the median price of the RMB: USD exchange rate repeatedly fluctuating at more than 100 basis points, with intermittent appreciation and depreciation.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Since then, the fluctuation of RMB to the middle price of the US dollar exceeding 100 points has appeared frequently, but the process has been changed.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">Since the reform of the exchange rate, the RMB against the United States dollar more than 100 points up and down fluctuations frequently occur, but the process of rising and falling alternately.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>去年“8·11”汇改之前的最后一次汇改措施实施于2005年，十年间人民币对美元显著升值。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">The last exchange rate reform measures prior to the “8.11” exchange rate reform last year were implemented in 2005. In the last 10 years, the RMB has appreciated significantly against the USD.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Last year's "8·11" before the transfer of reform measures implemented in 2005, a decade of RMB appreciation of the dollar significantly.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">The last change before the August 11, 2005, was a significant appreciation of the renminbi against the dollar over the past decade.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>新汇改实施以来，人民币改变了之前升值状态，一年间人民币汇率中间价贬值约8％。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">Since the new currency reforms, Renminbi reversed its appreciation and its central parity rate dropped by about 8% within an year.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Since the implementation of the new exchange, the renminbi has changed its previous appreciation status, the renminbi exchange rate in the middle of a year, the devaluation of about 8%.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">Since the implementation of the new exchange rate reform, the renminbi has changed its previous state of appreciation, with the midpoint value of the renminbi depreciating by about 8 per cent over the course of a year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>今年10月1日，国际货币基金组织将正式接纳人民币，成为ＳＤＲ（特别提款权）权重货币。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">On October 1 this year, the International Monetary Fund will officially include the RMB as a currency in the SDR (Special Drawing Rights) basket.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">October 1 This year, the International Monetary Fund will formally accept the renminbi, the SDR (Special drawing rights) The weight of the currency.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">On October 1, the International Monetary Fund will officially accept the renminbi as a SDR (Special Drawing Rights) weighted currency.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>本周，中国海关总署公布的统计数据显示，今年前7个月，中国进出口总值13.21万亿元人民币，比去年同期下降3％。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">Figures announced by the General Administration of Customs this week revealed that for the first seven months of this year, China’s total imports and exports fell 3% year-on-year to RMB13.21 trillion.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">In the first 7 months of this year, China's imports and exports were 13.21 trillion yuan, down 3% from a year earlier, according to statistics released by the Customs administration of China this week.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">This week, statistics released by China's General Administration of Customs showed that China's imports and exports totaled 13.21 trillion yuan in the first seven months of this year, down 3 percent from the same period last year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而在7月当月，中国进出口总值同比仅下降0.9％，特别是出口同比增长了2.9％。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">Also in July, the sum of export and import decreased only 0.9% y-o-y, while export increased 2.9% during the same time.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">In the month of July, China's imports and exports fell only 0.9% year-on-year, especially as exports rose 2.9% per cent year-on-year.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">In the same month in July, the value of China's imports and exports fell by only 0.9 per cent year-on-year, particularly as exports grew by 2.9 per cent year-on-year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>相关专家认为，尽管7月进出口有企稳迹象，但不应有过高预期。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">Some experts believe that although imports and exports in July exhibited signs of stability, overly optimistic expectations should be avoided.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Relevant experts believe that, despite signs of stabilisation in July, there should be no high expectations.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">Experts believe that despite signs of stabilization in exports and imports in July, expectations should not be too high.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>7月，中国进出口总值2.09万亿元人民币，同比下降0.9％。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">In July, China’s total import and export amounted to RMB2.09 trillion, down 0.9% year-on-year.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">July, China's imports and exports of 2.09 trillion yuan, the year-on-year decline of 0.9%.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">In July, the total value of China's imports and exports was 2.09 trillion yuan, down 0.9 percent year-on-year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>其中，出口1.22万亿元人民币，增长2.9％；进口8730亿元人民币，下降5.7％；贸易顺差3428亿元，扩大34％。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">In which exports amounted to 1.22 trillion RMB for a 2.9% growth; imports amounted to 873.0 billion RMB, decreasing by 5.7%; and trade surplus amounted to 342.8 billion RMB for a 34% growth.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Among them, exports 1.22 trillion yuan, the growth 2.9%, imports 873 billion yuan, falls 5.7%, the trade surplus 342.8 billion yuan, expands 34%.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">Of this total, exports amounted to 1.22 trillion yuan, an increase of 2.9 per cent; imports amounted to 873 billion yuan, a decrease of 5.7 per cent; and the trade surplus amounted to 342.8 billion yuan, an increase of 34 per cent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.sl">
    <source>尽管进出口总值同比依然下降，但出口数据出现了增长，这也是自今年3月以来，出口实现连续第五个月增长。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.ht">Although total imports and exports have decreased compared to the same period last year, data for export value has increased. This is the fifth consecutive month with growth in exports since March this year.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.gg">Despite the year-on-year decline in imports and exports, export data have grown, which is the fifth consecutive month of export growth since March this year.</translation>
    <translation system="133_ifeng0812.news.49767909_0_zh.c6">Although the total value of imports and exports still fell year-on-year, the export figures showed an increase, marking the fifth consecutive monthly increase in exports since March this year.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
