<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>东北虎，目前被世界自然保护联盟(IUCN)濒危物种红色名录列为濒危(EN)物种。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">The Siberian tiger is now listed as an endangered (EN) species by the International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN) Red List.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">The Amur tiger, currently classified as endangered (EN) by the World Conservation Union (IUCN) 's Red List of endangered species.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">The Siberian tiger, currently listed as an endangered (EN) species on the IUCN Red List of Endangered Species.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据吉林省林业厅介绍，1998年中美俄等国联合监测的数据显示，吉林省仅有野生东北虎4到6只、东北豹3到5只。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">According to the Forestry Department of Jilin, the 1998 data from a joint monitoring exercise by China, the US and Russia showed that there were only four to six Siberian tigers, and three to five Amur leopards living in the wild in Jilin Province.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">According to the Forestry Department of Jilin Province, 1998, the United States and Russia and other countries monitoring data show that Jilin Province only has wild Amur tigers 4 to 6, Northeast Leopard 3 to 5.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">According to the Forestry Department of Jilin Province, data from joint monitoring by China, the United States, Russia and other countries in 1998 showed that there were only four to six wild Siberian tigers and three to five northeastern leopards in Jilin Province.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据吉林省林业厅保护处处长于长春介绍，近年来吉林省不断加大对野生动物的保护，东北虎、东北豹在中国的种群数量正显著增长，分布区域不断扩展。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">According to Yu Changchun, director of the conservation section of the Jilin Forestry Department, said that Jilin Province has been expanding protection efforts for the wildlife. The populations of the northeastern tiger and northeastern leopard have achieved significant growth and their ranges have been growing as well.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">According to Changchun, director of the Protection Department of Forestry Department of Jilin Province, in recent years, Jilin Province has been increasing the protection of wildlife, the population of Amur tiger and northeast leopard in China is increasing significantly and the distribution area is expanding.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">According to Yu Changchun, director of the protection division of the Jilin Provincial Forestry Department, the population of Siberian tigers and northeastern leopards in China is growing significantly and the distribution area is expanding in recent years as Jilin Province has continuously increased its protection of wild animals.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2015年最新监测数据显示，仅吉林省境内就监测到野生东北虎27只、东北豹42只。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">Data from the latest monitoring in 2015 revealed that 27 Siberian tigers and 42 Amur leopards living in the wild were detected within Jilin Province.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">The latest monitoring data in 2015 showed that only 27 wild Amur tigers and 42 Northeast leopard were detected in Jilin Province.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">The latest monitoring data for 2015 showed that 27 wild Siberian tigers and 42 northeastern leopards were detected in Jilin Province alone.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>作为分布在中俄交界区域的世界野生动物保护旗舰物种，中俄两国间的合作对于野生东北虎、豹的种群恢复和繁衍意义重大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">As flagship species of World Animal Protection distributed across the China-Russia border, the China-Russia partnership is especially meaningful to restore and increase the populations of northeastern tigers and leopards.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">As the flagship species of World Wildlife conservation in the Sino-Russian border region, cooperation between China and Russia is significant for the recovery and reproduction of wild Amur tigers and leopard populations.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">As the world's flagship wildlife conservation species distributed in the Sino-Russian border region, the cooperation between China and Russia is of great significance for the population restoration and reproduction of wild Siberian tigers and leopards.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据吉林省林业厅介绍，此前吉林省已与俄罗斯建立了长期稳定的合作交流机制。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">According to the Department of Forestry of Jilin, the province has established a long-term and stable system of cooperation and exchange.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">According to the Forestry Department of Jilin Province, the Jilin Province has established a long-term and stable cooperation and exchange mechanism with Russia.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">Jilin Province has previously established a long-term and stable cooperation and exchange mechanism with Russia, according to the forestry department of Jilin Province.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在11日结束的2016中国珲春虎豹保护国际论坛上，中俄两国林业部门和动物保护组织再次达成多项共识。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">During the 2016 International Conference for the Conservation of Hunchun Tigers and Leopards of China that concluded on the 11th, forestry agencies and animal protection groups of China and Russia have once again reached multiple consensus.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">At the end of 11th, the 2016 China Hunchun Tiger Leopard Protection International Forum, the Chinese and Russian forestry sector and animal protection organizations once again reached a number of consensus.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">At the 2016 Hunchun Tiger and Leopard Conservation International Forum in China, which ended on November 11, the forestry departments and animal protection organizations of China and Russia once again reached a number of common understandings.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.sl">
    <source>吉林省林业厅表示，加强中俄两国虎、豹保护合作，不仅是中国东北虎、豹保护面临的十分紧迫的任务，也是维系俄罗斯虎、豹种群健康的当务之急。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.ht">The Jilin Forestry Department expressed that strengthening the conversation partnership between China and Russia is a desperate task for protecting the northeastern tigers and leopards of China. It is also imperative in maintaining the health of Russian tiger and leopard populations.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.gg">Jilin Province Forestry Department said, strengthen the Sino-Russian Tiger, leopard protection cooperation, not only is China's Siberian tiger, leopard protection is facing a very urgent task, but also to maintain the Russian tiger, leopard population health priorities.</translation>
    <translation system="035_ifeng0812.news.49767755_0_zh.c6">Jilin Provincial Forestry Department said that strengthening cooperation between China and Russia in tiger and leopard conservation is not only a very urgent task facing China's northeast tiger and leopard conservation, but also to maintain the health of the Russian tiger and leopard population.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
