<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>行业数据显示，2015年煤炭产能总规模接近60亿吨，全国煤炭产能过剩18亿吨。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Industry figures revealed that in 2015, coal production capacity totaled approximately 6 billion tonnes, with excess capacity of 1.8 billion tonnes nationwide.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Industry data show that 2015 coal production capacity of nearly 6 billion tons, the national coal production capacity of 1.8 billion tons.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Industry data show that total coal production capacity in 2015 was nearly 6 billion tons, with a national surplus of 1.8 billion tons of coal capacity.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>近十年来，国务院前后共发布过5次淘汰过剩与落后产能的通知。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">For nearly 10 years, the State Council of the People's Republic of China have announced 5 notices for eliminating redundant and obsolete production capacities.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">In recent ten years, the State Council has issued a total of 5 times before and after the elimination of excess and backward production capacity notice.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Over the past decade, the State Council has issued a total of five times before and after the elimination of excess and backward production capacity.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>虽然前4次没有针对煤炭行业，但目标行业直接与煤炭业产生关系。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Although the coal industry was not the target in the first four times, the targeted industries were directly related to coal industry production.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Although the first 4 times did not target the coal industry, but the target industry directly with the coal industry to produce relations.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Although the first four times did not target the coal industry, but the target industry has a direct relationship with the coal industry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>去年11月到今年1月，秦皇岛5500大卡动力煤价格长期在370元/吨低位徘徊，90%的煤炭企业陷入亏损。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">From November last year to January this year, the Qinhuangdao 5,500 kcal steam coal has been fluctuating around a price of 370 Yuan/ton, and 90% of coal industries are experiencing losses.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Last November to this January, Qinhuangdao 5500 kcal power coal prices for a long time in 370 yuan/ton low hovering, 90% of coal enterprises into a loss.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Between November last year and January, Qinhuangdao's 5,500 kilocalories of thermal coal prices hovered at a low of 370 yuan / ton for a long time, with 90 percent of coal companies in the red.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而2月份以来，煤价逐步回升，近期秦皇岛动力煤价格更是连续上涨四周，上升到16个月来的高点，一度攀升到每吨436元，比年初上涨近70元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Since February, coal prices have started to rebound. The price of steam coal at Qinhuangdao has risen for 4 consecutive weeks, reaching a peak during the last 16 months at a price of 436 Yuan per ton, a figure that almost rose by 70 Yuan compared to the start of the year.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">And since February, coal prices have gradually picked up, the recent Qinhuangdao power coal price is continuously rising around, rose to a 16-month high, once climbed to 436 yuan per ton, a rise of nearly 70 yuan than the beginning.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">And since February, coal prices gradually recovered, the recent Qinhuangdao thermal coal prices rose for four consecutive weeks, rose to a 16-month high, once climbed to 436 yuan per ton, up nearly 70 yuan from the beginning of the year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>随着价格回升，各界担心随之产生：一批小煤矿会不会复工复产？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">As prices rebound, concerns have arisen: Will some of the small coal mines resume production?</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">As the price picks up, all the worries come along: Will a batch of small coal mines return to resuming production?</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">As prices recovered, concerns arose about whether a group of small coal mines would return to work and return to production.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>对此，中国（海南）改革发展研究院经济所所长匡贤明进行了分析与解读。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Kuang Xianming, director of the China Institute for Reform and Development (Hainan), analyzed and interpreted this.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">In this respect, China (Hainan) Reform and Development Institute of Economic Director Kao Xianming Analysis and interpretation.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">In this regard, China (Hainan) Reform and Development Research Institute, Director of the Institute of Economics Kuang Xianming conducted analysis and interpretation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>匡贤明：去产能引起了各方的高度关注，今天公布的煤炭行业去产能的成绩单也确实让大家感到比较担心。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Kuang Xianming: Elimination of excess capacity caught everyone’s attention. The report card on the elimination of excess capacity in the coal industry announced today has indeed caused greater concern.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Kao Xianming: To production capacity has aroused the attention of all parties, the coal industry released today to the production capacity of the report card also really make everyone feel more worried.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Quang Xianming: De-capacity has attracted a lot of attention from all sides, and today's announcement of the coal industry's report card for de-capacity has really made people feel more worried.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这三个表层的因素还是反映出了过去我们的增长方式转变相对滞后的原因，就是由政府主导的增长方式至今还没有得到根本性的转变。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">These three superficial factors still reflect the lag in the change in our growth model, i.e., the government driven growth model has yet to experience a fundamental change to date.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">The three-layer factor reflects the relative lag of our growth patterns in the past, where the government-led growth pattern has not yet undergone a fundamental shift.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">These three superficial factors still reflect the fact that the transformation of our growth pattern has lagged behind in the past, that is, the government-led growth pattern has not yet been fundamentally transformed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第二，这也与地方政府的推进力度直接相关，在去产能的过程中，资金和相应的配套措施都要到位，从这个方面看来，不同地区的差异确实比较大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Second, it is directly related to the advance effort exerted by the local government. Cutting industrial overcapacity requires proper supportive measures which are varied in different places.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Second, this is directly related to the promotion of local government, in the process of going to capacity, funds and corresponding measures are to be in place, from this perspective, the difference between different regions is indeed relatively large.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Second, this is also directly related to the local government's efforts to promote, in the process of capacity removal, the funds and corresponding supporting measures have to be in place, from this perspective, the differences between different regions are indeed relatively large.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第三，如果目前进度比较慢的一些省份要在下半年赶进度，它们可能会面临较大的风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Third, if some of the provinces which are currently progressing at a slower rate expect to catch up in the second half, they would face bigger risks.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Third, if some of the provinces that are slower now are going to catch up in the second half of the year, they may face greater risks.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Third, some provinces that are currently making slower progress may be at greater risk if they are to catch up in the second half of the year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在这种情况下，依靠中央奖补资金来推进去产能的进程可能会产生一定负面的影响。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Under such straits, reliance on rewards and compensations from the central government to further increase production capacity will generate a certain degree of negative impact.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">In this case, the process of boosting the capacity by relying on the central prize for funding may have some negative effects.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">In this case, relying on central incentive funds to advance the process of capacity removal may have a certain negative impact.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>首先，去产能不是简单的进行总量控制。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">First, removing production capacity is not simply controlling total volume.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">First of all, go to capacity is not simple to carry out total control.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">First of all, capacity reduction is not simply a matter of total quantity control.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>我们的目的是要通过淘汰落后的产能，推进结构的优化，重构整个煤炭行业的新业态。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Our aim is to get rid of obsolete production capacity, achieve structural optimization, and re-organize the coal industry into a new business form.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Our aim is to reconstruct the new industry of the whole coal industry by eliminating backward production capacity and promoting structural optimization.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Our aim is to reconfigure the new format of the entire coal industry by eliminating backward production capacity and promoting the optimization of the structure.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在部署去产能的过程中，地方政府一定要把去产能和煤炭产业的转型升级结合起来，大力发展相关的服务业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">The local government, during the deployment of overcapacity cutting, shall combine the effort with the transformation of coal industry to drive the development of related service sector.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">In the process of deployment to capacity, the local government must combine the production capacity with the transformation and upgrading of the coal industry, and vigorously develop the related services.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">In the process of deploying desalination capacity, local governments must combine desalination capacity with the transformation and upgrading of the coal industry and vigorously develop the relevant service industries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>第二，要想在今年年内完成今年的去产能任务，我们还是要充分发挥行政监督和行政监察的力量。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Secondly, to complete the task of reducing production capacities this year, we must ensure thorough enforcement of our administrative supervision and administrative monitoring capacities.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Secondly, in order to complete this year's capacity task, we should give full play to the power of administrative supervision and administrative monitoring.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Second, if we want to complete this year's desalination task within this year, we still have to give full play to the strength of administrative supervision and administrative supervision.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>最后，我们要加强社会保障的兜底作用。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">Finally, we must strengthen miscellaneous provisions and functions of social programs.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Finally, we should strengthen the reveals role of social security.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Finally, we should strengthen the role of social security.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因为市场直接涉及到就业的问题，所以我们要加强对员工和职工的就业技能培训。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.ht">As the market is directly related to employment issues, we must strengthen employable skill training for the employees and vocational workers.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.gg">Because the market directly involves the problem of employment, we should strengthen the employment skills training for employees and workers.</translation>
    <translation system="078_ifeng0812.news.49766908_0_zh.c6">Because the market is directly related to the issue of employment, so we should strengthen the employment skills training for employees and workers.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
