<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.sl">
    <source>南湖公园水域管理科科长郑建军介绍，南湖水底最深处超过10米，不了解情况下水者，很可能发生危险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.ht">Zheng Jianjun, Director of Nanhu Park’s Water Management Department, said that Nanhu Lake exceeds 10 meters at its deepest. Swimmers unaware of the situation may be at risk.</translation>
    <translation system="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.gg">South Lake Park Water Management Section chief Zheng Jianjun Introduction, South Lake bottom depths of more than 10 meters, do not know the situation of the sewer, very likely to occur dangerous.</translation>
    <translation system="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.c6">Zheng Jianjun, head of the water management section of the South Lake Park, said that the deepest part of the South Lake is more than 10 meters, and those who do not understand the situation into the water are likely to be dangerous.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.sl">
    <source>“虽说南湖救援队非常专业，但仍希望广大划船的游客能穿上救生衣，在湖上不要做违规行动，安全游玩。”郑建军说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.ht">“Although the Nanhu Rescue Team is extremely professional, we hope that rowers can wear life vests and avoid illegal activities and actions on the lake to have a safe recreational experience.” said Zheng Jianjun.</translation>
    <translation system="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.gg">Although the South Lake Rescue Team is very professional, but still hope that the vast number of boating visitors can wear life jackets, in the lake do not do illegal acts, safe play. "said Zheng Jianjun.</translation>
    <translation system="124_xinhua0812..c_1119379209_zh.c6">"Although the South Lake rescue team is very professional, but still hope that the vast number of boating tourists can wear life jackets, not to do illegal actions on the lake, safe play," Zheng said.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
