<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿夫妇2015年收入为1075万美元，缴纳了34.2%的联邦税</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">The Clintons have an income of 10.75 million USD for 2015, and paid a Federal Tax of 34.2%.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">The Clintons paid $10.75 million for 2015 years, paying a 34.2% federal tax.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">The Clintons earned $10.75 million in revenue in 2015 and paid 34.2 percent in federal taxes</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>希拉里·克林顿于周五公布了其2105年的纳税申报单，申报单显示这位民主党总统候选人和她的丈夫2015年的收入为1075万美元，并且缴纳了34.2%的联邦税。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">On Friday, Hillary Clinton disclosed her tax returns of 2015. The document showed that the Democratic Party Presidential Candidate and her husband received an income of 10.75 million USD in 2015, and paid a federal tax of 34.2%.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Hillary Clinton published its 2,105-year tax return in Friday, which shows the Democratic presidential candidate and her husband earning $10.75 million in 2015 years and paying a 34.2% federal tax.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Hillary Clinton released her 2105 tax returns Friday showing the Democratic presidential nominee and her husband earned $10.75 million in 2015 and paid 34.2 percent in federal taxes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>2015年，克林顿夫妇的慈善捐款金额为100万美元，其中大部分捐助给了克林顿基金会；前总统比尔·克林顿的演讲费达到近530万美元，而前国务卿凭借一本关于她在国务院任职期间的书从出版商西蒙与舒斯特那里获得了300万美元的收入。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">In 2015, the Clintons gave 1 million US dollars as charitable donations, most of which were donated to The Clinton Foundation. Former President Bill Clinton’s speech fees amounted to nearly 5.30 million dollars, while the former Secretary of State received an income of 3.00 million dollars from the publisher Simon &amp; Schuster for her book about her job at the Department of State.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">In 2015, the Clintons ' charitable donations amounted to $1 million, most of which were donated to the Clinton Foundation; former President Bill Clinton's speech cost amounted to nearly 5.3 million dollars, The former secretary of state, with a book on her tenure at the State Department, received $3 million from the publisher, Simon and Schuster.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">In 2015, the Clintons made $1 million in charitable contributions, most of which went to the Clinton Foundation; former President Bill Clinton's speaking fees reached nearly $5.3 million, while the former secretary of state received $3 million from publishers Simon &amp; Schuster for a book about her tenure at the State Department.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿的竞选伙伴——弗吉尼亚州联邦国参议员蒂姆·凯恩和他的妻子安妮·霍尔顿公布了10年的纳税申报单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Clinton’s running mate, US Senator from Virginia Tim Kaine and his wife Anne Holton, publicly disclosed their tax returns for the last 10 years.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Clinton's running mate, Virginia State Kaine and his wife 安妮·霍尔顿, announced a 10-year tax return.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Clinton's running mate, Senator Tim Kaine of the Commonwealth of Virginia, and his wife, Anne Holden, released 10 years of tax returns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>两人2015年缴纳了20.3%的联邦税。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">The two paid 20.3% Federal tax in 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">The two men paid a federal tax of 20.3% in 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">The pair paid 20.3 percent in federal taxes in 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿的竞选助手詹妮弗·帕尔米耶里在一份声明中表示：希拉里·克林顿和蒂姆·凯恩将继续成为财务透明的标杆。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Clinton’s running mate Jennifer Palmieri expressed in another statement: Hillary Clinton and Tim Kaine shall continue to serve as beacons of financial transparency.”</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Clinton's campaign aide, 詹妮弗·帕尔米耶里, said in a statement: "Hillary Clinton and Kaine will continue to be the benchmark for financial transparency." ”</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">"Hillary Clinton and Tim Kaine will continue to be the benchmark for financial transparency," Clinton campaign aide Jennifer Palmieri said in a statement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>与之形成鲜明对比的是，唐纳德·特朗普以虚假的理由进行掩盖并且收回了他之前所作出的公布纳税申报单的承诺。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">In contrast, Donald Trump has used fake excuses as a cover up, and retracted his previous promise to release his tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">In stark contrast, Mr. Donald Trump concealed the false reasons and withdrew his previous commitment to publish the tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">In contrast, Donald Trump covered up on false grounds and retracted his earlier promise to release his tax returns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>虽然法律没有要求，但按照惯例，美国总统候选人应公开他们的纳税申报单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Although not legally required, it is customary for US presidential candidates to disclose their tax returns to the public.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Although the law is not required, in accordance with established practice, the United States presidential candidates should disclose their tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Though not required by law, it is customary for U.S. presidential candidates to make their tax returns public.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>作为一名纽约商人，特朗普以及他的律师将美国国税局的审计作为拒绝公布纳税申报单的理由。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">As a New York businessman, Trump and his lawyer have used the audit by the US Internal Revenue Service as an excuse to refuse to publicly disclose his tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">As a New York businessman, Trump and his lawyer used the IRS audit as a reason to refuse to publish a tax return.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">As a New York businessman, Trump, along with his lawyers, cited an IRS audit as a reason for refusing to release his tax returns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿竞选助手伊恩·萨姆斯在推特上表示由你们做主，并且附上了民主党候选人的纳税申报单链接。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Clinton's campaign staff Ian Sams expressed on Twitter that the people should decide, and provided links to the tax returns of the Democratic Party presidential candidate.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Clinton's campaign aide, 伊恩·萨姆斯, said on Twitter that you were the boss and attached a link to the Democratic candidate's tax return.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Clinton campaign aide Ian Summers tweeted that it's up to you and attached a link to the Democratic nominee's tax returns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>周四，特朗普的特别法律顾问迈克尔·科恩向CNN表示，在审计完成前他不会允许特朗普公布纳税申报单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">On Thursday, Michael Cohen, special legal counsel to Donald Trump, told the CNN that he will not allow Trump to disclose his tax returns before the audit is completed.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">In Thursday, Trump's special legal advisor, 迈克尔·科恩, told CNN that he would not allow Trump to publish his tax returns until the audit was completed.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">On Thursday, Trump's special counsel, Michael Cohen, told CNN that he would not allow Trump to release his tax returns until the audit is complete.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>批评特朗普的人，包括2012年共和党总统候选人米特·罗姆尼和其他共和党人表示特朗普拒绝公布纳税申报单会引发对其资本净值、慈善捐款、商业交易和各种其他关系的质疑，包括与俄罗斯的关系。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">People who criticize Trump include the 2012 Republican Party presidential candidate Mitt Romney and other Republicans who expressed that Trump’s refusal to publish his tax returns will lead to doubts regarding his net assets, charitable donations, business transaction, and other relationships, including his relationship with Russia.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Critics of Trump, including Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney and other Republicans in 2012, said Trump's refusal to publish tax returns would raise questions about his net worth, charitable donations, business deals and other relationships, including relations with Russia.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Critics of Trump, including 2012 Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney and other Republicans, said Trump's refusal to release his tax returns would raise questions about his net worth, charitable donations, business dealings and various other relationships, including with Russia.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿抓住这一问题猛烈抨击，于周五发布了一段网络视频，突出高调的民主党人敦促特朗普公布其纳税情况。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Clinton took aim at this issue, and released an online video on Friday, highlighting high-profile Democrats urging Trump to publicly release his tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Clinton seized on the issue and launched a network video in Friday highlighting High-profile Democrats urging Trump to announce his tax payments.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Clinton seized on the issue to lash out, releasing an online video on Friday highlighting high-profile Democrats urging Trump to release his tax returns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>周四，她在密歇根州的经济政策演讲中提出了这个问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">In Michigan State on Thursday, she mentioned this issue in a speech on economic policy.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">She raised the issue in an economic policy speech in Michigan in Thursday.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">She raised the issue Thursday during an economic policy speech in Michigan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>她对众人说：“几十年来，他拒绝像其他总统候选人那样公布自己的纳税申报单。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">She told the people: “For decades, he has refused to publish his tax returns as other presidential candidates had done before him.”</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">"For decades, he refused to publish his tax returns as other presidential candidates," she told the crowd. ”</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">"For decades, he refused to release his tax returns like other presidential candidates," she told the crowd.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>根据《政客新闻网》的报道，特朗普在上世纪九十年代有两年几乎没有缴纳过一分钱的税，《纽约时报》商业专栏作家于周五引用了多位税务律师和会计的话，他们均表示目前的情况可能依然如此。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Politico reported that Trump paid virtually no tax for two years in the 1990s. New York Times business columnists quoted many tax lawyers and accountants on Friday. They said that this may well be the case at this time.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">According to the politician's news network, Trump had barely paid a penny in the last two years of the 90, and the New York Times business columnist quoted a number of tax lawyers and accountants in Friday, all of whom said the current situation might remain the same.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">According to Politico News, Trump paid hardly a penny in taxes for two years in the 1990s, and the New York Times business columnist on Friday quoted a number of tax lawyers and accountants who said that might still be the case.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>联邦税已成为总统竞选中的一大问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Federal tax has become a major issue for presidential elections.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Federal taxes have become a big problem in the presidential race.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Federal taxes have become a big issue in the presidential campaign.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿用身价亿万的投资家沃伦·巴菲特的名字命名了一条规定，保证年收入超过100万美元的人至少缴纳30%的税。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Clinton named a rule after billionaire Warren Buffett, which ensured that a minimum tax rate of 30% will be applied on people who earned more than US$1 million in income.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Clinton named Warren Buffett, a billionaire investor, with a rule guaranteeing that people who earn more than $1 million a year pay at least a 30% tax.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Clinton named a rule after billionaire investor Warren Buffett, guaranteeing that people earning more than $1 million a year would pay at least 30 percent in taxes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>奥巴马总统也支持这项提议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">President Obama also supported this proposal.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">President Obama also supported the proposal.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">President Obama also supported the proposal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>上周，克林顿在伯克希尔·哈撒韦公司所在的内布拉斯加州奥马哈举行了一次集会，巴菲特在会上要求特朗普见面并交换纳税申报单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Last week, Clinton held a gathering at Omaha, Nebraska, the home of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. At the gathering, Warren Buffett asked for a meeting with Trump and to exchange tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Last week, Mr. Clinton held a rally at Berkshire Hathaway's Nebraska State Omaha, where Mr. Buffett asked Trump to meet and exchange tax returns.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Last week, Clinton held a rally in Omaha, Nebraska, where Berkshire Hathaway's company is based, where Buffett asked Trump to meet and exchange his tax returns.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>巴菲特表示，他也正在接受IRS的审计，特朗普“害怕的”不是税务机关，而是选民。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Buffet said that he is also being audited by the IRS at this time. What Trump is “afraid of” is not the tax authorities but voters.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Mr. Buffett said he was also being audited by the IRS, and Trump was "scared" not by tax authorities but by voters.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Mr Buffett said he was also being audited by the IRS, and that Mr Trump was "afraid" not of the tax authorities but of voters.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿竞选小组所公布的最早的纳税申报单为2007年。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">The earliest tax return Clinton’s election team disclosed was that of 2007.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">The first tax returns announced by the Clinton campaign group were 2007 years.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">The earliest tax returns released by the Clinton campaign are from 2007.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>目前居住在纽约查巴克的克林顿夫妇在2007年至2014年期间所缴纳的平均联邦税率达到约32%，综合税率约40.5%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">The Clintons, who now live in Chappaqua, New York, paid an average Federal tax rate of approximately 32%, and a combined tax rate of about 40.5% between 2007 and 2014.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">The average federal tax rate paid by the Clintons in Chaback, New York, between 2014 and 2007 amounted to about 32%, with a combined tax rate of about 40.5%.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">The Clintons, who currently live in Chabac, New York, paid an average federal tax rate of about 32 percent and a combined tax rate of about 40.5 percent between 2007 and 2014.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>克林顿夫妇2015年的纳税申报单显示，与大部分美国人不同，他们的工资收入只有100美元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Tax returns of the Clintons in 2015 showed that, unlike most Americans, they only received a salary of only 100 US dollars.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">The Clintons ' 2015-year tax returns show that, unlike most Americans, they earn only $100 in wages.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">The Clintons' 2015 tax returns show that, unlike most Americans, they are paid as little as $100.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>他们的主要投资是低成本的指数共同基金，并且克林顿夫妇的分红和利息收入为 109,000美元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Their primary investment is in a low-cost index fund, and the dividend and interest income Mr and Mrs Clinton received amounted to US$109,000.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">Their main investment is the low cost Index mutual fund, and the Clintons ' dividend and interest income is $109,000.</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Their main investments are low-cost index mutual funds, and the Clintons have a dividend and interest income of $109,000.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="160_reuters.165952_en.sl">
    <source>凯文·卓鲍报道；乔纳森·奥迪斯编辑</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.ht">Reported by Kevin Zobott and edited by Jonathan Otis</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.gg">凯文·卓鲍 report; 乔纳森·奥迪斯 Editor</translation>
    <translation system="160_reuters.165952_en.c6">Reporting by Kevin Chopper; Editing by Jonathan Ortiz</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
