<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>一户流氓家庭在遭驱逐前毁坏位于康沃尔郡索尔塔什的廉租房</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">A family of hooligans wrecked low-rent housing in Saltash Cornwall before being evicted</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">A family of rogue families destroyed a low-rent house in Sortas, Cornwall, before being deported.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">A rogue family destroys low-rent housing in Saltash, Cornwall, before being evicted</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>因恐吓邻居而遭驱逐的一户流氓家庭，在离开前对其所住廉租房进行了破坏，造成了50000英镑的损失。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">A family of miscreants who was evicted for terrorizing their neighbors vandalized their cheap rental property before leaving, causing a loss of 50,000 Sterling pounds.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">A family of rogue families who had been evicted for threatening their neighbours had damaged their low-rent housing before leaving, costing 50000 of pounds.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">A rogue family evicted for intimidating neighbours caused £50,000 in damage to their low-rent accommodation before leaving.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>在遭到一长串的投诉后，Tanya Skeldon 与其丈夫 Shaun Trebilcock 被赶出了位于康沃尔郡索尔塔什的廉租房。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">After receiving a long string of complaints, Tanya Skeldon and her husband Shaun Trebilcock were evicted from their cheap rental property located at Saltash in Cornwall County.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">After a long list of complaints, Tanya Skeldon and her husband, Shaun Trebilcock, were evicted from a low-rent house in the Cornish County of Sortas.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Tanya Skeldon and her husband Shaun Trebilcock were evicted from their low-rent house in Soltash, Cornwall, after a long list of complaints.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>在被强制从该住所遣离后，住房协会官员惊讶地发现这里遭到了严重破坏。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">The officials of housing association was stunned to discover the place was damaged severely after the forced evacuation.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">After being forcibly removed from the residence, housing association officials were surprised to find that there had been serious damage.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">After being forcibly removed from the residence, housing association officials were surprised to find that it had been severely damaged.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>墙上到处是洞，地板被扯破了，垃圾扔得满地都是，墙壁上被涂的乱七八糟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">The walls are covered with holes. The floor has been ripped up. Garbage is strewn everywhere, and there is graffiti all over the walls.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">The walls were full of holes, the floors torn, the rubbish strewn all over the floor, the walls smeared with clutter.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">There were holes all over the walls, the floor was ripped, garbage was thrown all over the floor, and the walls were covered in a mess.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>遭到驱逐后，这家人一直在搬家，据说目前住在私人住宅</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">The family has been moving after the evacuation. It was said they are lodging in a private residence.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">After being expelled, the family has been moving and is said to be living in a private house.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The family has been moving since being evicted and is said to be currently living in a private home</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>康沃尔郡住房协会房屋经理 Donna McEvoy 说，她担心这处房子已经无法挽救了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Donna McEvoy, housing manager at Cornwall Housing, said she feared the house would be beyond rescue.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Donna McEvoy, housing manager at Cornwall County Housing Association, said she feared the house could not be saved.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Donna McEvoy, housing manager for the Cornwall Housing Association, said she was concerned the house was beyond saving.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>她说：“对于住在这里的人们来说，这就是一场噩梦，我不认为人可以这样生活。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">She said, “For the people who live here, this is a nightmare. I don’t think people can live like that.”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">"It's a nightmare for people who live here, and I don't think people can live like this," she said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">"It's a nightmare for the people who live here, and I don't think people can live like that," she said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>现在有很多事情需要权衡，因为这处房屋很可能会成为康沃尔郡一个不太好的元素。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">There are many things that must be considered. This house may become a negative factor for Cornwall County.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">There are a lot of things to weigh now, because this House is likely to become a bad element in Cornwall.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">There are a lot of things to weigh in now because the house is likely to be a bad element in Cornwall.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>这户家庭臭名昭著，他们的名字同样臭名昭著。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">This family is infamous, and their name is equally notorious.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">The family is notorious and their names are equally notorious.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The family is notorious, and their names are equally notorious.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>这对夫妇有三个儿子，他们会不时住在这里。警方表示，这户人家的恐怖行为包括使用棒球棍在街头打架、恐吓附近居民、吸毒、贩毒、大喊大叫、争吵以及咒骂。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">This couple has 3 sons. They would live here every now and then. The police expressed that the household commits terror activities that include fighting in the street with baseball bats, intimidating nearby residents, drug abuse, drug dealing, shouting, arguing, and cursing.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">The couple had three sons and they would live here from time out. Police said the family's terrorist acts include the use of baseball bats in the streets to fight, intimidation of nearby residents, drugs, drug trafficking, shouting, quarrels and swearing.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The couple, who have three sons, will live here from time to time.Police said the family's terror included using baseball bats to fight in the streets, terrorising nearby residents, taking drugs, drug trafficking, shouting, arguing and swearing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>六月份，这位名叫 Skeldon 的47岁租客收到了一份反社会行为决议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">In June, a 47-year old renter named Skeldon received a resolution for his anti-social behaviors.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">In June, the 47-year-old tenant named Skeldon received a resolution on anti-social behavior.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The 47-year-old tenant, Skeldon, received an anti-social behaviour resolution in June.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>在这栋可能遭到拆除的房子里，许多房间都是放置许久的垃圾</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Trashed-filled rooms in a house that may be demolished</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">In a house that could be demolished, many of the rooms are long rubbish.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Many of the rooms in the house, which is likely to be demolished, are long standing rubbish</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>在这间曾经交易过毒品的房间里，地板被掀起来了</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Floorboards of the room where drugs were traded were lifted</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">In this room where the drugs were traded, the floors were lifted.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The floor was lifted in the room where the drugs had been sold</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>邻居称，经常看到他们在街头打架，也经常因此报警</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Neighboring residents said that they often see them fighting in the streets, and often called the police to deal with this.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Neighbors say they often see them fighting in the streets, and they often call the police</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Neighbours claimed they were often seen fighting in the streets and often called police over the incident</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>在给了11周的延长期让他们自愿搬离后，康沃尔郡住房协会本周强行将她与她的丈夫驱离该住所。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">After giving an 11-week extension to voluntarily leave the place, the Cornwall County Residential Authority forcibly evicted her and her husband from their residence this week.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">After giving them a 11-week extension, the Cornish Housing Society forced her and her husband to drive away from the house this week.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The Cornwall Housing Society this week forcibly removed her from the residence with her husband after giving them an 11-week extension to move voluntarily.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>终于松了口气的邻居们为此欢呼不已，他们表示，之前的生活简直是人间地狱。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Neighbors who finally breathed a sign of relief cheered because of this. They said that life in the past was a living hell.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">The neighbors, who finally breathed a sigh of joy, said that life had been a living hell.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Neighbours who were finally relieved cheered, saying that life had been a living hell.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>一位邻居说道：“他们不在乎任何人。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">A neighbor said: “They don't care about anyone.”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">"They don't care about anyone," said one neighbour. ”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">"They don't care about anyone," said one neighbour.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>我们在他们隔壁住了20年，一直这么糟糕。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">We lived next to them for 20 years. It’s been terrible all this time.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">We've lived next door to them for 20 years, and it's been so bad.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">We've been living next door to them for 20 years and it's been so bad.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>我们曾无数次看到警察登门。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">We have seen the police come by many times.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">We've seen the police countless times.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">We've seen the police at the door countless times.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>“今天早晨，我们竟睡不着了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">“We couldn’t sleep this morning.”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">"We couldn't sleep this morning." ”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">"This morning we couldn't sleep.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>我们早早就起床了，因为这里太安静了——我们还不习惯呢！</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">We woke up early because it was just too quiet. We are not used to this yet!</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">We got up early because it was so quiet-we weren't used to it!</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">We get up early because it's so quiet here - we're not used to it yet!</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>他们终于走了，真是太好了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">They finally left. Thank goodness.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">It's very kind of them to leave at last.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">It's great that they're finally gone.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>康沃尔郡住房协会社区执行经理 Adam Fitzpatrick 说道，这户人家没能好好配合当地政府。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Cornwall Housing's neighborhood enforcement manager Adam Fitzpatrick said that this family failed to cooperate with the local government.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Fitzpatrick, the Community executive manager of the Cornish Housing Society, said the family had failed to cooperate with the local government.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Adam Fitzpatrick, community executive manager of the Cornwall Housing Association, said the family had failed to cooperate with the local government.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>这家人在这所房子里住了20年，警察经常造访</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">The family lived in this house for 20 years and has been frequented by the police</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">The family lived in the house for 20 years and the police often visited</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The family has lived in the house for 20 years and is regularly visited by police</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>垃圾和旧玩具被扔在该廉租房杂草丛生的一边</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Rubbish and old toys are thrown at the side of the low-rent housing project where weeds are overgrown</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Rubbish and old toys were tossed over the overgrown side of the low-rent rent</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Garbage and old toys were thrown on the overgrown side of the tenement</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>他补充说：“令人遗憾的是，该房客没有为她与家人的行为而负任何责任，驱逐是康沃尔郡住房协会最后考虑的做法。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">He added: “What is disappointing is that the tenant did not bear any responsibility for the actions that she and her family members have committed. Eviction is the final measure considered by the Cornwall residence committee.”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">He added: "It is regrettable that the tenant has not been held responsible for the conduct of her family and the expulsion is the last thing considered by the Cornwall Housing Association." ”</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">He added: "It is regrettable that the tenant did not take any responsibility for her behaviour with her family and the eviction was the last thing the Cornwall Housing Association considered."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>这是一起非常难处理的案件，因为他们的行为非常极端，而他们的所作所为也一定让邻居们感到万分恐惧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">This is a very difficult case to handle because their behavior was rather extreme. What they did must have terrified the neighbors.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">This is a very difficult case to deal with, because their behavior is very extreme, and what they do must make the neighbors feel extremely terrified.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">It was a very difficult case to deal with because their behaviour was so extreme and what they were doing must have been extremely frightening for the neighbours.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>我感谢我的团队所做的工作，也要感谢德文郡与康沃尔郡警方以及勇敢向我们提供信息的社区成员。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">I thank my team for the work they have done. I also want to thank the Devon and Cornwall Police as well as members of the community who have courageously provided us with information.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">I am thankful for the work done by my team and thanks to the Devon and Cornwall Police as well as the community members who are brave enough to provide us with information.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">I thank my team for their work, as well as Devon and Cornwall Police and members of the community who have been brave enough to provide us with information.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>我希望此举将给邻居们带来些许安慰，并传递这样一个信息：我们对反社会行为绝不容忍。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">I hope that this act will bring some comfort to the neighborhood, and transmit this message: We shall not tolerate anti-social behavior.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">I hope this will bring some comfort to our neighbors and convey the message that we are not tolerant of anti-social behaviour.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">I hope this will provide some comfort to our neighbours and send a message that we will not tolerate anti-social behaviour.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>Fitzpatrick 先生表示，他们的三个儿子在不同时期都在这个房子里住过，但是也说了，他们都才20多岁。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Mr. Fitzpatrick expressed that their three sons have lived in this house at different times, but he also added that they're only in their twenties.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Mr Fitzpatrick says three of their sons lived in the house at different times, but said they were only more than 20 years old.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Mr Fitzpatrick said their three sons had lived in the house at various times, but said they were all in their 20s.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>在他们遭驱离后，其中一间卧室的地板上还扔着一个脏床垫</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">After they were evicted, a dirty mattress was left on the floor of one of the bedrooms</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">After they were driven away, one of the bedroom floors was littered with a dirty mattress.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">A dirty mattress was also thrown on the floor of one of the bedrooms after they were removed</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>住房协会工人很快将清理房子周围成堆的垃圾</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Housing association workers swiftly cleaned up heaps of garbage around the house</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Housing association workers will soon be cleaning up piles of rubbish around the house</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Housing association workers will soon be clearing piles of rubbish around the house</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="34" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>2014年，警方曾搜查了该房屋，发现了70多克大麻，还发现了天平、吸毒用具及1,700英镑现金。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">In 2014, police had searched this house and found more than 70 grams of marijuana, as well as scales, drug kits and GPB1,700 in cash.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">In 2014, police raided the house, found more than 70 grams of cannabis, and found scales, drug paraphernalia and 1,700 pounds of cash.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">In 2014, police had searched the house and found 70 grams of marijuana, as well as scales, drug paraphernalia and £1,700 in cash.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="35" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>认罪后，Skeldon 因持有 B 类毒品及贩卖毒品意图被处以罚款。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">After pleading guilty, Skeldon was fined for possession of Class B drugs and intent to traffick drugs.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">After pleading guilty, Skeldon was fined for possessing class B drugs and drug trafficking.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">After pleading guilty, Skeldon was fined for possession of Class B drugs and trafficking in drugs with intent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="36" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>她声称，钱是用来给2013年死于车祸的儿子 Lee Skeldon 买墓碑的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">She claimed that the money would be used to buy a headstone for her son, Lee Skeldon, who died in a car accident in 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">She claims that the money was used to buy gravestones for the son Lee Skeldon, who died in a car accident in 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">She claimed the money was used to buy a tombstone for her son, Lee Skeldon, who died in a car crash in 2013.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="37" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>据了解，在无家可归后，Tanya 与其丈夫现在住在普利茅斯的一处私人房屋。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">From our understanding, after losing her home, Tanya and her husband is now residing at a private house at Plymouth.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">It is understood that after homeless, Tanya and her husband now live in a private house in Plymouth.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">It is understood Tanya and her husband now live in a private house in Plymouth after becoming homeless.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="38" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>该住房多间房间的墙上都画满了涂鸦。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Graffiti littered the walls of many of the rooms in this residence.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">The walls of the house were painted with graffiti.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">The walls of many of the rooms in the house were covered with graffiti.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="39" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>警方表示，他们将驱逐违抗租户规则的租客。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">The police expressed that they will evict any tenant who violate the tenants’ rule of conduct.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Police said they would expel tenants who defied tenant rules.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Police said they would evict tenants who defied the tenants' rules.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="40" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>德文郡与康沃尔郡警局的 Angela Crow 表示，此次驱逐向其他继续违抗租户规则的租客发出了明确警告。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Angela Crow of the police department of Devon and Cornwall said that this eviction will send a clear warning to tenants who continue to violate the tenants’ code of conduct.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Angela Crow, of Devon and the Cornish Police Department, said the eviction sent a clear warning to other tenants who continued to defy tenant rules.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Angela Crow, of Devon and Cornwall Police, said the eviction issued a clear warning to other tenants who continued to defy tenant rules.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="41" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>“这一警告针对的是那些认为自己的行为不会受到指责，以及那些受这种行为摧残的人们，”她说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">“This warning is directed as those who think that nobody will complain about their behaviors, and for people who were victimized by such behaviors,” she said.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">"The warning is for people who think their actions are not being blamed, and those who have been devastated by this behavior," she said.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">"This warning is for people who don't think they're going to be blamed for their actions, and for people who have been devastated by it," she said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="42" doc-id="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.sl">
    <source>德文郡与康沃尔郡警局绝不容忍犯罪与反社会行为，他们将继续携手合作伙伴保护我们的社区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.ht">Police departments of Devon and Cornwall tolerate zero criminal and anti-social activity. They will continue protecting our community with partners.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.gg">Devon and Cornwall Police will never tolerate crime and anti-social behaviour, and they'll continue to work with partners to protect our communities.</translation>
    <translation system="017_dailymail.co.uk.170822_en.c6">Devon and Cornwall Police do not tolerate crime and anti-social behaviour and will continue to work with partners to protect our communities.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
