<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>连续熬夜看奥运赛事容易损伤心脏</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">Staying up all night to watch the Olympics makes one prone to heart damage</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">Staying up late watching Olympic Games can easily damage the heart</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">Staying up late to watch the Olympics can damage your heart</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>巴西奥运会赛事正如火如荼地进行，即便赛事播出时在国内是半夜时分，很多市民也会熬夜观看。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">The Olympic games in Brazil are currently all the rage. Even though many of the games are broadcast during midnight hours in China, many fellow citizens will stay up all night to watch these games.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">The Brazilian Olympic Games are in full swing, even if the event is broadcast at home in the middle of the night, many people will stay up to watch.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">Brazil's Olympic events are in full swing, and many citizens will stay up to watch them even if they are broadcast in the middle of the night in the country.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>对此，医生特别提醒，熬夜看赛事存在健康隐患，有可能引发心血管疾病。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">For this, doctors specifically mind people that staying up all night to watch TV sports events may be potentially hazardous to health and could lead to cardiovascular diseases.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">In this respect, doctors especially remind, stay up late to watch the event there is a health hazard, it is possible to cause cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">In response, doctors specifically warned that staying up late to watch the tournament had health hazards that could potentially trigger cardiovascular disease.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>如果长时间熬夜，该激素仍会大量分泌，人体会持续处于紧张兴奋的状态，无法得到正常的恢复，容易引起血管收缩、血压升高，从而引起心血管疾病。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">For people staying up late into the night, the hormone will be secreted in large volumes, keeping one energized and in a state of alertness. However, such people won't be able to rest properly and are prone to vasoconstriction, increased blood pressure, and tendency to suffer from cardiovascular diseases.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">If long stay up late, the hormone will still be a lot of secretion, the human body will continue to be in a state of intense excitement, can not get normal recovery, easy to cause vasoconstriction, blood pressure rise, resulting in cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">If you stay up for a long time, the hormone will still be secreted in large quantities, the human experience continues to be in a state of tension and excitement, unable to get a normal recovery, easy to cause vasoconstriction, blood pressure rise, and thus cause cardiovascular disease.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>韩志远特别提醒，有高血压、高血糖、高血脂、吸烟习惯、家族病史等心血管危险因素的群体，如果熬夜，会更容易引发心血管疾病。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">Han Zhiyuan issued a special reminder to groups with high blood pressure, high blood sugar, high cholesterol, a smoking habit, a family medical history and other cardiovascular risk factors that if they stay up late, they would easily trigger cardiovascular illness.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">Hanzhiyuan Special reminder, there are hypertension, hyperglycemia, hyperlipidemia, smoking habits, family history and other cardiovascular risk factors, if staying up late, will be more likely to cause cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">Han specifically cautioned that groups with cardiovascular risk factors such as high blood pressure, high blood sugar, high blood lipids, smoking habits and family history were more likely to develop cardiovascular disease if they stayed up late.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>如果长期熬夜，不仅心血管功能受影响，而且胃肠功能、免疫系统、神经内分泌系统都会受影响，甚至罹患肿瘤的风险也会增大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">Staying up late over a long period of time will not only affect one’s cardiovascular function but also one’s gastrointestinal function, immune system and neuroendocrine system; even the risk of getting cancer will increase.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">If long stay up late, not only cardiovascular function is affected, and gastrointestinal function, immune system, neuroendocrine system will be affected, even the risk of cancer will increase.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">Staying up late for long periods of time not only affects cardiovascular function, but also gastrointestinal function, the immune system, the neuroendocrine system, and even the risk of developing tumors.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>对于老年朋友，韩志远建议，尽量不要为了看奥运比赛而熬夜，特别是有心血管疾病史的群体。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">For fellow senior citizens, Han Zhiyuan recommend avoiding staying up all night to watch the Olympics, especially those who have a history of cardiovascular diseases.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">For old friends, Hanzhiyuan advises, try not to stay up late to watch the Olympic Games, especially with a history of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">For older friends, Han suggests trying not to stay up late to watch the Olympics, especially for groups with a history of cardiovascular disease.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>在上届“世界杯”足球赛期间，韩志远曾接诊过一名60多岁的患者，其心肌梗塞的引发或与熬夜看比赛有关。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">During the previous “FIFA World Cup”, Han Zhiyuan saw a patient in his sixties who suffered a heart attack for staying up late to watch the matches.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">During the last "World Cup" football match, Hanzhiyuan had a more than 60-year-old patient who had a heart attack or was linked to staying up late watching the game.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">During the last World Cup, Han Zhiyuan had seen a patient in his 60s whose heart attack was triggered or related to staying up late to watch the game.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>韩志远介绍，今年以来，其科室已接诊了一些25岁左右的心肌梗塞或者脑中风患者，这很大程度上是患者长期熬夜的生活方式造成的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">Han Zhiyuan said that since the beginning of this year, the department has admitted a number of patients aged 25 years or so with myocardial infraction or stroke. This, to a very large extent, was the result of a lifestyle of staying up late over long periods.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">Hanzhiyuan introduced, this year, the department has been in the reception of some 25-year-old myocardial infarction or stroke patients, which is largely the patient's long stay up late lifestyle caused.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">Han Zhiyuan said that so far this year, its departments have received some 25-year-old patients with myocardial infarction or stroke, which is largely due to the patient's long stay up late lifestyle.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>1.不要每天都熬夜，偶尔熬夜观看最喜欢的体育项目，其他项目不妨等第二天看赛事重播。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">1. Do not stay up every night. People can stay up once in a while to watch their favorite sports event, but try waiting for the second day replay for other events.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">1. Do not stay up every day, occasionally stay up late to watch the favorite sports events, other items may wish to wait for the second day to watch the replay.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">Don't stay up late every day, occasionally stay up late to watch your favorite sports, other sports might as well wait until the next day to watch the replay of the event.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.sl">
    <source>2.熬夜时适时补充水分，多吃水果，可预防血管堵塞、增强机体免疫力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.ht">2. When staying up late at night, drink enough water and eat lots of fruits to prevent the clogging of blood vessels and to enhance systemic immunity.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.gg">2. Stay up late when the timely replenishment of water, eat more fruit, can prevent blockage of blood vessels, enhance the body's immune power.</translation>
    <translation system="129_peopledaily0812.health.c404177-28631549_zh.c6">2. Stay up late when the timely replenishment of water, eat more fruits, can prevent blockage of blood vessels, enhance the body's immune system.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
