<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>近日，河北省慈孝基金将16000元慰问金送到井陉县小作、台头、贵泉等村6户失亲家庭手中。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">Recently, the Cixiao Foundation of Hebei Province has delivered consolation money of 16,000 RMB to 6 families at the villages of Xiaozuo, Taitou, and Guiquan in Jingjing County who had lost a loved one.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">Recently, Hebei Province Tzu-filial fund will be 16000 yuan condolences to Jingxing County small, Taiwan head, your spring and other villages 6 families lost their hands.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">Recently, the Hebei Province Compassion Fund sent 16,000 yuan to Jingxing County Xiaozuo, Taitou, Guiquan and other villages in the hands of six families who lost their families.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这是该基金向社会发出寻找“7.19洪灾中失亲少年儿童和孤独老人”启示后的又一次慰问关爱行动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">This is yet another consolation and care campaign initiated by the Fund after their previous search for “Lost Youths, Children, and Elderly Victims of the July 19 Flood”.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">This is the foundation of the Fund to the community to find "7.19 floods in the loss of children and lonely elderly" after the revelation of another caring action.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">This is the Fund to the community to find "7.19 floods in the bereaved children and lonely elderly" after the revelation of another act of sympathy and care.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>7.19强降雨致使河北省多地受灾，造成省内部分地区出现洪涝灾害，并出现人员死亡和失踪。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">Heavy rain on July 19 affected multiple areas in Hebei Province, leading to floods to parts of the province with people going missing and dying as a result.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">7.19 heavy rains caused many disasters in Hebei province, causing floods in some parts of the province, and people died and disappeared.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">7.19 Heavy rainfall has affected many areas of Hebei Province, causing flooding in some areas of the province, as well as deaths and disappearances.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>好人“老铁”因帮助小区义务排水不幸牺牲，留下2岁的幼儿和身怀六甲的妻子，好人“老铁”的感人事迹感动了整个省城。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">The good man “Old Iron” lost his life when volunteering for a drainage project for his community, leaving behind a 2-year old son and a pregnant wife. The story of good “Old Iron” quickly moved the entire provincial town.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">Good people "old iron" due to help the community obligation drainage unfortunate sacrifice, leaving 2-year-old children and pregnant wife, good people "old iron" touching deeds moved the entire provincial capital.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">Good man "old iron" for helping the community duty drainage unfortunate sacrifice, leaving a 2-year-old toddler and pregnant wife, good man "old iron" sentimental touched the entire provincial city.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月4日，河北省慈孝基金工作人员和河北品牌会志愿者一起来到好人“老铁”家中，把3200元爱心款交到“老铁”的家人手里。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">On August 4, work personnel from the Hebei Province Cixiao Fund and volunteers of the Hebei brand association arrived at good “Old Iron’s” home to deliver a charity fund of 3,200 RMB to his surviving family members.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">August 4, Hebei Province Tzu Chi Fund staff and Hebei brand volunteers came together to the good people "old Iron" home, the 3200 yuan love to the "Old iron" family hand.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">August 4, Hebei Province, the staff of the Compassion Fund and Hebei Brand Association volunteers came to the good people "Lao Tie" home, the 3200 yuan of love money to "Lao Tie" in the hands of the family.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>当品牌会副会长叶莉了解到“老铁”家人的现状后，当即决定在品牌会的企业会员里开展“爱心义卖”活动，帮助“老铁”家人共度难关。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">When Ye Li, vice director of the brand association, learned about the conditions faced by the family members of “Old Iron”, she decided to initiate a “Charity Sales” event amongst corporate members in the brand association to help the “Old Iron's” family members make it through the tough times.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">When the vice president of the brand Li Ye understand the "old iron" family status, immediately decided in the brand will be the enterprise members to carry out "love bazaar" activities to help "old iron" family to tide over the difficulties.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">When the brand will vice president Ye Li learned about the status of the "old iron" family, immediately decided in the brand will be the enterprise members to carry out "love charity" activities to help the "old iron" family to tide over difficulties.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.sl">
    <source>河北省慈孝基金，全称为河北省志愿服务基金会·慈孝基金，由河北品牌会筹委会发起，成立于2015年8月。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.ht">The Hebei Province Cixiao Fund, also known by its full name as the Hebei Province Volunteer Service Foundation - Cixiao Fund, was founded in August 2015 by the organizing committee of Hebei Brand Association.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.gg">Hebei Province Tzu-filial fund, the full name of the Voluntary Service foundation of Hebei province, Tzu-filial fund, by the Hebei brand will be launched by the Preparatory Committee, founded in August 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="047_ifeng0812.news.49765246_0_zh.c6">The Hebei Province Compassion Fund, known as the Hebei Province Voluntary Service Foundation · Compassion Fund, was launched by the Hebei Brand Association Preparatory Committee and was established in August 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
