<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据台湾媒体报道，台“行政院长”林全昨天上午宣布，“政党及其附随组织不当取得财产处理条例”自今天起生效。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">Taiwan media reported that Taiwan “Legislative Yuan Premier” Lin Chuan announced yesterday morning that the “Rule for Managing Ill-gotten Assets by Political Parties and Their Affiliates” will become effective from today.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">Taiwan's chief executive, Lin Quan, announced yesterday morning that the "political parties and their accompanying organization's improper acquisition of property regulations" came into effect today, according to Taiwanese media reports.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">Taiwan's "Executive Premier" Lin Quan announced yesterday morning that "the regulations governing the improper acquisition of property by political parties and their affiliated organizations" will take effect from today, according to Taiwanese media reports.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>国民党副主席詹启贤则表示，“一个一百多年历史的国民党，有社会的承诺跟责任，不会这样就倒闭”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">Steve Chan, Vice Chairman of the Kuomintang said, “With a history of more than a century, the Kuomintang has social commitment and responsibility, and will not collapse just like that.”</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">KMT vice chairman Jianghi said, "a more than 100-year-old Kuomintang, with social commitment and responsibility, will not fail in this way."</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">Zhan Qixian, vice chairman of the Kuomintang, said: "A Kuomintang with a history of more than 100 years has social commitments and responsibilities, and will not fail in this way."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>林全强调，如果政党、附随组织或受托管理人等违反条例所定禁止处分的规定，委员会将依职权调查并“依法”处分、裁罚。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">Lin Chuan emphasized that any political party, affiliated organization, or commissioned manager who violates the penalty provisions of the Act, the member of the Committee shall exercise their duties and enforce punishment and penalties in “accordance with the law”.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">Lin Quan stressed that if a political party, an affiliated organization or a trustee manager, etc. violate the provisions of the prohibition imposed by the regulations, the Commission shall investigate and punish the penalty according to the terms of reference.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">Lin stressed that if political parties, affiliated organizations or trustees violate the prohibition against punishment stipulated in the regulations, the committee will investigate ex officio and punish them "in accordance with the law."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>林全也宣布不当党产委员会的副主委人选，将由台“廉政署副署长”洪培根担任。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">Lin Chuan also announced that Hung Pai-ken, Taiwan’s “Agency Against Corruption Deputy Director-General”, will be the Vice Chairman candidate for the Ill-gotten Party Assets Settlement Committee.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">Lin Quan also announced that the Vice-Chairman of the party's production committee would be appointed by Hongpegen, deputy director of the ICAC.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">Lin also announced that he would not be the vice chairman of the party's property committee, and that Hung Pei-kan, Taiwan's "deputy director of the Independent Commission Against Corruption," would be appointed to the post.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他说，由顾立雄担任不当党产委员会主委是不二人选，借用洪培根过去查察相关重大案件的经验，将作为委员会清查相关不当党产案件的基础。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">He said that Koo Li-hsiung is the best pick as the chairperson of the Ill-gotten Party Assets Settlement Committee. Koo shall make use of Hung Pei-ken’s experiences in handling major cases of similar nature and use the experiences as the basis for investigating cases related to ill-gotten party assets.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">He said that Koo as the Main Committee of the Commission is the only candidate, borrowing Hongpegen in the past to examine the relevant major cases of experience, will be the Committee to inventory the relevant cases of improper party production basis.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">He said that Gu Lixiong is the only person to serve as the chairman of the inappropriate party property committee. Borrowing from Hong Bacon's past experience in inspecting relevant major cases, it will serve as the basis for the committee to identify relevant cases of improper party property.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>詹启贤认为，今天只要还有党产，没有人会给你社会捐款，若党产统统被充公收走，国民党刚好可请求社会支持与赞助，“今天真的没有了才有机会去要”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">Steve Chan believed that as long as party assets exist today, no one will give public donations. If party assets were to be completely confiscated, this would be just the right time for the Kuomintang to ask for public support and sponsorship. “Only if we have nothing today will we have the opportunity to ask”.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">Jianghi believes that today, as long as there is party production, no one will give you social donations, if the party produced all confiscated away, the Kuomintang just can request social support and sponsorship, "Today really do not have the opportunity to go."</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">Jen Chih-hsien believes that as long as there are still party properties today, no one will give you social donations. If all party properties are confiscated and taken away, the Kuomintang can just ask for social support and sponsorship.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.sl">
    <source>詹启贤也强调，就算不当党产条例上路后，国民党党产没被完全充公、没收，剩下的仍会依承诺捐出去，让党产准归零，党要一切从零开始。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.ht">Chan Chi-hsien emphasized that even if the act on handling ill-gotten party assets is enforced, any remaining Kuomintang asset that has yet to be fully nationalized or confiscated shall be donated according to his promise. Kuomintang assets shall be completely liquidated for the Party to start from square one.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.gg">Jianghi also stressed that even if improper party production regulations on the road, the Kuomintang party production has not been completely confiscated, confiscated, the rest will still be pledged to give out, so that the party to zero, the party should all start from scratch.</translation>
    <translation system="130_ifeng0812.news.49765646_0_zh.c6">Zhan Qixian also stressed that even if improper party property regulations on the road, the Kuomintang party property has not been completely confiscated, confiscated, the rest will still be donated in accordance with the commitment, so that the party will return to zero, the party should start from scratch.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
