<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据中国之声《新闻晚高峰》报道，8月下旬，日本首相安倍晋三将赴肯尼亚出席第六届非洲开发会议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">According to Evening Peak News of Voice of China, Shinzō Abe, Prime Minister of Japan, will attend the Sixth Tokyo International Conference on African Development to be held in Kenya at the end of August.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">In late August, Japan's prime minister, Shinzo Abe, is to attend the sixth session of the African Development Conference in Kenya, according to the Chinese voice, news of the evening peak.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">In late August, Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe will travel to Kenya to attend the sixth African Development Conference, according to the Voice of China's Newsnight Summit.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>非洲开发会议由日本主导，此前的五次会议均是在日本东京或者横滨举行，因此，本次会议也将是首次移师非洲。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">The Conference of Africa's Development is organized by Japan. The first five sessions of this Conference were held in the Japanese cities of Tokyo or Yokohama. This will therefore be the first session of the Conference held in Africa.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">The African development Conference, dominated by Japan, was preceded by five meetings in Tokyo or Yokohama, so the conference will be the first to move to Africa.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">The Conference on African Development, led by Japan, will also be the first to move to Africa, as all five previous meetings have been held in Tokyo or Yokohama, Japan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日本外务省官员就此表示，在非洲当地召开会议有助于引起非洲和欧洲各国对日本的关注。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">As regards this, an official of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Japan said that convening a conference locally in Africa helps attract the attention of African and European nations with regard to Japan.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Japanese Foreign ministry officials said the local meeting in Africa helped draw attention from African and European countries to Japan.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">In this regard, Japanese Foreign Ministry officials said that local meetings in Africa to help draw the attention of African and European countries to Japan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>为了配合安倍晋三的此次出访，据共同社消息，日本自民党将向相关各国派遣议员团。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">To support Shinzo Abe’s visit, reports from Kyodo News said that the Liberal Democratic Party of Japan will be sending representative delegations to various countries.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">To coincide with Mr. Abe's three visit, the LDP will send a parliamentary group to the countries concerned, according to Kyodo News.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">To coincide with Abe's trip, the Liberal Democratic Party of Japan will send parliamentary groups to relevant countries, according to Kyodo news agency.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日本“入常”之路始于上世纪90年代初，而由日本发起的非洲开发会议同样始于1993年，这不是巧合！</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">Japan’s path to “become a permanent member” began in the early 1990s, and the Tokyo International Conference on African Development hosted by Japan began in 1993 as well; this was by no means a coincidence!</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">It is no coincidence that Japan's "frequent" road began in the early 90, when the African Development Conference, launched by Japan, also started in 1993.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">It is no coincidence that Japan's path to "business as usual" began in the early 1990s, while the African Development Conference, initiated by Japan, also began in 1993!</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>非洲在联合国拥有53个席位，是联合国的重要票仓，日本要想“入常”，又怎么会舍弃非洲？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">African countries occupy 53 seats in the United Nations, making the continent an important source of votes in the UN. If Japan wants to enter the Permanent Security Council, it cannot afford to forget Africa.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Africa has 53 seats in the United Nations and is an important ticket for the United Nations, and how can Japan abandon Africa if it wants to be "regular"?</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">With 53 seats in the United Nations, Africa is an important vote holder of the United Nations. How can Japan abandon Africa if it wants to become a permanent member of the United Nations?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>还将与各国相关人士就极端组织“伊斯兰国”及恐怖活动对策交换意见。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">Opinions regarding the extremist “Islamic State” organization and terrorist activities were also exchanged with relevant representatives from various countries.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">An exchange of views will also be exchanged with interested parties on the extreme organization of "Islamic States" and terrorist tactics.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">It will also exchange views with relevant people from various countries on the extremist group Islamic State and the response to terrorist activities.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“西部组”将访问塞拉利昂、利比里亚、几内亚比绍等7个国家。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">The “western division” shall visit 7 countries such as Sierra Leone, Liberia, and Guinea-Bissau.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">The Western Group will visit 7 countries, including Sierra Leone, Liberia and Guinea-Bissau.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">The "Western Group" will visit Sierra Leone, Liberia, Guinea-Bissau and seven other countries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日本外相岸田文雄近来也在联合国安理会上就此次非洲开发会议说明了意图。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">The Japanese foreign minister Fumio Kishida also disclosed his aims during this session of conference on African development at the United Nations Security Council meeting.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Japan's foreign-Kishida bank has also recently stated its intentions in the UN Security Council on the African Development Conference.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">Japanese Foreign Minister Fumio Kishida recently stated his intention on the African Development Conference at the United Nations Security Council.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>安倍曾在此间宣布，为了撒哈拉沙漠以南非洲国家的稳定，将在5年内提供1000亿日元（约合人民币61亿元）的援助。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">During this period, Abe announced that in order to ensure stability to sub-Saharan African countries, Japan will provide an aid of 100 billion Japanese Yen (approximately equivalent to 6.1 billion RMB) across a period of 5 years.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Mr Abe has announced here that it will provide 100 billion yen (about 6.1 billion yuan) of aid in 5 years for the stability of sub-Saharan African countries.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">Abe announced here that he would provide 100 billion yen (6.1 billion yuan) in aid over five years for the sake of stability in sub-Saharan African countries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>观察人士普遍认为，一直以来，日本对非洲的慷慨主要有两个目的：一是增加日本在非洲的存在感；二是争取在入常问题上赢得非洲国家的支持。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">Observers generally believe that there are two main objectives for Japan's generosity to Africa all this time: The first is to increase Japan’s existence in Africa, and the second is to win the support of African nations for its bid to become a permanent member of the UN Security Council.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Observers generally believe that Japan has been generous to Africa for two purposes: to increase Japan's sense of presence in Africa and to win the support of African countries on the issue.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">Observers generally agree that Japan's generosity toward Africa has always had two main purposes: to increase Japan's sense of presence in Africa; and to try to win support from African countries on the issue of membership.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日本问题专家杨伯江分析称，“从政治方面，非洲虽然相对发展滞后，但是国家数量比较多，所以日本一向把它视为所谓的‘大票田’。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">Yang Bojiang, an expert on Japan-related issues, analyzed and concluded, “From a political perspective, Africa may lag in terms of development on a relative basis, but it has a large number of countries. Japan has always regarded it as a ‘major source of votes’.”</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">"From a political point of view, Africa, although relatively underdeveloped, has a larger number of countries, so Japan has always regarded it as a so-called ' large field, '" said Yang Bojiang, a Japanese expert. ”</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">"Politically, Africa is relatively underdeveloped, but it has a large number of countries, so Japan has always regarded it as the so-called 'big vote field,'" said Yang Bojiang, an expert on Japan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>今后日本是不会放弃的，对于非洲的工作也不会就此终止，会不断加强。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">In the future, Japan will not be abandoning this. They will continue to strengthen their work in Africa and will not give it up.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">In the future, Japan will not give up, and its work on Africa will not be terminated.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">Japan will not give up in the future, and its work on Africa will not stop there, and it will continue to be strengthened.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>经济方面，因为日本的生产能力比较强，但是国内市场相对有限，特别是目前在少子老龄化背景下，内需相对比较低迷。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">In terms of economy, Japan has stronger production capacity, but its domestic market is somewhat limited, especially given the low birth rate and aging population that have resulted in a comparatively low internal demand.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Economic aspect, because Japan's production capacity is relatively strong, but the domestic market is comparatively limited, especially at present in the background of the minority aging, domestic demand is relatively depressed.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">On the economic front, because Japan's production capacity is relatively strong, but the domestic market is relatively limited, especially in the context of the aging of children, domestic demand is relatively low.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>不过，从10年前的小泉纯一郎，到10年后的安倍，其间，日本曾多次发起的入常“冲刺”，却均铩羽而归。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">However, from Junichiro Koizumi 10 years ago to Abe 10 years later, Japan has initiated several “dashing attempts” to enter the UN Permanent Security Council, all of which has ended in failure.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">However, from Junichiro Koizumi, 10 ago, to Abe, 10 years later, Japan has repeatedly launched the "sprint", but all failed to return.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">However, from Junichiro Koizumi 10 years ago to Abe 10 years later, Japan has repeatedly launched the "sprint" of joining the club, but all have failed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日本问题专家杨伯江认为，日本入常意图一目了然，但入常之路势必困难重重。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">Japan specialist Yang Bojiang believed that Japan’s intent to become a permanent member was crystal clear, but the path to becoming a permanent member would be difficult.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">Japan's expert Yang Bojiang believes that Japan's intention to glance at the usual, but the road to the usual will be difficult.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">According to Yang Bojiang, an expert on Japan, Japan's intention to join the WTO is clear at a glance, but the road to becoming a permanent member is bound to be very difficult.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.sl">
    <source>日本要实现自己的目标，首先要和周边国家搞好关系，其中，无论在地缘政治争夺还是在民族争端以及历史认识问题上，日本需要有一个正确的态度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.ht">To achieve its own objectives, Japan must first build good relations with neighboring countries. In particular, whether in terms of geopolitical contention, national disputes or historical understanding, Japan must have the correct attitude.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.gg">In order to achieve its goal, Japan must first make good relations with neighboring countries, in which the Japanese need to have a correct attitude, whether in the geopolitical contest or in the national dispute and the historical understanding.</translation>
    <translation system="096_ifeng0812.news.49767990_0_zh.c6">To achieve its goal, Japan must first establish good relations with its neighboring countries, in which it needs to have a correct attitude, whether in geopolitical rivalries or in ethnic disputes and issues of historical understanding.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
