<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>中国的火星计划来了</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">China’s Mars program unveiled</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">China's Mars program is coming</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">China's Mars mission is here.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>我国火星探测任务要一次实现环绕、着陆、巡视，这种形式在国外从没有过。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">The task of the Mars exploration mission of China is to achieve orbiting, landing, and inspection. Such format has never been carried out before in other countries.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The mission of Mars exploration in China is to be rounded, landed and inspected at once, and this form has never been in foreign countries.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">China's Mars exploration mission to achieve a circle, landing, patrol, this form has never been in foreign countries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>我国的火星探测发射目标是想一步环绕、着陆、巡视，这个任务具有相当大的难度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">China's Mars exploration launch target is to orbit, land and inspect in one attempt. This was a difficult mission.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The goal of our Mars reconnaissance launch is to get around, to land, to patrol, this task is very difficult.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">The goal of our country's Mars exploration and launch is to surround, land and patrol in one step, which is quite difficult.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因为火星探测要26个月才能遇到一个时间窗口，所以专家们正在严密地制定工程计划，争取在2020年这个窗口发射我国第一个火星探测器。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">The time window for exploring Mars happen only every 26 months. Experts are drawing up a stringent construction plan to launch our country’s first Mars probe when the opportunity arrives in 2020.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Because the Mars probe will take 26 months to meet a time window, experts are working on a rigorous engineering plan to launch the country's first Mars probe in the 2020 window.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Because Mars exploration takes 26 months to meet a window of time, experts are working closely on engineering plans to launch our country's first Mars rover in this window by 2020.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据许达哲介绍，尽管我国的飞行器已经进入了深空，但是完成火星探测任务仍不可或缺，探测火星意味着中国从真正意义上迈入深空探测时代。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">According to Xu Dazhe, although our country's space vehicle has been delivered into deep space, completion of a Mars exploration mission is indispensable. Mars exploration will mark the step by which China enters the era of deep space exploration.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">According to Hudazhe, although China's aircraft has entered deep space, but the completion of the mission is still indispensable, detection of Mars means that China from the real sense into the deep space exploration era.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">According to Xu Dazhe, although China's spacecraft has entered deep space, but the completion of the Mars exploration mission is still indispensable, Mars exploration means that China from the true sense into the era of deep space exploration.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“每隔两年或三年，才有一次火星距离地球最近的机会，在这个时间点上发射火星探测器，对运载火箭来说是最省能量的。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">“Mars comes closest to Earth only once every two or three years. Launching a Mars probe then would be most energy efficient for a carrier rocket.”</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">"Once every two or three years, there is a chance that Mars will be able to launch a Mars probe at this point in time, which is the most energy-saving for a launch vehicle." ”</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">"Every two or three years, there is only one chance for Mars to be closest to Earth, and launching a Mars rover at this point in time is the most energy-efficient for a launch vehicle," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“考虑到火星探测器的质量，将由我国长征五号运载火箭来完成发射任务。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">“Taking into consideration the quality of the Mars probe, the launch mission will be completed by our Long March 5 carrier rocket.”</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">"Given the quality of the Mars probe, the launch mission will be carried out by China's Long March No. Fifth launch vehicle." ”</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">"Taking into account the quality of the Mars rover, China will be the Long March V launch vehicle to complete the mission."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>我国的火星探测任务要一次实现环绕、着陆、巡视，这种形式在国外是从没有过的，国外曾拟一次实现环绕和着陆，但着陆失败了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">China’s mission to explore Mars aims to orbit, land and inspect in one attempt. This form has never been attempted overseas. A foreign mission had once attempted to orbit and land but the landing failed.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The mission of Mars exploration in China is to be rounded, landed and inspected at once, and this form has never been done abroad, and it has been proposed to be rounded and landed, but the landing failed.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">China's Mars exploration mission to achieve a surround, landing, patrol, this form has never been in foreign countries, foreign countries have been intended to achieve a surround and landing, but the landing failed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>火星探测涉及的技术领域非常多，特别之处还在于，虽然火星车是一个空间探测器，但与一般空间探测器相比，它又具有鲜明的特点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Mars exploration covers a large number of technological fields. Despite being a space exploration device, the unique feature of the device is that it has distinctive characteristics that set it apart from general space exploration probes.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">There are many technical areas involved in Mars exploration, and, in particular, although the rover is a space detector, it has distinct characteristics compared with the general space probe.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">There are many technical fields involved in Mars exploration, and the special thing is that, although the Mars rover is a space probe, it has distinct characteristics compared with the general space probe.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>也就是说，火星探测器要具备确定行驶路线、发现障碍危险的能力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">In other words, the Mars exploration vehicle must be given the ability to determine driving routes and detect obstacles and hazards.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">That is to say, the Mars rover has the ability to determine the route and the danger of discovering obstacles.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">That is to say, the Mars rover should have the ability to determine the route and discover the danger of obstacles.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>中国航天科技集团五院研究员庞之浩说，人类之所以对火星探测如此青睐，是因为探测火星具有重要的科学、技术等多方面意义，甚至关系到人类的未来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Pang Zhihao, researcher at China Academy of Space Technology said that the reason why human beings are so keen to explore Mars is because it has major scientific, technological and various other significance, and is even related to the future of humanity.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Part, a researcher at the five Academy of China Aerospace Technology Group, said that the reason why humans are so popular with Mars exploration is that it has important scientific, technological and other implications, even for the future of mankind.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Pang Zhihao, a researcher at the Fifth Academy of the China Aerospace Science and Technology Group, said that the reason why people are so interested in Mars exploration is because it has important scientific, technological and other significance, and even concerns the future of mankind.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>目前火星已成为除地球以外人类研究程度最高的行星，人类利用空间探测器进行火星探测的历史几乎贯穿整个人类航天史。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Currently, Mars is the best-studied planet by the human race. The use of space probes for Mars exploration almost permeates the entirety of human aerospace history.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Mars has now become the planet with the highest level of human research beyond Earth, and the History of Mars exploration by using space probes has been almost throughout the history of human spaceflight.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Mars has now become the planet with the highest degree of human research outside the Earth, and the history of human exploration of Mars using space probes runs through almost the entire history of human spaceflight.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因此，人类希望有朝一日在火星建立居住基地，最终向火星移民，把它变成人类的第二家园。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Hence, the human race hopes to construct a residential base on Mars in the future, colonize the planet, and make it a second home for the species.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">As a result, humans hope to build a living base on Mars and eventually immigrate to Mars, turning it into a second home for mankind.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">As a result, humanity hopes to one day establish a residential base on Mars, eventually migrating to it and turning it into a second home for humanity.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>大量迹象还表明，火星以前很可能与目前的地球一样，只是经过几十亿年的演化才变成大气层稀薄、温度较低、水源枯竭等样子。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Large volumes of evidence suggest that Mars, in the past, may be like present day earth, and only assumed its current form with thin atmosphere, low temperature, and dwindling water resources after an process of change lasting billions of years.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">There are plenty of signs that Mars, like the current Earth, has only evolved over billions of of years to become thinner, cooler, and drained of water.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">There are also plenty of indications that Mars, like Earth today, may have evolved over billions of years to become a thin atmosphere, cooler temperatures, depleted water sources, and so on.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因此，探测或载人登陆火星进行研究，可以为防止地球变成人类难以生存的第二个火星提出预案。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Therefore, inspecting or sending manned spacecraft to Mars for study will help us find solution to prevent earth become a uninhabitable Mars, the second.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">As a result, exploration or manned landings on Mars can be used to prevent the Earth from becoming a second Mars for human survival.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">So exploration or manned landing on Mars for research could offer a preview of preventing the Earth from becoming a second Mars that would be difficult for humans to survive.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>截至2016年6月，全球共进行了114次月球探测，43次火星探测。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">As of June 2016, 114 lunar explorations and 43 Mars explorations had been carried out worldwide.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">As of June 2016, the world conducted 114 lunar probes and 43 Martian probes.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">As of June 2016, 114 lunar expeditions and 43 Mars expeditions had been conducted globally.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>不过，从20世纪90年代至今，人类共进行了18次火星探测，而月球探测只进行了14次。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">However, since the 1990s, the human race has launched a total of 18 Mars exploration missions. In comparison, only 14 Lunar exploration missions had been carried out.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">However, since the 1990s, humans have conducted 18 Martian probes, while lunar probes have been conducted only 14 times.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Since the 1990s, however, there have been 18 missions to Mars, compared with 14 to the moon.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>目前有5个火星轨道器和2辆火星漫游车在工作，但只有1个月球轨道器和1个月球着陆器在工作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">At this time, five Mars orbiters and two Mars rovers are in operation, but only one lunar orbiter and one lunar lander are in operation.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">There are currently 5 Mars Orbiter and 2 Mars rover working, but only a 1-month ball orbiter and a lunar lander are working.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">There are currently five Mars orbiters and two Mars rovers in operation, but only one lunar orbiter and one lunar lander are operational.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>世界航天大国都制定了以火星系统为目标的探测计划，由此可见，当今的火星探测比月球探测还热。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Leading countries in the aerospace industry have stipulated exploration projects that target the planet Mars. This demonstrates that in modern times, Mars exploration is more popular than lunar exploration.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The world's space Powers have developed a plan to target the Mars system, which shows that today's Mars is hotter than lunar exploration.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Today's exploration of Mars is hotter than that of the moon, as evidenced by the fact that the world's major spacefaring nations have developed plans to target the Mars system.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2013年11月5日，印度发射了第一个火星探测器“曼加里安”，成为亚洲第一个成功探测火星的国家。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">On November 5, 2013, India launched its first Mars exploration probe Mangalyaan, and became the first country in Asia to successfully start a Mars exploration mission.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">On November 5, 2013, India launched its first Mars probe, "Mangarian", to become Asia's first successful country to detect Mars.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">On November 5, 2013, India launched its first Mars rover, Mangarian, making it the first country in Asia to successfully explore Mars.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“曼加里安”用于研究火星表面、大气和矿物特征，探寻火星上是否有甲烷和生命迹象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">“Mangalyaan” is used to study the surface, atmospheric, and mineral characteristics of Mars to search whether there are methane and signs of life on the planet.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">"Mangarian" is used to study the surface, atmosphere and mineral characteristics of Mars to see if there are any signs of methane and life on Mars.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">"Mangarian" is used to study the surface, atmosphere and mineral features of Mars, and to search for signs of methane and life on Mars.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这次任务最难的地方，就是探测器进入火星大气后气动外形和降落伞减速只有一次机会</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">The most challenging part of this mission is that the probe has only one chance for its aerodynamic shape and parachute to decelerate when it enters the Martian atmosphere</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The hardest part of this mission is that the probe enters the Martian atmosphere, with the aerodynamic shape and parachute deceleration only one chance.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">The most difficult part of the mission was that the rover had only one chance to enter the Martian atmosphere with its aerodynamic configuration and parachute deceleration</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据中国航天科技集团公司五院总体部的火星探测器总设计师孙泽洲介绍，火星探测任务面临着许多技术挑战。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">According to Sun Zezhou, chief designer of the Mars exploration vehicle at the integrated department of facility 5 of the China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation, the Mars exploration mission faces many technical challenges.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The Mars reconnaissance mission faces many technical challenges, according to General architect Sun, director of the Mars probe, five yuan of China Aerospace Technology Group.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">The Mars exploration mission faces many technical challenges, according to Sun Zezhou, chief architect of the Mars rover in the general department of the Fifth Academy of the China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>火星大气气压很低，只有地球表面大气压力的1%，具有很高的不确定性。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">The atmospheric pressure on Mars, at only 1% that on Earth, has significant uncertainties.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">The atmospheric pressure on Mars is very low, with a high degree of uncertainty, only 1% of the Earth's surface atmosphere.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Mars has a very low atmospheric pressure, only 1% of the atmospheric pressure on the Earth's surface, with a high degree of uncertainty.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>有关它的变化和风暴时特性等因素，科学家们还没有透彻的认识。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Scientists have yet to arrive at a clear understanding about its changes, the properties of the storms, and other functions.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Scientists have not yet got a thorough understanding of the changes and characteristics of storms.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Scientists do not yet have a thorough understanding of factors such as its variability and storm-time characteristics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>火星在夏季常形成类似地球沙尘天气的尘暴，这会导致火星车接收的太阳光能量急剧下降，必须为火星车设计“休眠”模式，让其耐心地等待尘暴过去。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">As Mars experiences sand storms familiar with those on the earth, the rover will not receive enough solar energy for operation. Therefore, it has to have a " Sleeping" mode till the end of the storm.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Mars often forms dust storms similar to Earth's dust in summer, which can cause a sharp drop in the amount of solar energy The rover receives, and must design a "dormant" model for the rover to wait patiently for the dust storm to pass.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Mars often forms dust storms in the summer that resemble the dust of the Earth, causing a sharp drop in the sun's energy received by the rover, which must be designed to "sleep" in order to patiently wait for the dust storm to pass.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>同时，火星大气对太阳光照还有削减作用，这为火星探测的能源供给带来难题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">The atmosphere of Mars will also weaken incoming solar radiation, providing yet another challenge to power supply for Mars exploration.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">At the same time, the Martian atmosphere has a reduced effect on solar illumination, which poses a problem for the energy supply that Mars detects.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">At the same time, the Martian atmosphere has a diminishing effect on solar light, which poses a problem for the energy supply for Mars exploration.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这就要求探测器的太阳翼面积更大，而且需不断调整，努力对准太阳方向。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">This requires the probe to have larger solar panels that must be constantly adjusted to direct them towards the sun.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">This requires that the detector's solar wing area is larger, and it needs to be constantly adjusted to aim for the sun.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">This requires that the probe's solar wing area is larger and needs to be constantly adjusted in an effort to align with the direction of the sun.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>还有，火星表面重力只有地球的38%，但是比月球表面的重力大多了，因此探测器需要更大的功率。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">In addition, the surface gravity on Mars is only 38% that of Earth, but is a lot larger than that on the Moon. Therefore, a probe with more power is required.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Also, Mars ' surface gravity is only 38% that of the earth, but much more than the gravity of the moon's surface, so the detectors need greater power.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Also, the surface gravity of Mars is only 38% of that of Earth, but it is much greater than that of the lunar surface, so the probe needs more power.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这次火星探测任务最核心、最难的地方，就是探测器进入火星大气后气动外形和降落伞减速的过程，只有一次机会，必须确保成功。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">“The most central and hardest part of this Mars exploration mission is the aerodynamic configuration and the parachute deceleration process after the probe enters the atmosphere of Mars. There is only one opportunity, and ensuring its success is critical.”</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">"The core and hardest part of this mission is the process of the spacecraft's aerodynamic appearance and parachute deceleration after entering the Martian atmosphere, with only one chance to ensure success," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">"The most central and most difficult part of this mission is the aerodynamic shape and parachute deceleration of the spacecraft as it enters the Martian atmosphere.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>孙泽洲说，由于地球与火星距离遥远，整个过程无法由地面实时控制，所以必须依靠探测器自主完成。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Sun Zezhou said that as Earth was a long distance away from Mars, it was impossible to control the entire process on a real-time basis. Therefore, a probe is required to complete the mission autonomously.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Sun said that because the Earth and Mars far away, the whole process can not be real-time control of the ground, so must rely on the detector to do it autonomously.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Sun said the whole process could not be controlled by the ground in real time because of the distance between the Earth and Mars, so it had to be done autonomously by the rover.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>由于没有那么多的推进剂来抵消那么高的速度，所以登陆火星时，减速要依靠火星大气的作用，然而火星大气难以在地面模拟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">As there was insufficient propellant to offset such a high speed, when landing on Mars, deceleration would depend on the effect of the Martian atmosphere. The atmosphere on Mars however, is difficult to simulate on Earth.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Because there are not so many propellants to offset that high speed, the slowdown depends on the Martian atmosphere when landing on Mars, but the Martian atmosphere is hard to simulate on the ground.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Since there are not so many propellants to offset that high velocity, the deceleration upon landing on Mars depends on the action of the Martian atmosphere, which is difficult to simulate on the ground.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>庞之浩说，总体来讲，探测火星的方式与探测月球的方式相似，也是“绕、落、巡、回”，最终实现载人登陆火星的目标。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">Pang Zhihao said, “On the whole, the methods used to explore Mars and the Moon are similar. It also involves “orbit, land, inspect, return”, ultimately achieving the goal of bringing people to Mars.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">In general, part said, the way to detect Mars is similar to the way the moon is detected, and it is also a "detour, Fall, patrol, return" to achieve the goal of manned landing on Mars.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">In general, the way to explore Mars is similar to the way to explore the moon, Pang said, and is also to "circle, fall, patrol, and return," ultimately achieving the goal of a manned landing on Mars.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="34" doc-id="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.sl">
    <source>由于火星距离地球比月球距离地球要远得多，所以探测火星需要攻克一系列更复杂的技术难关。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.ht">As Mars is further away from Earth than the Moon, exploring Mars requires overcoming a series of more complex technical difficulties.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.gg">Since Mars is much farther from Earth than the moon, exploring Mars needs to overcome a series of more complex technical hurdles.</translation>
    <translation system="154_ifeng0812.news.49765603_0_zh.c6">Because Mars is much farther away from Earth than the Moon is from Earth, exploring Mars will require tackling a series of more complex technical hurdles.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
