<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.sl">
    <source>海口海事法院凌晨立案确保临高渔船沉没事件当事人权益</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.ht">The Haikou Maritime Court put the case on record early morning to ensure the rights of the parties concerned with the sinking of the Lingao fishing boat</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.gg">Haikou Maritime Court early morning filing to ensure the rights and interests of Lingao fishing vessel sinking</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.c6">Haikou Maritime Court opened a case in the early hours of the morning to ensure the rights and interests of the parties involved in the sinking of a fishing boat</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.sl">
    <source>3名身亡船员的亲属于8月7日凌晨4点赶赴海口海事法院，提起诉前财产保全扣押涉嫌肇事货轮的申请。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.ht">Relatives of the three sailors who perished arrived at the Haikou Maritime Court at 4am on August 7 to file an application for property preservation before prosecution to detain the vessel suspected of causing the accident.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.gg">3 of the relatives of the dead crew rushed to Haikou Maritime Court on August 7 at 4 o'clock in the morning to submit an application for the seizure of the alleged cargo vessel before the prosecution.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.c6">The relatives of the three deceased crew members rushed to the Haikou Maritime Court at 4 a.m. on 7 August to file an application for the seizure of the suspected hit-and-run cargo ship for property preservation before prosecution.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.sl">
    <source>4日事发后，涉嫌肇事货轮被海事局扣押于海口秀英港协助调查。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.ht">After the incident on the 4th day, the cargo freighter suspected for the cause of the accident was detained by the Maritime Safety Administration at Haikou Xiuying Port to support the investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.gg">4th after the incident, the suspected cargo vessel was detained by the Marine Bureau Yuhai Port to assist in the investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.c6">4 after the incident, the suspected hit-and-run cargo ship was detained by the Maritime Administration in Haikou Xiuying Port to assist in the investigation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.sl">
    <source>鉴于海事局72小时扣押期限于8月7日上午9点届满，遇难者亲属于7日凌晨向法院提起财产保全申请。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.ht">The Maritime Safety Administration’s 72-hour detention period lapsed at 9am on August 7. Relatives of victims filed their applications for property preservation with the Court in the early hours on the 7th.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.gg">In view of the expiry of the 72-hour detention period at 9 o'clock in the morning on August 7, the relatives of the victims filed an application for property preservation to the court early on 7th.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.c6">In view of the expiration of the 72-hour detention period of the Maritime Administration at 9 a.m. on 7 August, relatives of the victims filed an application for property preservation with the court in the early hours of 7 August.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.sl">
    <source>凌晨4点20分，申请人提起诉前财产保全，值班法警耐心接待。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.ht">At 4:20am, the applicants filed for property preservation before the prosecution. Bailiffs on duty received them patiently.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.gg">4:20 A.M., the applicant before the prosecution of property preservation, on duty bailiff patient reception.</translation>
    <translation system="138_ifeng0812.news.49768151_0_zh.c6">At 4: 20 a.m., the applicant filed an application for pre-indictment property preservation and was patiently received by the judicial police on duty.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
