<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>昨日上午10时许，X9003次国际货运班列从西安新筑车站开出，前往哈萨克斯坦的阿拉木图。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">At about 10am yesterday, the X9003 international freight train heading to Almaty, Kazakhstan departed from Xinzhu train station in Xi’an.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">Yesterday 10 o'clock in the morning Xu, X9003 international freight class from XI ' an new building station, to Kazakhstan Almaty.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">At about 10 a.m. yesterday, the X9003 international freight train left Xian Xinzhu Station for Almaty, Kazakhstan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>该趟列车的开行，标志着西安铁路局自2013年开行中亚国际货运班列以来，开行车数成功突破10000车。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">Xi’an Railway Station marks the successful breakthrough of operating 10,000 trains with the departure of this train service since it began operating the China-Central Asia international freight service in 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">The train's opening, marking the Xi ' an railway bureau since 2013 to open the international freight class in Central Asia, the number of driving a successful breakthrough 10000 vehicles.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">The train's departure marks the Xi'an Railway Administration's success in driving more than 10,000 cars since it launched the Central Asian International Freight Train in 2013.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据了解，此班货运班列运输的货物品类涵盖工业原材料、机械设备、工业零配件、建材、食品、轻工产品六大类、共计206个品种。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">It was reported that the cargo transported on this freight train included a total of 206 product varieties in six major categories, namely, industrial raw materials, machinery and equipment, industrial parts and components, building materials, food, and light industry products.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">It is understood that this class of freight transport class cargo category covers industrial raw materials, machinery and equipment, industrial spare parts, building materials, food, light industrial products six categories, a total of 206 varieties.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">It is understood that this class of freight train transportation of goods category covers industrial raw materials, machinery and equipment, industrial spare parts, building materials, food, light industrial products, a total of 206 varieties.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>截至今年8月11日，新筑车站共开行中亚班列221列、10009车，累计发运出口货物33.8万吨，其中2016年开行84列，同比增长47%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">As of August 11 this year, a total of 221 trips, 10,009 train cars, and 338,000 tons of goods have departed from the newly constructed train station, of which 84 train cars have left in 2016 for a 84% growth compared to the same period last year.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">As at August 11 this year, the new station opened a total of 221 rows of Central Asian class, 10009 vehicles, the cumulative shipment of exports of 338,000 tons, of which 2016 years opened 84 rows, year-on-year growth of 47%.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">As of 11 August this year, a total of 221 Central Asian trains and 10,009 vehicles had been operated at Xinzhu Station, with a cumulative total of 338,000 tons of exported goods shipped, including 84 in 2016, an increase of 47 percent over the same period last year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据了解，中亚班列首趟运载的货物均为“陕西制造”，而如今，它已吸引大量的外地货源积极上列。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">According to information, the goods carried by the first Central Asian trip are entirely “made in Shaanxi”. Today, it has attracted a large volume of commodities from other areas and eagerly waits to be loaded onto the trains.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">It is understood that the first trip to the Central Asian class is "Made in Shaanxi", and today, it has attracted a large number of foreign sources actively listed above.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">It is understood that the first shipment of the Central Asian class are "made in Shaanxi," and now, it has attracted a large number of foreign sources actively on the list.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>截至7月底，中亚班列集装箱到发量突破6.4万标箱，较2015年同期增长8%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">As at end-July, the Central Asia freight train container  throughput exceeded 64,000 TEUs, up 8% from the same period in 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">As at the end of July, the Central Asian class container had exceeded 64,000 TEU in volume, representing a 8% increase over the same period in 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">By the end of July, the number of shift container deliveries in Central Asia had exceeded 64,000 TEU, an increase of 8 per cent compared with the same period in 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>随着中亚班列的加密开行，西安铁路局新筑车站货运量逐年提升。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">As trips to Central Asia become increasingly frequent, shipment volumes of the new train station constructed by the Xi'an Railway Bureau also continued to grow by the year.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">With the encryption of Central Asian classes, the traffic volume of the new station of Xi ' an railway bureau has been upgraded yearly.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">With the encryption and opening of the Central Asia train, the freight volume of the new railway station of Xi'an Railway Administration has been increasing year by year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2015年，新筑车站全年货运吞吐量247.7万吨，截至2016年8月10日，货运发送量已经达到153.1万吨，较去年同期增长6.7%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">In 2015, the annual throughput of the newly constructed station totaled 2,477,000 tonnes. As of August 10, 2016, freight shipments have already reached 1,531,000 tonnes, up 6.7% year-on-year.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">2015, the new station full year freight throughput of 2.477 million tons, as of August 10, 2016, the volume of shipments has reached 1.531 million tons, compared with the same period last year growth of 6.7%.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">In 2015, the new station handled 2.477 million tons of freight for the whole year, and as of August 10, 2016, the volume of freight sent had reached 1.531 million tons, an increase of 6.7% over the same period last year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.sl">
    <source>为了满足未来发展需要，西安铁路局以新筑车站为中心的西安新筑铁路综合物流中心建设规划已经出台，全力打造现代化的新筑铁路综合物流园区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.ht">To meet the requirements for future development, the Xi'an Railway Bureau has released plans for constructing the Xi’an Xinzhu Rail Integrated Logistics Center with Xinzhu Railway Station as its center. The Bureau will focus its energy on building a modern Xinzhu Rail Integrated Logistics Park.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.gg">In order to meet the needs of future development, Xi ' an railway station, the new construction of the comprehensive Logistics Center in XI ' An, has been launched to build a modern new railway integrated logistics park.</translation>
    <translation system="158_ifeng0812.news.49766664_0_zh.c6">In order to meet the needs of future development, Xi'an Railway Administration has launched the construction plan of Xi'an Xinzhu Railway Integrated Logistics Center centering on the new railway station, making every effort to create a modern new railway integrated logistics park.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
