<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>保加利亚8个月来首次出现通货膨胀</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Bulgaria saw inflation for the first time in eight months</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">Bulgaria has seen inflation for the first time in 8 months.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">Bulgaria's inflation for first time in eight months</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>国家统计结果表明，7月保加利亚的月通货膨胀率为1%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">National statistical results showed that Bulgaria’s monthly inflation rate was 1% in July.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">The national statistical results show that in July Bulgaria's monthly inflation rate was 1%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">National statistics show that the monthly inflation rate in Bulgaria was 1 per cent in July.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>这是几年来（自2012年6月起） 最高的通货膨胀率。去年10月 （通货膨胀率0.2%） 之后，通货膨胀率首次突破零点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Inflation was at its highest level in years (since June 2016), surpassing zero for the first time since October last year (inflation at 0.2%).</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">This is the highest rate of inflation in years (since June 2012). After last October (inflation rate 0.2%), the inflation rate exceeded 0 points for the first time.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">This is the highest rate of inflation in several years (since June 2012), which broke above zero for the first time since October last year (0.2 per cent).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>相比之前的12个月 （2014年8月至2015年7月），过去12个月 （2015年8月至2016年7月） 的年平均通货膨胀率 （以消费者价格指数衡量）为 -0.8%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Compared to the previous 12 months (August 2014 to July 2015), the annual average inflation rate (based on the consumer price index) for the last 12 months (August 2015 to July 2016) was -0.8%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">Compared with the previous 12 months (August 2014 to July 2015), the average annual inflation rate (measured in consumer price indices) for the past 12 months (August 2015 to July 2016) was 0.8%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">The average annual inflation rate (as measured by the consumer price index) over the past 12 months (August 2014 to July 2015) was -0.8% compared to the previous 12 months (August 2014 to July 2015).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>相比2016年6月，2016年7月的消费者价格指数为101.0%，即月通货膨胀率为 1.0%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Compared to June 2016, the Consumer Price Index (CPI) in July 2016 stood at 101.0%, i.e., the monthly inflation rate was 1.0%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">Compared with June 2016, the consumer price index in July 2016 was 101%, or the monthly inflation rate was 1%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">The consumer price index for July 2016 was 101.0 per cent compared to June 2016, representing a monthly inflation rate of 1.0 per cent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>今年至今的通货膨胀率 （2016年7月相对于2015年12月） 为 -0.2%。相比2015年7月，2016年7月的年通货膨胀率为 -0.2%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Inflation rate to date for this year (July 2016 relative to December 2015) was -0.2%. When compared to July 2015, the annual inflation rate in July 2016 was -0.2%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">The inflation rate so far this year (July 2016 versus December 2015) is 0.2%. Compared with July 2015, the annual inflation rate in July 2016 was 0.2%.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">The inflation rate so far this year (July 2016 compared to December 2015) is -0.2%, compared to July 2015, when the annual rate was -0.2%.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>相比上月，下列几类消费品的价格在2016年7月出现上涨：食品和非酒精饮料 (1.7%)、交通 (1.8%)、娱乐与文化 (6.3%)、餐厅与酒店 (1.2%)、其他商品与服务 (0.3%)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">When compared to the previous month, the prices of the following consumer items have rose during July 2016: food and non-alcoholic beverages (1.7%), transportation (1.8%), entertainment and culture (6.3%), restaurants and hotels (1.2%), and other products and services (0.3%).</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">The prices of the following categories of consumer goods rose in July 2016 compared to last month: Food and Non-alcoholic Beverages (1.7%), Traffic (1.8%), Entertainment and Culture (6.3%), restaurants and hotels (1.2%), and other goods and services (0.3%).</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">Prices of the following categories of consumer goods increased in July 2016 compared to the previous month: food and non-alcoholic beverages (1.7 per cent), transport (1.8 per cent), entertainment and culture (6.3 per cent), restaurants and hotels (1.2 per cent) and other goods and services (0.3 per cent).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>价格出现下降的有服装与鞋类 (2.2%)、家具、家电和常规维护 (0.5%)、医疗 (0.1%)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Prices that have fallen include apparel and shoes (2.2%), furniture, home appliances and routine maintenance (0.5%), as well as health care (0.1%).</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">Prices declined with clothing and footwear (2.2%), furniture, home appliances and conventional maintenance (0.5%), Medical (0.1%).</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">Declining prices were recorded for clothing and footwear (2.2 per cent), furniture, appliances and routine maintenance (0.5 per cent) and medical care (0.1 per cent).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="162_novinite.com.17830_en.sl">
    <source>与上月价格持平的有酒精饮料和烟草、住房、水、电、天然气和其他燃料、通信、教育。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.ht">Commodity prices that remained stable last month include alcoholic beverages, tobacco, housing, water, electricity, natural gas and other fuels, communication, and education.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.gg">Alcoholic beverages and tobacco, housing, water, electricity, natural gas and other fuels, communications, and education were flat with prices last month.</translation>
    <translation system="162_novinite.com.17830_en.c6">At the same price as last month were alcoholic drinks and tobacco, housing, water, electricity, gas and other fuels, communications, education.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
