<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>很多NBA球员都证明了自己的实力。但是有人进步就有人衰落。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Many NBA players have proven themselves, but progress for some meant regress for others.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Many NBA players have proved their strength. But some progress is the downfall of others.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">A lot of NBA players have proven themselves, but some have improved and others have declined.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>无论是因为年龄的增大还是出场时间被限制，每个赛季都有一些球员的表现会出现退步。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Due to aging or restrictions on playing time, performance of several players may become worse for each season.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Whether it's because of the age or the time limit, there are some players who will show a setback every season.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Whether it's because of increased age or limited playing time, there are a number of players who have regressed every season.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>当然了，有些“退步”可能仅仅是数据的缩水，这些球员的实力可能并未下降。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Of course, some of this “degeneration” could be attributed to lowered statistics, but the true ability of these players probably stayed the same.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Of course, some "backwards" may just be the shrinking of the data, and the players ' strength may not fall.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Of course, some of the "regressions" may simply be data shrinkage, and the strength of these players may not have diminished.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>即便韦德仍是联盟里最好的得分后卫之一，但是他在公牛的表现应该不会有热火那么好了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Although Wade is still regarded as one of the best shooting guards in the NBA, his performance with the Bulls will unlikely be as good as when he was at Miami Heat.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Even though Wade is still one of the league's best scoring guards, his performance at the Bulls should not be as good as the heat.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Even though Wade is still one of the best shooting guards in the league, he probably won't do as well with the Bulls as the Heat.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他和隆多组成的后场射程有限，当家球星巴特勒的三分命中率也只有32.8%，这让他们下赛季的进攻会打得很拥挤。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">He and Rondo has limited perimeter shot range, and their superstar Butler only has a 32.8% chance of scoring with a three-point shot. Offenses they head for the next season will be extremely crowded.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">He and Rondo have a limited range of the back field, the Star Butler's three-point hit is only 32.8%, which makes them very crowded next season's attack.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">He and Rondo have limited backcourt range and the establishment star Butler is shooting just 32.8 percent from three-point range, making their offense crowded for next season.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>来到了风城，闪电侠势必把球权更多地让给巴特勒和隆多，自己很可能在常规赛选择养生打法。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">After arriving at the Windy City, Wade “the Lightning” will, where possible, pass the ball to Butler and Rondo while he himself adopts a more wholesome gameplay strategy in conventional games.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Came to the Windy City, the Lightning man will be more than the ball to Butler and long, he is likely to choose in the regular game regimen.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Coming to Windy City, the Blitzkrieg is bound to cede more of the ball to Butler and Rondo, and he is likely to choose a regimen to play during the regular season.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>奥卡福的情况比较尴尬，作为上赛季76人的第一选择，他在新赛季不得不和西蒙斯以及恩比德竞争上场时间和球权。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Okafor’s position is quite precarious. As the only option for the 76ers in the last season, he was forced to jostle with Simons and Embiid for play time and ownership of the ball during the new season.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Okafor's situation was awkward and, as the first choice for 76 people last season, he had to compete with Simmons and Embid in the new season.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Okafor is in an awkward position, having to compete with Simmons and Embiid for playing time and ball rights in the new season as the first choice for the 76ers last season.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这一竞争可能不会来的很快，西蒙斯还需要适应NBA赛场，恩比德也要尽快从伤病中完全恢复，但是奥卡福能否在76人的长人阵中有位置还是个问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">This competition may not be imminent. Simmons still has to adapt to the NBA game. Embiid also has to fully recover from his injuries as soon as possible. Whether Okafor will hold a permanent position in the 76ers however, remains questionable.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">This competition may not come quickly, Simmons also needs to adapt to the NBA arena, Embid also want to recover from the injury as soon as possible, but the Okafor can be 76 people in the long array of positions is still a problem.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">The rivalry may not come soon, Simmons will have to adapt to the NBA and Embiid will have to fully recover from the injury as soon as possible, but Okafor's place in the 76ers' lineup remains a question.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>上个赛季，奥卡福32%的得分来自低位进攻，这一比例高于考辛斯、武切维奇和布鲁克·洛佩斯，同时他的使用率也高居联盟前40。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">In the previous season, Okafor’s 32% scoring rate was attributed to low post offense. This ratio was higher than that of Cousins, Vučević, and Brook Lopez. His usage rate is also amongst the top-40 of the entire NBA.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Last season, Okafor's 32% score came from low attacks, which were higher than Caucins, Vucevic and 布鲁克·洛佩斯, while his use was high in the top 40 of the league.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Okafor scored 32 percent from the low post offense last season, a higher percentage than Cousins, Vucevic and Brooke Lopez, while his usage rates were also high in the league's top 40.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>随着西蒙斯已经展现了出色的控球前锋潜质，恩比德也拥有着更适合NBA比赛的身材，奥卡福的地位恐怕很难再那么稳固了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">As Simmons has demonstrated great potential as a point forward and Embiid is starting to get a physique more suitable for NBA games, Okafor’s position will only become less stable.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">As Simmons has shown excellent control striker potential, Embid also has a better fit for the NBA game, and Okafor's position may be hard to stabilize.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">With Simmons already showing excellent possession forward potential and Embiid in better shape for NBA games, Okafor's position is likely to be hard to get any more secure.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>过去两个赛季，汤普森的使用率已经稳定在了联盟前20，而这也是他生涯最出色的两个赛季。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">For the last two seasons, Thompson has been one of the top-20 most commonly fielded players in the NBA. Those were his most impressive two seasons in his entire career.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">For the past two seasons, Thompson's usage has stabilized in the top 20 of the league, which is the best two seasons of his career.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Thompson's usage has stabilized in the league's top 20 over the past two seasons, the best of his career.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>不过问题是，随着杜兰特的到来，汤普森的使用率一定会下降，这势必将影响他的发挥。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">The problem is that with the arrival of Durant, the chance for having Thompson play in the games will definitely drop, further lowering his chances of performing.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">The problem, however, is that with Durant's arrival, Thompson's usage rate will surely drop, which will affect his play.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">The problem, though, is that Thompson's usage is bound to decline with Durant's arrival, and that's bound to affect his play.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这一影响将不仅是出手次数的影响，汤神的持球进攻在下赛季肯定也会大大减少，这在某些方面也会降低对手对他的防守难度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">This not only affected the chances for Thompson to play the game, his field goal attempts will be vastly reduced in the next season, and reduce the challenges faced by his opponents when defending against him.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">This effect will not only be the impact of the number of shots, Tang Shin's ball attack in the next season will certainly be greatly reduced, which in some ways will reduce the opponent's defense difficulty.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">The impact will be not only in terms of the number of shots taken, but the Towns' holding offense will certainly be significantly reduced next season, which in some ways will also make it easier for opponents to defend him.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>杜兰特的到来一定会让勇士队的球员们数据缩水，但这其中缩水最严重的恐怕就是汤普森了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">The arrival of Durant will definitely result in a drop in numbers among Warriors’ players, but Thompson will probably have the most to lose.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Durant's arrival will certainly make the Warriors ' figures shrink, but the most serious shrinkage is Thompson.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Durant's arrival is sure to shrink the Warriors' player numbers, but it's probably Thompson who has lost the most.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但这并不意味着汤神的水平退步，这更像是他为球队整体做出了牺牲。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">This does not mean that Thompson’s standards have dropped. In fact, it appears that he’s making sacrifices for the sake of the entire team.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">But that does not mean that Tang Shin's level of decline is more likely to make a sacrifice for the team as a whole.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">But that doesn't mean that Tommy's level has regressed, it's more like he's made sacrifices for the team as a whole.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>帕克在上个赛季表现得比数据反映的要好些，不仅是因为他的篮下效率来到了生涯最高，他和阿尔德里奇的化学反应也让马刺队受益。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Parker’s performance last season was better than his stats suggested. Not only did Parker achieve his career best in rebound efficiency, his chemistry with Aldridge also benefited the Spurs.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Parker's performance last season was better than the data reflected, not only because his basket efficiency came to the highest level, but he and Aldridge's chemistry also benefited the Spurs.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Parker did better last season than the numbers suggest, not only because his basketball efficiency was at its highest in his career, but also because his chemistry with Aldridge benefited the Spurs.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>邓肯退役，吉诺比利宣布再战一年，GDP的组合最终也走到了尽头，作为三个人里最年轻的一个，法国跑车的油箱里也没有多少油了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Duncan has retired, while Ginóbili announced that he will play for another year. The GDP combination has finally come to an end. As the youngest of the three, there is little gas in the tank of the French sports car.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Duncan retired, and Gino announced another year of war, the combination of GDP finally came to an end, as the youngest of three people, the French sports car is not much oil in the tank.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Duncan retired, Ginobili announced another year of fighting, and the GDP combination finally came to an end, and as the youngest of the three, the French sports car didn't have much fuel in its tank.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在得到了第三枚总冠军戒指之后，只有贾巴尔、乔丹和拉塞尔比詹姆斯赢得了更多的常规赛MVP，而乔丹是唯一一个FMVP比詹姆斯多的人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Only Jabbar, Jordan, and Russell won more standard MVP games than James after obtaining their third championship rings. Jordan is the only person with more FMVP than James.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">After winning the third championship ring, only Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, Jordan and Rasselbijams won more regular MVP, and Jordan was the only one FMVP James Dore.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">After getting their third championship ring, only Abdul-Jabbar, Jordan and Russell won more regular-season MVPs than James, and Jordan was the only one with more than James.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>哦，对了，詹姆斯刚刚为克利夫兰带来了过去52年里第一座职业体育冠军奖杯。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">O yes, James has just helped deliver the first professional sports championship trophy to Cleveland in 52 years.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">Oh, yes, James has just brought Cleveland the first professional sports champion trophy in the last 52 years.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">Oh, and by the way, James has just brought Cleveland its first Pro Sports Championship trophy in the last 52 years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>来到了职业生涯第14个赛季的詹姆斯需要更好的保证体力，为季后赛做好准备。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">James, who is in the 14th season of his professional career, needs to better retain his physical strength to prepare well for the playoffs.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">James, who has come to the 14th season of his career, needs to be better prepared for the playoffs.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">James, who arrived in his 14th season of his career, needs to be better guaranteed physical strength and ready for the playoffs.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因此，在常规赛里，詹姆斯的数据很可能进一步下滑，他会把更多的重担分给欧文来承担，不过他仍然会轻松地成为联盟前三的球员。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.ht">Therefore, during the regular season, James’ stats may well decline further. He will share more of his burden with Owen but he will easily remain one of the top 3 NBA players.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.gg">So in the regular season, James ' data is likely to fall further and he will take more of the burden to Owen, but he will still be easily the top three player in the league.</translation>
    <translation system="022_ifeng0812.news.49768361_0_zh.c6">As a result, James' numbers are likely to slide further during the regular season, and he'll share more of the burden with Irving, though he'll still be an easy top-three player in the league.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
