<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>为何我们需要西蒙、加布丽埃勒和劳瑞</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Why we need Simon, Gabrielle, and Laurie</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Why do we need Simon, Gabrielle and Laurie?</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Why do we need Simon and Gabrielle and Laurie?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>我就是这样评价今年的女子奥运体操队的，原因不止一个。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">This was how I evaluated the women's Olympic gymnastic team, and there is more than one reason for it.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">That's why I'm judging this year's women's Olympic gymnastics team for more than one reason.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">That's how I rate this year's women's Olympic gymnastics team for more than one reason.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>首先，从1984年起，我去了每一届夏季奥运会，但美国从未这般占据霸主地位。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Firstly, I have attended every Summer Olympics since 1984, and the United States has never dominated the sport as they did today.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">First of all, since 1984, I have been to every Summer Olympics, but the United States has never been such a dominant position.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">First of all, I've been to every Summer Olympics since 1984, but the United States has never been so dominant.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>其次，这支体操队有三名优秀的体操运动员——西蒙·拜尔斯 (Simone Biles)、加布丽埃勒·道格拉斯 (Gabby Douglas) 和劳瑞·埃尔南德斯 (Lauren Laurie Hernandez)，她们一直激励着众多有色人种女孩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">This team of gymnasts include 3 excellent athletes: Simone Biles, Gabby Douglas, and Lauren “Laurie” Hernandez who have inspired many girls of color.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Second, the gymnastics team has three excellent gymnasts-西蒙·拜尔斯 (Simone Biles), 加布丽埃勒·道格拉斯 (Gabby Douglas) and 劳瑞·埃尔南德斯 (Lauren Laurie Hernandez), They have been inspiring many colored girls.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Second, the team has three elite gymnasts - Simone Biles, Gabby Douglas and Lauren Laurie Hernandez - who have always inspired many girls of color.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>这支队伍的组成令所有人都倍感自豪，因为里面包含了犹太教的阿里·莱斯曼 (Aly Raisman) 和天主教的麦迪逊·科希安 (Madison Kocian)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">The composition of the team is something that everyone can be proud of. It includes Aly Raisman, a Jew, and Madison Kocian, a Catholic.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">The composition of this team has made everyone proud, as it contains the Jewish 阿里·莱斯曼 (Aly Raisman) and the Catholic Madison Chian (Madison Kocian).</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Everyone is proud of the team's composition, which includes Aly Raisman of Judaism and Madison Kocian of the Catholic Church.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>这支队伍终于看起像美国队了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">This team is finally starting to look like an American team.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">The team finally looks like the American team.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">The team finally looked like the American team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>它还巩固了黑人及拉丁裔女性在这项运动中的巅峰地位。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">It also strengthened the leading position of African and Latin American women in this sport.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">It also cemented the pinnacle of black and Hispanic women in the sport.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">It also cemented the pinnacle of black and Latino women in the sport.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>过去四年里，首屈一指的女体操运动员一直是非裔美国人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">For the last four years, the best female gymnast in the US has been an African American.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">The leading female gymnasts have been African-American for the past four years.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">The leading female gymnast has been African-American for the past four years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>去年，西蒙和加布丽埃勒分列第一、第二位。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Last year, Simone and Gabrielle were ranked first and second.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Last year, Simon and Gabrielle the first and second place.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Last year, Simon and Gabrielle finished in first and second place.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>这太厉害了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">That was awesome.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">That's too bad.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">That's awesome.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>上届奥运会，加布丽埃勒·道格拉斯“出人意料”地成为了奥运冠军，这令美国欢呼不已。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">In the previous Olympics, Gabrielle Douglas “surprisingly” became the Olympics champion, a feat that got America cheering.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">The last Olympic Games, 加布丽埃勒·道格拉斯 "unexpectedly" became the Olympic champion, which cheered the United States.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">The United States was cheered at the last Olympics when Gabrielle Douglas "unexpectedly" became an Olympic champion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>如今，全世界都能见证三届世界冠军西蒙·拜尔斯、道格拉斯和劳瑞·埃尔南德斯精彩绝伦的表现。他们把常规的体操技巧演绎得出神入化。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Today, the world can witness the exciting performances of three-time world champions, Simone Biles, Gabby Douglas and Laurie Hernandez. They have elevated conventional gymnastic techniques to the highest level of artistic interpretation.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Today, the world can witness three world champion 西蒙·拜尔斯, Douglas and 劳瑞·埃尔南德斯 fantastic performance. They performed the usual gymnastics skills.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Today, the world can witness the superb performance of three-time world champions Simon Byers, Douglas, and Laurie Hernandez, who have taken conventional gymnastics skills to their hearts' content.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>周四，西蒙帮助美国队在女子个人全能项目上实现四连冠。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">On Thursday, Simone helped the US team achieve four consecutive championships in the women’s individual all-around event.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">In Thursday, Simon helped the United States to achieve four consecutive championships in women's individual all-around projects.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">On Thursday, Simon helped the U.S. team to a four-game winning streak in the women's individual all-around event.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>她的队友阿里·莱斯曼斩获了银牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Her teammate Aly Raisman won the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Her teammate 阿里·莱斯曼 the silver medal.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Her teammate, Ali Leseman, scooped the silver medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>我们登上了这项运动的巅峰，但在全美体操教学课堂上却并非如此。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">We have ascended the zenith of this sport, but gymnastic classes throughout the entirety of the United States are not like this.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">We climbed to the top of the sport, but not in the American gymnastics class.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">We have reached the pinnacle of the sport, but not in the national gymnastics classroom.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>西蒙、加布丽埃勒和劳瑞进入奥运代表队的途径跟阿里及麦迪逊一样。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">The journey that took Simon, Gabby, and Laurie into the Olympics team was similar to that experienced by Ali and Madison.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">The way Simon, Gabrielle and Laurie entered the Olympic team was the same as Ali and Madison.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Simon, Gabrielle and Laurie entered the Olympic team in the same way as Ali and Madison.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>她们是“终极五人组”(Final Five)，因为下届奥运体操队将由四名体操运动员组成，这是 Marta Karolyi 最后一年执教。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">They will be the “Final Five” as the next Olympic gymnastics team will be composed of 4 athletes. This is the last year in which Marta Karolyi will be serving as the coach.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">They are the "Ultimate Five" (final Five), because the next Olympic gymnastics team will be composed of four gymnasts, this is Marta Karolyi last year to teach.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">They are the "Final Five" because the next Olympic gymnastics team will be made up of four gymnasts, Marta Karolyi's final year in charge.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>但是现实却是，体操是一项费用昂贵的运动，体操运动员主要在私人体操俱乐部进行训练，她们的父母需要支付训练、设施、差旅、服装、比赛及旅馆费用（包括教练及体操运动员和家人的相关费用），并且费用清单还在不断增加。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">The truth is that gymnastics is an expensive sport. Gymnasts are mainly trained in private gymnastic clubs. Their parents must pay for expenses that include training, facilities, traveling, clothing, competition fees, and accommodation (including relevant expenses for the coach, gymnasts, and family members). The list of expenses is still growing.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">But the reality is, gymnastics is an expensive sport in which gymnasts are trained mainly in private gymnastics clubs, and their parents need to pay for training, facilities, travel, clothing, competitions and hotel fees (including the costs of coaches and gymnasts and their families), and the list of costs is increasing.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">But the reality is that gymnastics is an expensive sport, with gymnasts training mainly in private gymnastics clubs, their parents paying for training, facilities, travel, clothing, competitions and hotels (including those related to coaches and gymnasts and their families), and the list of costs is constantly growing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>大部分的体操俱乐部坐落在可为该项产业提供支持的富裕的郊区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Most sports clubs are situated in affluent neighborhoods that can provide support for this industry.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Most of the gymnastics clubs are located in affluent suburbs that can support the industry.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Most of the gymnastics clubs are located in the affluent suburbs that support the industry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>体操运动员的所有训练都在这些俱乐部完成，对体操运动员的家庭而言是一笔长期的昂贵开支。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">All the training of gymnasts was conducted at these clubs, which was a long-term and considerable expense for the families of gymnasts.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">All of the gymnasts ' training is done at these clubs and is a long and expensive expense for gymnasts ' families.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">All the gymnasts' training is done at these clubs, which is an expensive long-term expense for the gymnasts' families.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>拜尔斯的教练艾米·伯尔曼 (Aimee Boorman) 和埃尔南德斯的教练 Maggie Haney 自这两名体操运动员开始练体操起一直执教她们。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Aimee Boorman, Biles’ coach, and Maggie Haney, the coach of Hernandez, have coached the two gymnasts since they began training in gymnastics.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Byers's coach 艾米·伯尔曼 (Aimee Boorman) and Hernandez's coach Maggie Haney have been coaching them since the two gymnasts began practicing gymnastics.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Byers' coach, Aimee Boorman, and Hernandez's coach, Maggie Haney, have coached the two gymnasts since they started gymnastics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>我们必须将更实惠、更可及的体操训练带给无数深受西蒙、加布丽埃勒和劳瑞影响的年轻女孩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">We must provide more practical and accessible gymnastic training to young girls who have been influenced by Simon, Gabrielle, and Laurie.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">We must bring more affordable, more accessible gymnastics training to countless young girls affected by Simon, Gabrielle and Laura.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">We must bring more affordable and accessible gymnastics training to the millions of young girls who have been influenced by Simon, Gabrielle and Laurie.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>20年前，我成立了自己的体操基金会。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">I founded my own gymnastics foundation 20 years ago.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">20 years ago, I set up my own gymnastics foundation.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Twenty years ago, I set up my own gymnastics foundation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>在我的组织中，我们在黑人住宅区向15,000余名城市青年（主要是黑人和西班牙裔美国人）提供免费、廉价的体操，并培养出全国乃至世界冠军。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">In my organization, we provide free and affordable gymnastics to more than 15,000 urban youths (mainly Black and Hispanic Americans) in Black neighborhoods, and have nurtured national and even world champions.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">In my organization, we offer free, inexpensive gymnastics to more than 15,000 urban youths (mostly black and Hispanic Americans) in black neighborhoods, and to develop national and even world champions.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">In my organization, we provided free, inexpensive gymnastics in black neighborhoods to more than 15,000 urban youth, primarily black and Hispanic, and produced national and even world championships.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>9月份，我们将扩大到底特律（我的家乡），向那些值得获得这一学习机会并将从这项了不起的奥运运动中受益的年轻人提供高品质体操。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">We shall expand to Detroit (my hometown) in September to provide quality gymnastics to youths who deserve this learning opportunity and could benefit from this fantastic Olympic sport.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">In September, we will expand to Detroit (my hometown) to provide high-quality gymnastics to those who deserve this learning opportunity and who will benefit from this remarkable Olympic campaign.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">In September, we will expand to Detroit (my home town) to offer high-quality gymnastics to young people who deserve this learning opportunity and will benefit from this remarkable Olympic sport.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>体操有助于培养身体的力量、灵活性及协调性，还有助于培养吃苦耐劳的精神、自律性及决心。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Gymnastics helps develop physical power, flexibility, and coordination. It also helps develop perseverance, self-discipline, and determination.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Gymnastics can help to cultivate the strength, flexibility and coordination of the body, but also help to cultivate hard-working spirit, self-discipline and determination.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Gymnastics contributes to the development of physical strength, flexibility and coordination. It also helps to develop a hard-working spirit, self-discipline and determination.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>这些可为一个人的健康、学业及工作成功带来终身益处。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">These can bring lifetime benefits to a person’s health, academic and career success.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">These can lead to lifelong benefits for a person's health, education, and success in work.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">These can have lifelong benefits for a person's health, academic and professional success.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>受这支队伍的鼓舞，成千上万名年轻女孩将学习体操，这真的很棒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Encouraged by this team, many girls will take up gymnastics. This is wonderful.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Inspired by this team, thousands of young girls will learn gymnastics, which is really great.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Inspired by this team, thousands of young girls will learn gymnastics, which is really great.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>参加运动意义重大，对女孩来说尤其如此。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">Participation in sports carries great significance, particularly for girls.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Participation in sports is significant, especially for girls.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Participation in sport is significant, particularly for girls.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>这是一个激动人心的时刻。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">This is an inspiring moment.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">It was an exciting moment.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">It's an exciting time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="062_cnn.167026_en.sl">
    <source>感谢西蒙、阿里、劳瑞、加布丽埃勒及麦迪逊在赢得奥运团体金牌过程中所精彩展现出来的“女孩力量”，也感谢她们激励如此多背景各异的年轻女孩开启通向健康、强大、成功之路。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.ht">We would like to thank Simone, Aly, Laurie, Gabrielle and Madison for their dazzling display of “girl power” enroute to winning the Olympic team gold medal, and we would also like to thank them for inspiring young girls from different backgrounds to unlock their path toward health, strength and success.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.gg">Thanks to Simon, Ali, Laurie, Gabrielle and Madison for the "Girl power" that has been shown in winning the Olympic team gold medals, and for inspiring young girls with so many backgrounds to open the path to health, greatness and success.</translation>
    <translation system="062_cnn.167026_en.c6">Thank you to Simon, Ali, Lawrie, Gabrielle and Madison for their "girl power" in winning the Olympic team gold medal, and for inspiring so many young girls of all backgrounds to embark on the path to health, strength and success.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
