<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>如何在持枪攻击中使用马伽术保护自己</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">How to use krav maga to protect yourself in the event of a gun attack</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">How to protect yourself with the use of gamma in a gun attack</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">How to Protect Yourself with Gamma in a Gun Attack</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>这个世界很危险，但是 Dailymail.com 上的这个视频或许能带给你一点安全感。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">This world is a dangerous place, but the video on Dailymail.com may provide you with a sense of security.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">The world is dangerous, but this video on DailyMail. com may give you a sense of security.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">The world is a dangerous place, but this video on Dailymail.com may give you a sense of security.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>我们向纽约的马伽术联盟 (Krav Maga Federation) 大师 Rhon Mizrachi 请教，了解如何近距离应对持枪行凶者。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">We then asked master Rhon Mizrachi of the Krav Maga Federation of New York to understand how to deal with an assailant armed with a gun at close range.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">We consulted the master Rhon Mizrachi of New York's Krav Maga Federation to learn how to deal with gunmen at close range.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">We asked Rhon Mizrachi, a master of the Krav Maga Federation in New York, for advice on how to deal with gun-toting assailants at close range.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>不论他是从前面，还是后面靠近你，该视频都会教你如何转败为胜。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">It does not matter if he approaches from the front or rear. This video will teach you how to reverse such encounters to your advantage.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">Whether he is close to you from the front or behind, the video will teach you how to defeat.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">Whether he's approaching you from the front or the back, the video will teach you how to turn defeat into victory.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>Mizrachi 说，如果枪手从后面靠近你，你首先要做的就是转身，以便你能看到袭击者，并“清除火线”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">Mizrachi said if the gunman approaches you from the back, the first thing to do is to turn around to get a good look at the attacker and to “eliminate the line of fire”.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">Mizrachi said that if the shooter approached you from behind, the first thing you had to do was turn around so that you could see the attacker and "clear the line".</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">If the gunman approaches you from behind, the first thing you have to do is turn around so you can see the attacker and "clear the line of fire," Mizrachi said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>接着，用前臂和肩膀夹住枪，然后用你的肘部击打袭击者面部。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">Then clamped the gun by forearm and shoulder, before striking the face of attacker by your elbow.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">Then, hold the gun with your forearm and shoulder and hit the attacker on the face with your elbow.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">Then, hold the gun between your forearms and shoulders, and then hit the attacker in the face with your elbow.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>接下来用膝盖顶其腹股沟，当袭击者因疼痛而弯下身子时，扭转他手中的枪，用枪管和后备枪组打他的脸，保持武器一直对准他。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">Next, hit the assailant’s groin with the knee cap. When the assailant bends over in pain, turn the gun in his hand around and hit his face with the gun barrel and the rear of the gun, making sure that the weapon is pointed at him.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">Then with the knee on his groin, when the attacker bent over with pain, he reversed his gun, hit him in the face with the barrel and the backing gun, and kept the weapon on him.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">Next he put his knee to his groin and, as the attacker bent over in pain, turned the gun in his hand and hit him in the face with the barrel and reserve gun, keeping the weapon pointed at him.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>如果枪手从前面靠近，也采用类似技巧——让你的身体不在火线范围内，夺取枪并扭转枪口，以便枪手不能开火。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">If the shooter approaches from the front, use the same technique - move  your body away from the scope of the firing line, grab the gun and flip muzzle around to prevent the shooter from shooting.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">If the gunman comes in from the front, it also uses a similar technique--to keep your body out of the firing line, grab the gun and twist the muzzle so that the shooter doesn't fire.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">If the gunman approaches from the front, use a similar technique - keep your body out of the line of fire, seize the gun and reverse the muzzle so that the gunman can't fire.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>与此同时，将重量压在枪上并击打袭击者的胸部，并从他紧握的手中扭转枪口，然后将枪口对准他。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">At the same time, put your weight on the gun and hit the chest area of the assailant, and then turn the gun held by the assailant around so that it faces him instead.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">At the same time, press the weight on the gun and hit the attacker on the chest and twist the muzzle from his clenched hand and then point the muzzle at him.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">At the same time, weight was placed on the gun and the attacker was hit in the chest and the muzzle was twisted from his clenched hands before being pointed at him.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>听起来很复杂？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">Does it sound complicated?</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">Sounds complicated?</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">Sounds complicated?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>查看视频，看看 Mizrachi 到底是怎么做的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">Take a look at the video to see how Mizrachi actually did it.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">Check out the video to see what Mizrachi is doing.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">Check out the video to see exactly how Mizrachi does it.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.sl">
    <source>但是请记住，如果你不是马伽术大师的话，要想摆脱抢劫，最安全的办法就是交出现金。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.ht">But remember, if you're not a master of Krav Maga, the safest method to get out of a mugging situation is to hand over your cash.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.gg">But remember, if you're not the master of the Gamma, the safest way to get out of a robbery is to hand over the cash.</translation>
    <translation system="021_dailymail.co.uk.170739_en.c6">But remember, if you're not a maestro, the safest way to get rid of a robbery is to hand over the cash.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
