<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>里约奥运会上长相酷似凯特王妃的自行车手及撞脸其他名人的选手受到追捧</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Growing fad for Rio Olympics cyclist bearing resemblance to Catherine, the Duchess of Cambridge, and other celebrity-lookalike athletes</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">The contestants who look like Kate Middleton's cyclists and other celebrities in the Rio Olympics have been courted.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Cyclists who look like Princess Kate and bump into other celebrities at the Rio Olympics are in hot demand</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>本周，2016里约奥运会上长相酷似凯特王妃的法国自行车手波林·费朗德·普雷沃 (Pauline Ferrand Prevot) 受到了观众们的大力追捧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">At the 2016 Rio Olympic Games this week, French cyclist Pauline Frrand Prevot, Princess Kate’s doppelganger, attracted much attention among viewers.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">The French cyclist 波林·费朗德·普雷沃 (Pauline Ferrand Prevot), who looks like Kate Middleton in the 2016 Rio Olympics this week, was eagerly sought after by viewers.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Pauline Ferrand Prevot, the French cyclist who looks exactly like Princess Kate at the 2016 Rio Olympics, has been courted by viewers this week.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>但是这位24岁的奥运选手不是本届夏季奥运会上唯一一位撞脸名人的金牌争夺者，至少社交媒体不这样认为。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">However, this 24-year old Olympic athlete is not the only one to run into a celebrity in this Summer Olympics. At least that’s what the social media believes in.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">But the 24-year-old is not the only gold medalist in this summer's Olympics, at least not by social media.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">But the 24-year-old Olympian isn't the only gold-medal contender to hit a celebrity face at this summer's Olympics, at least not on social media.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>因此，为纪念里约奥运会与当时屏幕上出现的所有名人脸，FEMAIL 整理了一份撞脸好莱坞明星的奥运选手名单。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">To celebrate all celebrity faces that have appeared in the Rio Olympics and television screens at that time, FEMAIL has compiled a list of Olympic athletes whose face bear close resemblance to that of Hollywood celebrities.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">So, to commemorate the Rio Olympics and all the celebrity faces appearing on the screen at that time, FEMAIL sorted out a list of the Olympians who had bumped into Hollywood stars.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">So, in honor of the Rio Olympics and all the celebrity faces that appeared on screen at the time, FEMAIL has put together a list of Olympians who have hit Hollywood stars.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>猎人与狼：美国男子射箭队员布莱迪·埃里森 (Brady Ellison)（左）从小就被比作莱昂纳多·迪卡普里奥 (Leonardo DiCaprio)</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Hunter and the wolf: Brady Ellison (left) of the US men's archer team who has been compared to Leonardo DiCaprio since a young age.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Hunter and Wolf: American male archery player 布莱迪·埃里森 (Brady Ellison) (left) from childhood to Leonardo DiCaprio (Leonardo DiCaprio)</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Hunter and Wolf: American men's archer Brady Ellison (left) has been compared to Leonardo DiCaprio since childhood</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>除了自行车赛道上撞脸凯特的选手外，很多网民很快发现某位射箭选手简直就是莱昂纳多·迪卡普里奥的孪生兄弟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">In addition to the contestant on the cycling track who was Kate's doppelganger, many netizens soon discovered that a certain archer was the twin of Leonardo DiCaprio.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">In addition to the contestants who hit Kate on the bike track, many netizens quickly discovered that an archer was a twin brother of Leonardo DiCaprio.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">In addition to the cyclist who bumped into Kate on the track, many Internet users quickly discovered that an archer was the twin brother of Leonardo DiCaprio.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>自从他的酷似于《华尔街狼人》 (Wolf of Wall Street) 主演造型的照片在推特上曝光后，美国男子射箭队员布莱迪·埃里森就在社交媒体上引起了巨大骚动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Ever since his photograph that bore a striking resemblance to the Wolf of Wall Street protagonist was revealed on Twitter, the American archer Brady Ellison started a massive trend in social media networks.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">The American male archery 布莱迪·埃里森 has caused a great stir in social media since his photograph of the Wall, the Wolf of the Wall Street, has been exposed to Twitter.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Brady Ellison, an American male archer, has caused a huge stir on social media since pictures of him posing as the star of the Wolf of Wall Street emerged on Twitter.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>事实上，这位射箭选手察觉到了社交媒体的炒作并承认打小就有人说自己长得像小李子。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">In fact, the archer sensed the hype in the social media and admitted that he has been said to have a "DiCaprio face" since a kid.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">In fact, the Archer sensed the hype of social media and admitted that small people said they looked like little plums.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">In fact, the archer sensed the hype on social media and admitted that when he was young, some people said he looked like a plum.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>“我自认为除了络腮胡以外，并不是长得很像，”布莱迪对《赫芬顿邮报》(Huffington Post) 说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">“I think that other than the beard, we don't look very much alike,” Brady told Huffington Post.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">"I don't think it looks like anything other than a beard," Brady told the Huffington Post (Huffington Post).</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">"I don't think I look much alike, except for the beard," Brady told the Huffington Post.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>“他是一个长相帅气的花花公子，所以我想这是对我的夸赞吧。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">“He looks like a handsome playboy. I guess I should take this as a compliment.”</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">"He's a good-looking playboy, so I guess it's a compliment." ”</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">"He's a good-looking dude, so I think that's a compliment."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>2012伦敦奥运会上最流行的对比之一今年无疑将被找到更多相似之处：英国跳远选手格雷格·卢瑟福 (Greg Rutherford) 长得像极了著名演员尼尔·帕特里克·哈里斯 (Neil Patrick Harris)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">The "celebrity face match" popular in the 2012 London Olympic Games are even hotter this year, for example the British jumper  Greg Rutherford and the famous Neil Patrick Harris.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">One of the most popular contrasts in the 2012 London Olympics will no doubt be found in more similarities this year: The British long jumper 格雷格·卢瑟福 (Greg Rutherford) looks like a famous actor Harris (Neil Patrick Harris).</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">One of the most popular comparisons at the 2012 London Olympics will no doubt find more similarities this year: Great Britain's long jumper Greg Rutherford looks exactly like the famous actor Neil Patrick Harris.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>长着一双会说话的大眼睛的俄罗斯体操选手穆斯塔芬娜 (Aliya Mustafina) 被指长相酷似古巴裔美国歌星格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡 (Gloria Estefan)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Russian gymnast Aliya Mustafina has eyes that spoke volumes, and is said to resemble Cuban American singer Gloria Estefan.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Mustafina (Aliya Mustafina), a Russian gymnast with big, talking eyes, was said to resemble Cuban-American singer 格洛丽亚·埃斯特凡 (Gloria Estefan).</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Aliya Mustafina, a Russian gymnast with big talking eyes, has been accused of looking like Gloria Estefan, a Cuban-American singer.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>而在泳坛，多年来，南非游泳运动员卡梅伦·范德伯格 (Cameron van der Burgh) 一直被拿来和《欢乐合唱团》(Glee) 主演马修·莫里森 (Matthew Morrison) 做比较。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">In the swimming arena, South African swimmer Cameron van der Burgh has always been compared with Matthew Morrison, the main singer of Glee.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">In swimming, for years, South African swimmer 卡梅伦·范德伯格 (Cameron van der Burgh) has been compared to "Glee" (Glee) starring Matthew Morrison (Matthew Morrison).</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">And in swimming, South African swimmer Cameron van der Burgh has been compared to "Glee" star Matthew Morrison for years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>换装：该用户认为倪家骏 (Nathan Adrian) 是该《盗梦空间》(Inception) 演员的“运动版”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Reload: This user feels that Nathan Adrian is the “sports version” of this Inception actor.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Dress up: The user thinks Yi Jia Jun (Nathan Adrian) is the "sports version" of the "Inception" (Inception) actor.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Dress up: The user believes Nathan Adrian is a 'sporty version' of the Inception actor</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>另外一对老被拿来比较的是网球明星拉菲尔·纳达尔 (Rafael Nadal) 和演员乔什·哈奈特 (Josh Hartnett)，他们的浓眉和嘴唇长得很像。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Another common comparison is the tennis star Rafael Nadal and the actor Josh Hartnett. The two bear striking resemblance thanks to their thick eyebrows and lips.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Another pair of old men were compared to tennis star Nadal (Rafael Nadal) and actor Hartnett (Josh Hartnett), whose eyebrows and lips looked alike.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Another pair that is often compared are tennis star Rafael Nadal and actor Josh Hartnett, who have thick eyebrows and lips that resemble each other.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>摘得银牌的俄罗斯游泳选手艾菲莫 (Yulia Efimova) 和演员安娜丽尼·麦考德 (Annalynne McCord) 拥有同样的古铜色皮肤和金发，而美国队的倪家骏则被粉丝比作“运动版的约瑟夫·高登·莱维特 (Joseph Gorgon Levitt)”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Russian swimmer Yulia Efimova who won the silver medal share the similar bronze skin tone and blond hair as actress Annalynne McCord, while Nathan Adrian of the US team has been regarded, by his fans, as the “athletic version of Joseph Gorgon Levitt”.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Russian swimmer Effimo (Yulia Efimova) and actor 安娜丽尼·麦考德 (AnnaLynne McCord) have the same bronze skin and blonde hair, while the American team's Yi Jia Jun is likened to "the sporty version of 约瑟夫·高登·莱维特" (Joseph Gorgon Levitt) ".</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Silver medal-winning Russian swimmer Yulia Efimova and actor Annalynne McCord have the same bronzed skin and blonde hair, while Team USA's Ni Jiajun has been compared by fans to the 'sporty Joseph Gorgon Levitt'.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>女汉子：足球明星霍普·索罗 (Hope Solo)（左）和《嗜血法医》(Dexter) 演员珍妮弗·卡彭特(Jennifer Carpenter)（右）拥有相似的脸型和眼睛</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Heroines: Football star Hope Solo (left) and actress Jennifer Carpenter who starred in Dexter (right) have similar facial shapes and eyes.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Female man: Soccer star 霍普·索罗 (Hope Solo) (left) and "bloodthirsty forensic" (Dexter) actor 珍妮弗·卡彭特 (Jennifer Carpenter) (right) with similar face shape and eyes</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">FEMALE MAN: Soccer star Hope Solo (left) and Dexter actor Jennifer Carpenter (right) have similar faces and eyes</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>不是唯一的一个：一位推特用户很开心地发现其他人也看到了这些相似之处</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Not one and only: A Twitter user happily discovered that others also noticed the similarities</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Not the only one: a Twitter user is happy to find that other people have seen these similarities</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Not the only one: One Twitter user was happy to find that others saw the similarities as well</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>传播理论：据这位用户说，这一对长得像或许是有原因的</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Communication theory: According to this user, there may be a reason why the pair look alike</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Communication theory: According to the user, this pair looks like maybe there's a reason.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Communication theory: According to this user, the pair may look alike for a reason</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>一位推特用户最近开心地在网上宣称“其他网民也认为霍普·索罗和珍妮弗·卡彭特实际上长得一模一样。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">A Twitter user recently announced happily on the net that “other netizens also think that Hope Solo and Jennifer Carpenter actually look exactly alike.”</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">One Twitter user recently happily claimed online that "other netizens also think 霍普·索罗 and 珍妮弗·卡彭特 actually look exactly the same." ”</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">One Twitter user recently happily declared online that "other netizens agree that Hope Solo and Jennifer Carpenter actually look exactly alike."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>确实，这位美国足球明星和这位《嗜血法医》主演拥有相似度极高的脸型和眼睛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Indeed, the American football star and the leading actor of Dexter shared the similar facial forms and eyes.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Indeed, the American football star and the bloodthirsty M.E. have a very similar face and eyes.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Indeed, the American football star and the Bloodthirsty Forensics star have remarkably similar faces and eyes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.sl">
    <source>其他流行的对比包括克丽·沃尔什·詹宁斯 (Kerri Walsh·Jennings)，她的笑容几乎和女演员劳拉·琳妮 (Laura Linney) 的一模一样；还有获得金牌的体操选手盖比·道格拉斯 (Gabby Douglas)，她美丽而灿烂的笑容与《魅力四射》 (Bring It On star) 明星加布里埃尔·尤尼恩 (Gabrielle Union) 的笑容如出一辙。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.ht">Other popular comparisons include Kerri Walsh Jennings, whose smile is almost similar to actress Laura Linney, as well as gold medal winning gymnast Gabby Douglas, whose beautiful and radiant smile is exactly the same as Bring It On star Gabrielle Union.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.gg">Other popular comparisons include 克丽·沃尔什·詹宁斯 (Kerri Walsh· Jennings), her smile almost the same as the actress Laura Catherine (Laura Linney), and the gold-medal gymnast 盖比·道格拉斯 (Gabby Douglas), her beautiful and brilliant smile and "glamour" (Bring It on Star) Star Gabrielle (Gabrielle Union) smiles the same.</translation>
    <translation system="082_dailymail.co.uk.170695_en.c6">Other popular comparisons include Kerri Walsh Jennings, who has a smile almost identical to that of actress Laura Linney, and gymnast Gabby Douglas, who won the gold medal, who has a beautiful and radiant smile similar to that of Bringing It On star Gabrielle Union.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
