<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>昆斯费里大桥现已通至法夫</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Queensferry Crossing is now connected to Fife</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">The Queensferry Bridge is now in Fife.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">The Quinsferri Bridge is now accessible to Fife.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>该斥资13.5亿英镑的项目计划于2017年5月完工</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">The planned completion for the 1.35 billion Sterling Pound project is May 2017.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">The £ 1.35 billion project is scheduled to be completed in May 2017</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">The £1.35 billion project is scheduled to be completed in May 2017</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>工程师们已经把昆斯费里大桥 (Queensferry Crossing) 的北桥面和高架桥连接到一起，也就是说大桥如今已通至法夫。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Engineers have joined the north deck and viaduct of Queensferry Crossing, and said that the bridge now provides access to Fife.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">Engineers have connected the North Bridge of the Queensferry Bridge (Queensferry Crossing) to the viaduct, which means that it is now in Fife.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">Engineers have linked the northern deck of the Queensferry Crossing to the viaduct, which means the bridge is now connected to Fife.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>位于每座大桥三个桥头堡附近的四处“桥面风机”合龙现已接近竣工，而该项目为首个合龙的大桥。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">The joining of the “deck fans” around the three towers of each bridge is near completion, and the project is the first joint bridge.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">The closure of the "bridge deck fan" near the three bridgehead of each bridge is nearing completion and the project is headed for a closed bridge.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">The four "bridge fan" arcs near each of the bridge's three bridgeheads are now nearing completion, and the project is the first of its kind.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>起始于法夫的这段大桥长600米，重30,000公吨。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">The bridge that started at Fife has a length of 600 meters and a mass of 30,000 tons.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">The bridge starting in Fife is 600 metres long and weighs 30,000 tonnes.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">The bridge, which began in Fife, is 600 metres long and weighs 30,000 tonnes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>它使用了10,000公吨钢材、20,000公吨混凝土和46根斜拉索。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">10,000 tonnes of steel, 20,000 tonnes of concrete and 46 stay cables were used.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">It uses 10,000 metric tons of steel, 20,000 metric tons of concrete and 46 diagonal cables.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">It employs 10,000 metric tons of steel, 20,000 metric tons of concrete and 46 cables.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>该斥资13.5亿英镑的项目计划于2017年5月完工。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">The GBP1.35 billion project is scheduled for completion in May 2017.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">The £ 1.35 billion BN project is scheduled to be completed in May 2017.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">The £1.35 billion project is scheduled to be completed in May 2017.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>经济部长基思·布朗 (Keith Brown) 今天参观了现场，成为首批登上大桥的人之一。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Minister of Economy Keith Brown visited the venue today and became one of the first people to ascend the Crossing.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">Keith Brown, the economics minister, visited the scene today as one of the first people to board the bridge, 基思·布朗.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">Economy Minister Keith Brown visited the site today, becoming one of the first people to get on the bridge.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>他说："这是昆斯费里大桥建造过程中的一个历史性时刻。"</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">He said: “This is a historical moment for the building of the Queensferry Crossing.”</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">"This is a historic moment in the construction process of the Queensferry Bridge," he said. "</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">"This is a historic moment in the construction of the Quincy Bridge," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>我们都见证了在如此宏大项目上的工程作业，光是建造该大桥的这一段就使用了超过30,000公吨混凝土和钢材。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">We have witnessed the engineering work of such a massive project. More than 30,000 tonnes of concrete and steel were used just to build this section of this enormous bridge.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">We have all witnessed the engineering work on such a grand project, which uses more than 30,000 metric tons of concrete and steel in this section of the bridge.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">We have all witnessed engineering work on such an ambitious project, with more than 30,000 metric tons of concrete and steel used in this section of the bridge alone.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>尽管该桥的规模和重量都很巨大，但是完成高架桥和桥面之间的合龙却需要精细作业，需要非常精准的装配。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Despite the sheer size and mass of this bridge, completion of the elevated bridge and the joining of the bridge surface require precision engineering as well as equipment and parts made with great accuracy.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">Although the bridge is large in size and weight, the closure between the viaduct and the bridge requires meticulous work and very precise assembly.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">Despite the size and weight of the bridge, completing the connection between the viaduct and the bridge deck requires delicate work and very precise assembly.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>总的来说，近79%的总桥面现已安装完成，最后一段桥面的混凝土桥面今天在 Rosyth 浇注，也就是说所有桥面都已做好就位准备。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">On the whole, close to 79% of the bridge deck has been installed. The concrete deck of the last bridge deck was cast at Rosyth today. In other words, the entire bridge deck is ready.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">In general, nearly 79% of the total bridge deck is now installed, the last section of the bridge deck concrete bridge today in Rosyth pouring, that is, all the decks are ready.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">Overall, nearly 79 per cent of the total deck has now been installed and the concrete deck of the last section of the bridge was poured in Rosyth today, meaning that all decks are in place.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>昆斯费里大桥建造公司项目总监 Michael Martin 说："不管是哪个大桥项目，第一次合龙都是一个重大里程碑。"</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Queensferry Crossing Construction Company project supervisor Michael Martin said: “The first closure of the bridge surface is an important milestone for any bridge project.”</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">Queensferry Bridge Construction Company project director Michael Martin said: "No matter which bridge project, the first closure is a major milestone." "</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">"Whichever bridge project it is, the first one is a major milestone," said Michael Martin, project director at Quincy Bridge Construction Company.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>就该了不起的项目而言，此次合龙展现出前沿的土木工程技术。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">As far as this awesome project, the joining of the bridge displays cutting edge civil engineering technology.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">In terms of this remarkable project, the closure shows the frontier of civil engineering technology.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">As far as this remarkable project is concerned, Hailong has demonstrated cutting-edge civil engineering technology.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>安装最后一段路面板并将之连接至扩大的北桥堡路面板之后，接下来需要完成北侧或者接近陆地一侧的剩余缺口合龙。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Install the road slabs at the last section, and after connecting them to the road slabs of the expanded Beiqiaobao, join the remaining gaps on the north or the section close to land.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">After installing the last section of the pavement and connecting it to the enlarged North Bridge pavement, the remainder of the remaining gap on either side or near the land will need to be closed.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">After installing the final section of the road panel and connecting it to the expanded Northbridge Fort Road panel, the remaining gap closure on the north side or close to the land side needs to be completed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>完成该项作业需把北部高架引桥南移700毫米。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">Completing this work requires shifting the northern approach viaduct by 700 millimeters.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">The completion of this operation requires the North elevated approach to move south 700 mm.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">The completion of this operation will require the relocation of the northern viaduct approach bridge to the south by 700 millimetres.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>这是一次规模巨大的作业，同时也是一次非常精密的作业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">This was a task of enormous scale, and one of extreme precision.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">It was a huge operation and a very sophisticated one.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">It was a huge operation and at the same time it was a very sophisticated operation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>说它规模巨大，是因为高架桥长222米，重约6,000公吨，需要拉出一个约3%的斜度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">It is described as enormous because the viaduct is 222 meters long and weighs approximately 6,000 tonnes, requiring an incline of about 3%.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">It is large because the viaduct is 222 metres long and weighs about 6,000 tonnes and needs to pull out a slope of about 3%.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">It is said to be huge because the viaduct is 222 meters long and weighs about 6,000 metric tons, and needs to be pulled out at an angle of about 3 percent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>说它精密，是因为工程团队需要确保偏差非常之小，每边只有几毫米。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">For precision, the engineering team must ensure that the offsets are extremely small and kept within several millimeters on each side.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">It is precise because the engineering team needs to make sure that the deviations are very small, with only a few millimeters on each side.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">It's sophisticated because the engineering team needs to make sure that the deviation is very small, just a few millimetres on each side.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="041_bbc.242497_en.sl">
    <source>令人欣慰的是，一切都进展得很顺利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.ht">What’s comforting is that everything was implemented smoothly.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.gg">Thankfully, everything went well.</translation>
    <translation system="041_bbc.242497_en.c6">Thankfully, everything is going well.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
