<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月12日上午，国务院新闻办就2016年7月份国民经济运行情况举行新闻发布会。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">On the morning of August 12, the State Council Information Office held a press conference on the operating conditions of the nation’s economy in July 2016.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">On the morning of August 12, the State Council News office held a press conference on the operation of national economy in July 2016.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">On the morning of August 12, the Information Office of the State Council held a press conference on the operation of the national economy in July 2016.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>国家统计局新闻发言人、国民经济综合统计司司长盛来运表示，7月份，国民经济部分指标增速有所放缓，但仍运行在合理区间。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">Sheng Laiyun, National Bureau of Statistics Spokesman and Deputy Director-General of the Department of Comprehensive Statistics said that a number of national economic indicators grew at a slower rate in July but were still operating within a reasonable range.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">Laiyun, Director of National Bureau of Statistics and Statistics, said that in July, some indicators of the national economy slowed down, but still operating in a reasonable range.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Sheng Laiyun, spokesman for the National Bureau of Statistics and director of the General Statistics Department of the National Economy, said that the growth rate of some indicators of the national economy had slowed in July, but it was still operating within a reasonable range.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>国家统计局发布的数据显示，7月份固定资产投资增速、进口总额等数据有所回落。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">Figures from the National Bureau of Statistics revealed that fixed asset investment growth, total imports and other data declined again in July.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">Statistics released by the National Bureau of Statistics show that July fixed assets investment growth, total imports and other data fell.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Figures released by the National Bureau of Statistics show that the growth rate of fixed-asset investment and total imports fell in July.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>盛来运说，关于7月份的国民经济运行情况，我想借用总理曾经讲过的一句话“形有波动，势仍向好”，这能够比较好地概括7月份的经济运行的特征。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">Sheng Laiyun said, “As far as the operating condition of the national economy in July is concerned, I would like to borrow a phrase from the Premier, and that is ‘fluctuations exist but the trend remains positive’. This can better encapsulate the characteristics of the economy in July.”</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">Laiyun said that on the national economy in the July, I would like to borrow the words of the prime Minister has said that "the shape of volatility, the trend is still good", which can better summarize the characteristics of the July economic operation.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Sheng Laiyun said that with regard to the performance of the national economy in July, I would like to borrow a phrase once spoken by the Prime Minister, "The situation is fluctuating and the trend is still positive," which can better summarize the characteristics of the economic operation in July.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他解释“形有波动”是指7月份部分经济指标增速确实是有所回落。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">He explained that “fluctuations exist in the trend” refers to the fact that the growth rates of some of the July economic indicators have indeed declined.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">He explained that "form fluctuation" means that some of the growth rate of economic indicators in July did fall.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">He explained that "volatility" refers to the fact that the growth rate of some economic indicators did decline in July.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因为7月份国内外经济仍处在深度调整之中，国际形势复杂多变，世界经济的复苏不及预期，所以出口压力还是比较大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">The pressure on exporting sector is still huge due to the  drastic adjustment of domestic and international economy in July, profound change of international situation and the  world economic recovery failed the expectation.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">Since July domestic and foreign economy is still in the depth adjustment, the international situation is complex and changeable, the world economy recovery is not expected, so the export pressure is still relatively big.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Because the domestic and foreign economies were still undergoing deep adjustment in July, the international situation was complicated and changeable, and the recovery of the world economy was less than expected, so the pressure on exports was still relatively strong.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从国内情况看，整个经济还处在调整的关键阶段，调整的阵痛在释放，经济面临不小的下行压力，所以有些指标有些波动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">Domestically, the entire economy is still going through adjustments, and some adverse reactions to this adjustment have surfaced. Some indicators may fluctuate as the economy faces significant downward pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">From the domestic situation, the whole economy is still at the critical stage of adjustment, the pain of adjustment is released, the economy is facing a big downward pressure, so some of the indicators are somewhat volatile.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Domestically, the economy as a whole is still in the crucial stage of adjustment, the pain of adjustment is being released and the economy is facing considerable downward pressure, so some indicators are somewhat volatile.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>盛来运指出，7月份还有一个特殊情况，洪涝灾害比较严重，高温酷暑天气对一些地区的生产经营带来了一些影响。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">Sheng Laiyun pointed out the occurrence of extraordinary events in July: floods were worse than usual, and the hot weather and high temperatures affected production and the operations of some regions.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">Laiyun pointed out that there is a special situation in July, the flood disaster is more serious, high temperature and heat weather on some areas of production and operation has brought some impact.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Sheng noted that there was also a special situation in July, with more severe flooding and severe heat, which had some impact on production and operations in some areas.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>根据民政部最近发布的情况，全国6000多万人受灾，直接经济损失超过2000亿元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">Latest information released by the Ministry of Civil Affairs showed that the disaster has affected over 60 million people and led to a direct economic loss of over 200 billion RMB.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">According to the Ministry of Civil Affairs recently released the situation, more than 60 million people nationwide disaster, direct economic losses of more than 200 billion yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">According to a recent release by the Ministry of Civil Affairs, more than 60 million people across the country have been affected by the disaster, with direct economic losses of more than 200 billion yuan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从工业、投资、交通运输相关指标看，这些地区不同程度受到影响。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">These regions have been affected to varying degrees based on relevant industrial, investment and transportation indicators.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">From the relevant indicators of industry, investment and transportation, these areas are affected in varying degrees.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">These areas are affected to varying degrees in terms of industrial, investment and transport-related indicators.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>7月份的货物周转运量增速比上月回落3.6个百分点，洪涝灾害对这些地区的交通有一定的影响。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">The growth in inventory turnover volume in July dropped 3.6% compared to last month. The flooding disaster has imposed a certain degree of influence to traffic in these areas.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">In July, the volume of goods turnover slowed down by 3.6% last month, and the flood disaster had a certain impact on the traffic in these areas.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">The growth rate of goods turnover in July fell 3.6 percentage points from the previous month, with flooding having some impact on traffic in these areas.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从这些因素来看，7月份部分指标出现波动也是很正常，也是在预期之中。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">These factors show that volatility in some of the indicators in July is normal and within expectations.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">Judging from these factors, the volatility of some of the July indicators is also normal and is expected.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">Judging from these factors, it is also normal and expected that some of the indicators will fluctuate in July.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他表示，“势仍向好”指的是尽管经济增速有所回落，但是经济运行总体平稳，稳中有进、稳中向好的大势没有变。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">He said that the “trend is still positive” meant that although economic growth has decelerated, the economy was running steadily on the whole. The general trend of improvement amid stability and growing positively amid stability remained unchanged.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">He said, "the potential is still good" means that despite the slowdown in economic growth, but the overall smooth economic operation, stability in the direction of the good trend has not changed.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">He said the "trend is still positive" refers to the fact that despite the slowdown in economic growth, the overall economic performance is stable, steady and positive trend has not changed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.sl">
    <source>7月份CPI上涨1.8%，环比上涨0.2%;1-7月份CPI上涨2.1%，所以物价形势总体稳定。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.ht">CPI rose by 1.8% in July, and grew by 0.2% when compared to the previous period. CPI from January to July rose by 2.1%. These figures indicate that trends for commodity prices have, in general, remained steady.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.gg">July CPI Rose 1.8%, the chain Rose 0.2%; 1-July CPI Rose 2.1%, so the price situation is generally stable.</translation>
    <translation system="116_ifeng0812.news.49765988_0_zh.c6">CPI rose 1.8 per cent in July, up 0.2 per cent month-on-month, and 2.1 per cent in January-July, so prices are generally stable.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
