<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.sl">
    <source>市残联副理事长于波出席活动并作重要讲话。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.ht">Chang Yubo, the deputy director of the Disabled Persons’ Federation of the city, attended the event and gave an important address.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.gg">Vice Chairman of the City Federation of Disabled Bo attended the event and made an important speech.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.c6">City Disabled Association vice president Yu Bo attended the event and made an important speech.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.sl">
    <source>出席领导共同为第二批“爱心原山”雷锋私家车队授牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.ht">Leaders who were present presented an award to the second “Loving Yuanshan” Lei Feng private fleet of vehicles.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.gg">Attended the leadership jointly for the second batch of "Love Original Mountain" Lei Feng's private team award.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.c6">Attending the leadership jointly for the second batch of "love the original mountain" Lei Feng private car team licensing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.sl">
    <source>20年来，“爱心原山”以实际行动书写着人间大爱，原山林场先后接管、代管了5个困难事业单位，直接安置职工近千人次。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.ht">For over 20 years, the “Loving Yuanshan” project has employed actual actions to provide charitable services to the entire society. Yuanshan Forest Farm has received and managed 5 business units in difficult straits, helping to resettle nearly a thousand employees in the process.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.gg">Over the past 20 years, "Love the original Mountain" to the actual action to write the human Big Love, the original forest field successively took over, hosted 5 difficult institutions, direct placement workers nearly thousand.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.c6">Over the past 20 years, the "love of the original mountain" with practical action to write the great love of the world, the original mountain forest farm has taken over, in charge of the five institutions in difficulty, direct placement of workers nearly a thousand times.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在每次重大灾害面前，原山人都自发组织捐款捐物，向社会伸出援助之手。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.ht">When experiencing a major disaster, the people of Yuanshan will organize themselves to donate money and items, providing a helpful hand to the society.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.gg">In the face of each major disaster, the original people have spontaneously organized donations donated to the community to lend a helping hand.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.c6">In the face of every major disaster, the original mountain people have spontaneously organized donations to the community to lend a helping hand.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.sl">
    <source>全国道德模范提名奖、原山林场党委书记孙建博说，雷锋精神传承着时代的真善美，是一项符合社会主义价值体系的长久事业。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.ht">The spirit of Leifeng is the symbol of truth, rightness and beauty of our ear, a long-term course fitting in socialist values, said  Mr. Sun Jianbo, the Finalist Winner of National Moral Model and former Secretary of Party Committee of Shan LinChang.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.gg">National Moral Model Nomination award, former Mountain Forest Farm party secretary Sun Jianbo said, Lei Feng Spirit inherits the times of the truth and Beauty, is a socialist value system in line with the long-term cause.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.c6">Sun Jianbo, who was nominated for the National Moral Model Award and former party secretary of the Mountain Forest Yard, said the Lei Feng spirit inherits the truth, goodness and beauty of the times and is a long-term undertaking that conforms to the socialist value system.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.sl">
    <source>仪式结束后，参加活动人员参观山东原山艰苦创业纪念馆并体验无障碍设施建设。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.ht">When the ceremony ended, the participants of the event visited the Shandong Yuanshan Pioneers’ Memorial Hall to experience its barrier-free facilities.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.gg">After the ceremony, the participants visited the Shandong original mountain arduous pioneering memorial hall and experienced the barrier-free facilities.</translation>
    <translation system="146_ifeng0812.news.49767542_0_zh.c6">After the ceremony, the participants visited the Shandong Yuanshan Pioneer Memorial Hall and experienced the construction of barrier-free facilities.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
