<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.sl">
    <source>根据省人大常委会今年工作要点安排，常委会计划听取审议专项工作报告，并开展实施银行业监督管理法、服务地方经济发展情况专题询问。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.ht">According to work arrangements made this year by the Provincial People’s Congress Standing Committee, the Standing Committee shall review the project work reports, enforce the Banking Supervision Law, and review topics related to servicing local economic development.</translation>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.gg">According to the main points of this year's work of the NPC Standing Committee, the Standing Committee plans to hear the special report and to carry out special questions on the implementation of the banking supervision and management law and the local economic development.</translation>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.c6">In accordance with the arrangements for the work of the Standing Committee of the Provincial People's Congress for this year, the Standing Committee plans to hear and deliberate special work reports and carry out special inquiries on the implementation of the Law on Banking Supervision and the development of local economies.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月中旬，常委会将组织两个调研组赴部分市开展调研，为专题询问作准备。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.ht">In mid-August, the Standing Committee will organize two survey teams to carry out investigations in a number of branch cities to prepare for inquiries on this matter.</translation>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.gg">In mid-August, the Standing Committee will organize two research teams to conduct research in some cities to prepare for the topic.</translation>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.c6">In mid-August, the Standing Committee will organize two research groups to conduct research in some cities in preparation for special inquiries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.sl">
    <source>花建慧指出，省人大常委会听取和审议垂直管理部门专项工作报告并开展专题询问，在我省尚属首次，是加强和拓展人大监督工作的积极探索。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.ht">Hua Jianhui pointed out that the Provincial People’s Congress Standing Committee have listened and reviewed project reports given by a vertical management department and initiated project inquiries. This is the first time that such actions have been taken in this province, making it an active act of exploration to strengthen and expand the monitoring work of the People’s Congress.</translation>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.gg">Huaijianhui pointed out that the Provincial committee to listen to and consider the vertical management of special work reports and conduct special inquiries, in our province is the first time, is to strengthen and expand the NPC supervision work actively explore.</translation>
    <translation system="045_ifeng0812.news.49765537_0_zh.c6">Hua pointed out that the Standing Committee of the Provincial People's Congress listens to and considers the special work reports of the vertical administrative departments and carries out special inquiries for the first time in our province, which is an active exploration to strengthen and expand the supervision work of the National People's Congress.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
