<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据香港《东方日报》8月12日报道，目前内地钻石销售被指存在三大问题，包括虚标钻石净度推高售价、虚标钻石重量、售后无保障等。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">August 12 news report by Oriental Daily, a Hong Kong news company, said that there are 3 major issues of diamond sales in Mainland China. This includes false labeling of diamond purity to drive up prices, false labeling of diamond mass, and lack of post-sales guarantee.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">According to the Hong Kong Oriental Daily, August 12 reported that the mainland diamond sales are currently referred to three major problems, including the net price of falsely marked diamonds to push high prices, the weight of the diamond, the sale of no security.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">Hong Kong's Oriental Daily reported on August 12, the current mainland diamond sales are alleged to exist in three major problems, including false diamond clarity to push up prices, false diamond weight, after-sale insecurity and so on.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而安特卫普为全球最大的钻石交易中心之一，当地工匠的钻石切割技术名满天下，所出售的钻石经过严格鉴定，深受内地女士的欢迎。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">Antwerp is the largest diamond trading center in the world. Diamond cutting skills of local craftsman are famous throughout the world. The diamonds sold through the city have been stringently classified and are extremely popular amongst women in China.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">While Antwerp is one of the world's largest diamond trading centers, the local artisans of diamond cutting technology world, the sale of diamonds have been rigorously identified by the mainland ladies welcome.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">And Antwerp is one of the world's largest diamond trading centres, with local artisans renowned for their diamond-cutting skills, and the diamonds sold are highly qualified and popular with mainland women.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“一个小布袋，握在手心，轻飘飘的一小撮，价值近百万元”，一名参与代购钻石的刘姓大妈，向内地传媒描述她今年六月在安特卫普的经历。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">“A small palm-sized cloth bag, light and airy, is worth nearly a million”, a lady surnamed Liu purchasing diamonds on behalf of another was describing her experience at Antwerp in June this year to domestic media.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">"A small bag, held in the palm of the hand, a small small, the value of nearly million yuan," a participant in the purchase of the Diamond, Liu surname aunt, to the mainland media described her this year June in Antwerp experience.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">"A small cloth bag, held in the palm of your hand, a light handful, worth nearly a million dollars," said a woman surnamed Liu, who was involved in the purchase of diamonds, describing her experience in Antwerp in June this year to the mainland media.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她指自己把钻石藏在内衣里，连续几日上厕所、洗澡都带着，走路睡觉都十分紧张。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">She said that she hid the diamonds in her underwear. For a few days in a row, she would carry them along with her to the toilet and when she took a shower. She felt extremely nervous even when she was walking or sleeping.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">She refers to the diamond hidden in the underwear, a few days in a row to go to the toilet, bathing, walking to sleep is very tense.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">She said she hid the diamonds in her underwear, carried them to the toilet and shower for days on end, and was nervous about walking and sleeping.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她称在安特卫普所买的钻石，购入价为每克拉约五万五千元，同品质的钻石在厦门的零售价约十一万一千元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">She claimed that diamonds purchased at Antwerp sold for a price of about 55,000 RMB per carat. Diamonds of the same quality could fetch a retail sales price of 111,000 at Xiamen.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">She said Diamonds bought in Antwerp were priced at about $55,000 per carat, with the same quality of diamonds in Xiamen at a retail price of about 111,000 yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">She claims that diamonds bought in Antwerp cost about $55,000 per carat, while diamonds of the same quality retail at about $111,000 in Xiamen.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她日前以购入价加两成，把代购的钻石全部售出，一次过大赚二十万元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">She sold all the diamonds she purchased as agent at a 20% premium to the purchase price, and made a huge lump-sum profit of 200,000 yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">She recently bought the purchase price plus 20%, the purchase of all the Diamonds sold, a large profit of 200,000 yuan.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">A few days ago, she sold all the diamonds on her behalf at a 20% mark-up, making a profit of $200,000 at a time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据内地海关规定，钻石非旅客于行程中的用品或必需品，故属于货品范畴，出入境时需申报，否则或列作走私，情况严重可被判入狱。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.ht">Inland customs regulations stipulate that diamond are not necessities nor are used by the travelers during their trips, and would therefore be regarded as a merchandise and must be declared when entering or leaving the country. Failure to do so would be considered an act of trafficking which is punishable with a prison sentence for serious offenses.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.gg">According to the requirements of the mainland customs, diamond non-travellers may be sentenced to imprisonment for their goods or necessities in the course of their journeys and they are subject to declaration at the time of entry and exit or smuggling.</translation>
    <translation system="165_ifeng0812.news.49765262_0_zh.c6">According to the Mainland Customs, diamonds are not articles or necessities for passengers in their itinerary and therefore fall into the category of goods. They are required to be declared at the time of entry and exit. Otherwise, they may be classified as smuggled goods and are liable to imprisonment in serious cases.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
