<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>艾米是一个聪明漂亮的女孩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">Emmy is a smart and beautiful girl.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">Amy is a smart and beautiful girl.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">Amy is a smart and beautiful girl.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>她性格外向活泼，能与朋友们很好地相处，对环境的适应能力也不错。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">She has a outgoing and lively personality, and gets along well with her friends. She also adapts easily to the environment.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">She is outgoing and lively, able to get along well with her friends and has good adaptability to the environment.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">She is outgoing and lively, gets along well with her friends, and adapts well to the environment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>但艾米心里有一个小小的秘密：她不能长久将注意力集中在她要做的学习、工作任务上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">Amy had a tiny secret however: She was unable to focus on her studies and work.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">But Amy had a little secret: she couldn't keep her focus on the study and work she was going to do.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">But Amy had a little secret in her heart: she couldn't focus on the learning, working tasks she had to do for a long time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>这个秘密陪伴艾米很久了。平时问题并不严重》</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">This secret has accompanied Emmy for a while. Usually, the problems are not that serious.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">This secret accompanies Amy for a long time. The problem is not serious at ordinary times</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">This secret has been with Amy for a long time. Usually it's not a serious problem.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>即便通过分散的，模块化的时间来学习和工作，她也基本上都可以完成任务，并取得不错的成绩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">Although she had to use study and work using scattered, modular time slots, she was able to complete her tasks and achieve great results.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">Even through the decentralized, modular time to learn and work, she can basically accomplish the task, and achieve good results.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">Even with decentralized, modular time to study and work, she can basically get the job done and do well.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>但是，当任务重，时间紧的时候，艾米就感觉到非常痛苦和折磨。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">However, when confronted with a heavy task and pressed for time, Amy would be in agony and feel tortured.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">But when the task is heavy and time is tight, Amy feels very miserable and tortured.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">But when the task was heavy and the time was tight, Amy felt a great deal of pain and suffering.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>个体对于自我暴露及其情绪体验的抵抗，其目的在于不使个体的自我认识与自尊受到威胁。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">The purpose of an individual’s resistance toward self-disclosure and its emotional experience lies in preventing the individual’s self-awareness and self-esteem from being threatened.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">Individual's resistance to self exposure and its emotional experience is aimed at not endangering the individual's self-awareness and self-esteem.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">The purpose of individual resistance to self-exposure and emotional experience is not to endanger the individual's self-knowledge and self-esteem.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>也有些行为主义心理学家把阻抗理解为个体对于其行为矫正的不服从。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">Some behavioral psychologists interpret resistance as an individual’s defiance of efforts to correct his or her behavior.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">Some behavioral psychologists have also interpreted impedance as an individual's disobedience to their behavior correction.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">Some behaviorist psychologists have interpreted impedance as an individual's disobedience to his or her behavior modification.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>我试着让艾米做了一个练习，让她通过呼吸放松的方式让自己平静下来，去感受那份煎熬。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">I tried to have Emmy perform a training, using a breathing routine to relax and calm herself down in order to experience the pain.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">I tried to get Amy to do an exercise and let her calm down by breathing and relaxing to feel the torment.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">I tried to get Amy to do an exercise that allowed her to calm down and feel the pain by breathing in a relaxed way.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.sl">
    <source>而一旦离开那个被困住的情境，她感觉自己放松下来，重新获得了自由。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.ht">Upon leaving the sense of being trapped, she could feel that she was more relaxed and regained her freedom.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.gg">And once out of that trapped situation, she felt relaxed and freed again.</translation>
    <translation system="071_sina0812.eladies.doc-ifxuxnpy9281477_zh.c6">And once she left the trapped situation, she felt relaxed and free again.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
