<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>一名女性在瑞士高速公路上自杀并被辗身亡</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">A woman committed suicide on a highway in Switzerland, and was run over and killed</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">A woman killed herself and died on a Swiss motorway.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">A woman has died after killing herself and being run over on a Swiss motorway</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>受害者于午夜躺在高速公路上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The victims are lying on the highway during midnight.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">The victim lay on the motorway at midnight.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">The victim was lying on the motorway at midnight.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>这名试图自杀的女性于周四清晨在高速公路上被多辆车辗过。目前警方正在寻找目击者。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">This woman who attempted suicide was run over by multiple vehicles on the highway early Thursday morning. The police are looking for witnesses at this time.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">The woman who tried to kill himself was run over by several cars on the motorway in the early Thursday. The police are now looking for witnesses.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">The woman who tried to kill herself was run over by a number of cars on the highway early Thursday morning and police are looking for witnesses.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>这场事故发生在周四凌晨沃州莫尔日附近的A1高速公路上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The incident occurred in the early Thursday morning at Highway A1 near Morges at the canton of Vaud.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">The accident occurred on the A1 Highway near Vaud/waadt in early Thursday.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">The accident happened on the A1 motorway near Morges in the canton of Vaud in the early hours of Thursday morning.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>沃州警方表示，一名女性在深夜“绝望地”躺在公路上并且被多辆车辗过。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The police of Vaud canton expressed that a woman has, out of “despair”, laid on the highway and was crushed by multiple vehicles.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">Vaud/waadt police said a woman was "hopelessly" lying on the road in the middle of the night and was run over by several vehicles.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Police in the canton of Vaud said a woman was "desperate" to lie on the road late at night and was run over by multiple vehicles.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>受害者为一名49岁的瑞士女性，其行为明显带有自杀意图。她被多辆车辗过，其中包括一辆货车。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The victim was a 49-year-old Swiss woman. Her behavior was clearly suicidal. She was run over by multiple vehicles, including a truck.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">The victim, a 49-year-old Swiss woman, had apparently committed suicide attempts. She was run over by many cars, including a lorry.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">The victim, a 49-year-old Swiss woman who apparently acted with suicidal intent, was run over by a number of vehicles, including a lorry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>这名女性当场死亡。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The woman died on site.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">The woman died on the spot.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">The woman died at the scene.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>警方透露，多名涉事的驾驶员已接受了调查，但部分驾驶员仍未确认。目前警方正在呼吁他们以及事故目击者前来接受调查。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The police expressed that multiple drivers involved in the incident have agreed to become part of the investigation progress, but a number of drivers has yet to confirm the request. The police encourages them and other witnesses of the accident to be part of the investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">Police have revealed that a number of drivers have been investigated, but some drivers have not yet confirmed. Police are now calling on them and witnesses to the accident to be investigated.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Several of the drivers involved have been investigated, but some have yet to be identified, police said, calling on them and witnesses to the accident to come forward for investigation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>吉勒斯·霍夫施泰特尔律师向《日内瓦论坛报》表示，目前已开始进行刑事调查，这是此类事件的常规流程。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">Lawyer Gilles Hofstetter told Tribune de Genève that criminal investigations have been initiated at this time, a standard procedure for such incidents.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">吉勒斯·霍夫 Steiter, a lawyer for the Geneva Tribune, indicated that criminal investigations had been initiated, a routine process for such incidents.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Lawyers for Gilles Hofstadter told the Geneva Tribune that a criminal investigation has now been opened, a routine process for such incidents.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>但目前尚未知晓是否将有驾驶员面临指控。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">However, he is currently unaware if there are drivers who facing accusations.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">But it is not yet known whether there will be drivers facing charges.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">But it is not yet known whether any drivers will face charges.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>是否有可能避免碰撞？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">Can a collision be avoided?</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">Is it possible to avoid collisions?</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Is it possible to avoid collisions?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>霍夫施泰特尔表示：“这将由检察官来确定”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">Hofstetter said, “This will be determined by the prosecutor.”</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">"This will be determined by the prosecutor," said Hough Steiter.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Mr Hofstetter said: "It will be up to prosecutors to determine."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>根据过去五年另两起类似案件的结果，驾驶员将不承担责任。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">For two similar incidents that have occurred in the last 5 years, the drivers were not held responsible for this.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">According to the results of two similar cases in the past five years, drivers will not be liable.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Based on the results of two other similar cases in the past five years, the driver will not be held responsible.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>据该报报道，这两起案件都是因为有人在深夜走上高速公路所引起的。最终的判决是驾驶员不可能预料到在午夜有行人会穿越高速公路。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">According to this report, both cases were caused by people walking on the highway late at night. The final verdict is that the driver cannot predict that there would be pedestrians walking past the highway in midnight.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">Both cases were caused by the fact that someone had taken to the motorway late at night, according to the report. The final verdict was that the pilot could not have foreseen that pedestrians would cross the highway at midnight.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Both cases were caused by people taking to the motorway late at night, the paper reported, and the final verdict was that the driver could not have anticipated a pedestrian crossing the motorway at midnight.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>去年，一名警官被指控因疏忽而致人死亡，指控的内容是2014年8月，她在帕耶讷附近的A1高速公路上撞击了一名男子并且致其死亡。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">Last year, a police officer was accused of causing death by negligence. The charge was that in August 2014, she hit a man on the A1 expressway near Payerne resulting in his death.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">Last year, a police officer was charged with negligence for death, alleging that in August 2014, she hit a man and died on the A1 highway near payer.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Last year, a police officer was charged with causing death by negligence after she struck and killed a man on the A1 motorway near Payet in August 2014.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>法庭得知，这名22岁的受害者在饮酒后穿过公路。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">The court learned that the 22-year old victim walked across the highway after consuming alcohol.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">The court learned that the 22-year-old victim had been drinking and crossing the road.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">The 22-year-old victim crossed the road after drinking alcohol, the court heard.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>法官在调查后表示，这名女警察当时的驾驶行为完全合法，而这名男子出现在公路上“完全是意外且无法预料的情况”，而且这名女警察事后拨打了急救电话。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">After an investigation, the judge said that the female police officer’s driving behavior was completely legal at the time, and that the appearance of the man on the road was a “totally unexpected and unforeseen circumstance”. What’s more, this female police officer called the emergency services after the incident occurred.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">After the investigation, the judge said that the woman policeman's driving was perfectly legal and that the man appeared on the road "completely unexpected and unpredictable", and the policewoman later dialed the emergency call.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">After the investigation, the judge said the policewoman was driving in a perfectly legal manner at the time, while the man's presence on the road was "completely unexpected and unpredictable" and that the policewoman called emergency services afterwards.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="073_thelocal.38740_en.sl">
    <source>任何可提供有关周四莫尔日附近这起事故的信息的人应拨打021 644 83 46或 021 644 44 44联系警方。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.ht">Anyone who can provide information on the incident which occurred near Morges on Thursday should contact the police at 021 644 83 46 or 021 644 44 44.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.gg">Anyone who can provide information about the accident near the Thursday Moore Day should call 021 644 83 46 or 021 644 44 44 contact police.</translation>
    <translation system="073_thelocal.38740_en.c6">Anyone with information about the accident near Morges on Thursday should contact police on 021 644 83 46 or 021 644 44 44.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
