<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>NASA 气候模型：金星上曾适合人类居住</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">NASA climate model: Venus used to be hospitable to humans</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">NASA climate model: Venus was once fit for human habitation</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">NASA climate model: Venus was once suitable for human habitation</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>根据 NASA 新气候模型的预测，金星上曾适合人类居住。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">According to the predictions made by the latest climate model of NASA, Venus was once suitable for human habitation.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">According to NASA's new climate model, Venus has been fitted for human habitation.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">According to NASA's new climate models, Venus was once habitable.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>NASA 戈达德太空研究所的科学家开发了一个可探索金星过去情况的模型，该模型所使用的工具和算法与气候科学家所使用的十分类似。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">Scientists at NASA’s Goddard Space Flight Center developed a model that could explore past conditions of Venus. The tools and algorithms used by this model are very similar to those used by climate scientists.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">Scientists at NASA's Goddard Space Institute have developed a model to explore the past of Venus, which uses tools and algorithms similar to those used by climate scientists.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">Scientists at NASA's Goddard Institute for Space Studies have developed a model that explores the past of Venus, using tools and algorithms that are very similar to those used by climate scientists.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>该模型用于确定表面高温、无水并且大气层充满二氧化碳的金星是否曾经有类似于地球的环境。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">This model is used to verify whether Venus, with its high surface temperature, lack of water, and an atmosphere filled with carbon dioxide, ever had an earth-like environment.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">The model is used to determine whether Venus, which has high surface temperatures, no water and carbon dioxide in the atmosphere, has ever had a similar Earth-like environment.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">The model was used to determine whether Venus, with its high surface temperature, no water and its atmosphere filled with carbon dioxide, ever had an Earth-like environment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>此前，科学家认为金星自转速度较慢是因为其大气层较厚。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">In the past, scientists thought that the reason for the slower rotation rate of Venus was because it had a thicker atmosphere.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">Earlier, scientists believed that Venus ' rotation was slower because of its thicker atmosphere.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">Previously, scientists thought Venus's slower rotation was due to its thicker atmosphere.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>但最新的模拟表明金星可能曾经有一个较薄、类似于地球的大气层而且当时的自转速度同样较慢。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">However, the latest simulation indicated that Venus may have had a thinner atmosphere similar to that of Earth, and its rotation speed at the time was similarly slower.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">But the latest simulations suggest that Venus may have had a thinner, Earth-like atmosphere and at that time rotated at a slower rate.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">But the latest simulations suggest that Venus may have had a thinner, Earth-like atmosphere and was spinning just as slowly.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>该模型还能显示金星早期的地形。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">This model can even display the landforms of early Venus.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">The model also shows the early terrain of Venus.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">The model also shows the early topography of Venus.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>金星的干燥地区可能比地球多，但曾经有足够的水和地理变化来孕育生命并且防止快速蒸发。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">There may be more dry areas on Venus than on Earth, but it used to have enough water and geographic changes to nurture life as well as to prevent rapid evaporation.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">Venus may have more dry areas than Earth, but there has been enough water and geographical changes to nurture life and prevent rapid evaporation.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">Venus may have more dry areas than Earth, but there was enough water and geographic change to breed life and prevent rapid evaporation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>早期，照射在金星上的阳光亮度比地球暗了30%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">Earlier, the sun was 30% brighter on the surface of Earth than on Venus.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">In the early days, the sun shone on Venus 30% brighter than the Earth.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">In the early days, the light shining on Venus was 30 percent darker than on Earth.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>戈达德太空研究所科学家安东尼·德尔·杰尼奥在新闻发布会上解释说：“在戈达德太空研究所的模型模拟中，金星缓慢的自转使其一侧的白天时间长达近两个月。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">Anthony Del Genio, a scientist in the Goddard Institute for Space Studies explained in a press conference: “In the model simulation used by Goddard Institute for Space Studies, the slow rotation of Venus meant that one side of the planet has a day length of as long as 2 months.”</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">"The slow rotation of Venus at the Goddard Space Institute has made the day nearly two months on one side," 安东尼·德尔·杰尼奥, a scientist at the Goddard Space Institute, explained at a news conference. ”</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">"In the model simulations at the Goddard Institute for Space Research, Venus' slow rotation makes the day on its side nearly two months long," Anthony Del Genio, a scientist at the Goddard Institute for Space Studies, explained in a news release.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>这使表面变暖并且产生了能够形成厚云层的雨水，厚云层就像是一把伞一样为地面阻挡了大部分太阳的热量。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">This makes the surface warm and produces rain that can form thick clouds, which are like an umbrella that blocks most of the heat from the sun.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">This warms the surface and produces rain that can form thick clouds, which are like an umbrella that blocks most of the sun's heat.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">This warms the surface and produces rain that forms thick clouds that act like an umbrella to block most of the sun's heat from the ground.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>模拟的结果是金星的平均气候温度实际上比现在的地球还低了几度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">The results of the simulation show that the average climatic temperature of Venus was actually several degrees lower than that of modern-day Earth.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">The result of the simulation is that the average weather temperature of Venus is actually a few degrees lower than the current Earth.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">The result of the simulation is that Venus' average climate temperature is actually several degrees lower than Earth's today.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>该模型所模拟的金星演化与之前行星科学家推测的相近。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">The evolution of Venus as simulated by this model was similar to earlier estimates made by planetary scientists.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">The model simulates the evolution of Venus similar to that previously speculated by planetary scientists.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">The model simulates the evolution of Venus similar to that previously predicted by planetary scientists.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>尽管金星上可能曾经存在生命，但在几十亿年的过程中，金星暴露在过高的温度与紫外线下。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">Although life could have existed on Venus, the planet has been exposed to excessively high temperatures and ultra-violet rays over the course of billions of years.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">Although there may have been life on Venus, Venus has been exposed to high temperatures and ultraviolet rays in the course of billions of years.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">Although life may have existed on Venus, it was exposed to excessive temperatures and ultraviolet light over the course of billions of years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>星球上的海洋蒸发，水蒸汽也被紫外线烧尽。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">The ocean on the planet evaporated, and the water vapor was also burnt away by UV radiation.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">The oceans on the planet evaporate and the water vapor is burned out by ultraviolet rays.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">The planet's oceans evaporate, and water vapour is burned out by ultraviolet light.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>随着氢的逃逸，所留下的只有较厚的二氧化碳大气层和致命的温室气体效应，从而形成了我们今天所知道的金星。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">As hydrogen escapes, what remains are the thicker CO2 atmosphere and lethal greenhouse gas effect, forming what we now know as Venus.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">As hydrogen escapes, it leaves only a thicker carbon dioxide atmosphere and a lethal greenhouse gas effect, which forms what we know today about Venus.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">With the escape of hydrogen, all that is left is a thicker atmosphere of carbon dioxide and a deadly greenhouse gas effect, creating Venus as we know it today.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="169_upi.103566_en.sl">
    <source>研究人员在《地球物理研究通讯》期刊中发表了新的金星气候模型的模拟结果。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.ht">Researchers published new results of Venus weather simulation models on the journal of Geophysical Research Letters</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.gg">The researchers published the results of the new Venus Climate model in the journal Geophysical Research Newsletter.</translation>
    <translation system="169_upi.103566_en.c6">The researchers published the results of a new Venus climate model in the journal Geophysical Research Letters.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
