<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.sl">
    <source>经查，2016年7月27日，原赣州市定南县委书记陈阳霞到省纪委报到上班，担任党风政风监督室主任（副厅长级，试用期一年）。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.ht">Upon investigation, the former Ganzhou City Dingnan County Party Committee Secretary Chen Yangxia reported for work at the Provincial Commission for Discipline Inspection on July 27, 2016, assuming the role of director of the Office for Supervising Party and Political Conduct (deputy director-general grade with a one-year probation period).</translation>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.gg">After investigation, July 27, 2016, the original Ganzhou Dingnan County Secretary Chenyangxia to the Provincial Discipline inspection report to work, as party conduct political wind Supervision room director (Deputy Director class, probation one year).</translation>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.c6">After investigation, on July 27, 2016, Chen Yangxia, former secretary of the Dingnan County CPC Committee of Ganzhou City, reported to the Provincial Discipline Inspection Commission to work as director of the party style and government style supervision room (deputy director level, one year's probation period).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.sl">
    <source>当晚饮用的红酒由黎友才个人提供，其他费用由刘某某个人承担。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.ht">The wine for the dinner was provided by Li Youtai, other cost was taken by Liu.</translation>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.gg">That night the red wine is provided by Li YOUCAI individuals and other expenses are borne by Liu.</translation>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.c6">The red wine consumed that night was provided by Li Youcai personally, and the other expenses were borne by Liu.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.sl">
    <source>江西省纪委通报称，陈阳霞、程子亮等人在私人会所组织和接受吃请，违反了中央八项规定精神，触犯了党的纪律。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.ht">The Commission for Discipline Inspection of Jiangxi Province reported that Chen Yangxia, Cheng Ziliang and others organized and accepted invitations to dinner (extended as a bribe) at private clubs, in breach of the spirit of the CPC Central Committee's Eight Provisions, and violated Party discipline.</translation>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.gg">Jiangxi Province, the Ministry of Discipline reported that Chenyangxia, Cheng and other people in private clubs organized and accepted invitation, violated the central eight provisions of the spirit, violated the party's discipline.</translation>
    <translation system="008_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnpy9455610_zh.c6">The Jiangxi Provincial Commission for Discipline Inspection reported that Chen Yangxia and Cheng Ziliang, among others, had violated the spirit of the eight central regulations and violated party discipline by organizing and accepting invitations to dinner in private clubs.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
