<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刘赐贵赴三亚调研“双修、双城”要求提升城市建管水平</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">Liu Cigui went to Sanya to investigate and study “dual remediation and dual urban construction” requirements to improve city construction management standards</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">Liu Yigui to Sanya research "double repair, Twin Cities" request to improve the urban construction management level</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">Liu Cigui went to Sanya to research "Shuangxiu, Shuangcheng" to improve the level of urban construction and management</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>12日上午，刘赐贵主持召开座谈会，听取了三亚市“双修”“双城”试点工作推进情况的汇报及各有关部门的意见建议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">In the morning of the 12th, Liu Cigui chaired a conference and listened to reports on the implementation “dual remediation” and “dual construction” pilot programs as well as opinions and recommendations provided by various departments.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">12th morning, Liu Yigui presided over the symposium, heard the Sanya "double Repair" "Twin Cities" pilot work to promote the situation and the relevant departments of the suggestions.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">On the morning of December 12, Liu Cigui presided over a symposium and listened to a report on the progress of the pilot project of "Shuangxiu" and "Shuangcheng" in Sanya City and the opinions and suggestions of various departments concerned.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刘赐贵对试点工作中取得的阶段性成果和创造出的好经验、好做法给予充分肯定。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">Liu Cigui fully acknowledged the results and positive experiences and effective methods achieved for the step-by-step demonstration project.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">Liu Yigui has given full affirmation to the phased results achieved in the pilot work and to the good experiences and good practices created.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">Liu gave full recognition to the stage results achieved and the good experience and good practices created in the pilot work.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刘赐贵强调，三亚要紧紧抓住历史发展机遇，以“双修”“双城”试点工作为重要抓手，在全省经济社会发展中充分发挥好示范带动的龙头作用。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">Liu Cigui highlighted that Sanya must firmly leverage historical development opportunities, and use the pilot programs of “ecological restoration and urban repair” and “sponge city and integrated pipeline corridor development city” as key bases so as to give full play to its demonstration leadership role in the Province’s economic and social development.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">Liu Yigui stressed that Sanya should seize the opportunity of historical development, take "double repair" and "Twin Cities" pilot work as an important hand, and give full play to the leading role of demonstration in the economic and social development of the province.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">Liu stressed that Sanya should firmly seize the opportunity of historical development, take the pilot project of "double repair" and "twin cities" as an important task, and give full play to the leading role of good demonstration in the province's economic and social development.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>要在提升国际旅游岛国际化水平中发挥好带头作用，从点滴细节入手，丰富国际元素、打造国际精品。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">To improve the globalization standards for the International Travelling Island to better serve as a benchmark company, efforts shall include focusing on the details, enriching global elements, and building fine global brands.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">To promote international tourism island to play a good role in the internationalization, from the details, rich international elements, to create international products.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">It is necessary to play a good leading role in enhancing the internationalization level of the international tourist islands, starting with every little detail, enriching the international elements and creating international boutiques.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>要在城乡一体化和全域旅游中发挥好带头作用，加快特色风情小镇建设，将旅游元素融入每个项目，把三亚的每个乡村、城镇都建设成旅游景区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">In order to successfully play a leadership role in urban-rural integration and regional tourism, the building of towns with unique styles should be accelerated, tourism elements should be integrated in every project, and tourist attractions should be built in every village and town.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">To play a leading role in urban-rural integration and tourism in the whole region, speed up the construction of characteristic and amorous town, integrate the elements of tourism into each project, and build every village and town in Sanya into a tourist area.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">We should play a good leading role in the integration of urban and rural areas and global tourism, speed up the construction of towns with distinctive customs, integrate tourism elements into each project, and build every village and town in Sanya into a tourist attraction.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>要在“服务社会投资百日大行动”中发挥好带头作用，推动一批重大项目和园区建设，确保高质量项目的落地，把大行动的各项要求落实好。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">To ensure that the “100-day Mega Campaign for Servicing Social Investments” properly serves its pilot effect, a number of major projects and parks and proper implementation of high quality undertakings must be implemented. Every project requirement must be fulfilled accordingly.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">We should play a leading role in "service Social investment Hundred Days", promote a number of major projects and park construction, ensure the landing of high-quality projects, the implementation of the requirements of the major action.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">It is necessary to play a good leading role in the "100-day action for social investment in services," promote the construction of a number of major projects and parks, ensure the landing of high-quality projects, and implement the requirements of the major action.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.sl">
    <source>省委常委、三亚市委书记张琦，副省长王路，省政府秘书长陆志远参加调研座谈。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.ht">Zhang Qi, provincial party committee member and party committee secretary of Sanya City, Wang Lu, the vice provincial governor, and Lu Zhiyuan, secretary general of the provincial government, participated in this investigative conference.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.gg">Party committee, Sanya Municipal Committee secretary Zhang, vice Governor Wang, provincial government Secretary-General Lu Zhiyuan participated in the research discussion.</translation>
    <translation system="072_ifeng0812.news.49768304_0_zh.c6">Provincial Party Committee Standing Committee, Sanya Municipal Party Secretary Zhang Qi, Vice Governor Wang Lu, Secretary General of the provincial government Lu Zhiyuan to participate in the investigation and discussion.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
