<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>俄罗斯与土耳其：“格格不入联盟”？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Russia and Turkey - “An alliance of misfits?”</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Russia and Turkey: "Incompatible alliances"?</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Russia and Turkey: "Out of the Union"?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>一个手势结束一场危机。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">A hand gesture ended this crisis.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">A gesture to end a crisis.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">A gesture to end a crisis.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>俄罗斯与土耳其领导人周二进行会见，双方握手并宣布正式结束长达八个月的口水战与经济制裁。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">The leaders of Russia and Turkey met on Tuesday. The two parties shook hands, and announced that the eight-month long war of words and economic sanctions will officially cease.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Russian and Turkish leaders met in Tuesday, shaking hands and announcing a formal end to eight months of fighting and economic sanctions.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Russia and Turkey's leaders met on Tuesday, shaking hands and announcing an official end to an eight-month war of words and economic sanctions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>然而，当弗拉基米尔·普京在一座圣彼德斯堡宫殿金碧辉煌的大厅中迎接土耳其总统时，我有种强烈的感觉：此次和解是安卡拉最希望看到的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">However, when Vladimir Putin received the President of Turkey at the gilded palace halls of St. Petersburg, I had a strong feeling that this was the reconciliation Ankara had most hoped to see.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">However, when Vladimir Putin greeted the Turkish president in a magnificent hall in the palace of St. Petersburg, I had a strong feeling that the settlement was what Ankara would most like to see.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">However, when Vladimir Putin greeted the Turkish president in the glittering halls of a St. Petersburg palace, I had a strong feeling that the rapprochement was what Ankara wanted most.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>是的，双方确实握手了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Yes, both parties shook hands.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Yes, the two sides did shake hands.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Yes, the two sides did shake hands.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>然而，即使是按照普京先生一向内敛的标准来看，普京也只是浅浅微笑，几乎未流露出热情之意。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">However, Putin only gave a gentle smile. This seems to indicate little passion, even according to Putin’s subsumed standards.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">However, even as Mr Putin's usual standard of restraint, Putin is only a shallow smile, almost no enthusiasm.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Yet, even by Mr Putin's normally reserved standards, his smile is shallow and almost unenthusiastic.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>据报道，雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安则五次提到“好朋友”普京。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">According to the report, Recep Tayyip Erdoğan mentioned his “good friend” Putin five times.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">According to reports, Recep five times mentioned "good friend" Putin.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Recep Tayyip Erdogan, for his part, reportedly mentioned "good friend" Putin five times.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>我记不清了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">I don't remember it well.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">I can't remember.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">I can't remember.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>同时，他承诺与俄罗斯的关系将回归至危机发生前的水平，甚至达到更高水平。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">He also promised that relations with Russia will return to the level prior to the crisis, or even better.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">At the same time, he promised that relations with Russia would return to pre-crisis levels, even to a higher level.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">At the same time, he promised that relations with Russia would return to pre-crisis levels, or even higher.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>次日，此间一家报纸写到，埃尔多安先生则表现的好像什么都没发生一样。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">On the following day, a newspaper wrote that Erdoğan behaved as though nothing has happened.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">The next day, a newspaper here wrote that Mr Erdogan acted as if nothing had happened.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">The following day, a newspaper here wrote that Mr. Erdogan acted as if nothing had happened.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>但是，我认为他的热情暗示了某些相反的东西。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">I believe however, that his enthusiasm implied something quite the opposite.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">But I think his enthusiasm hints at something opposite.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">But, I think his enthusiasm suggests something to the contrary.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>然而，普京先生持续冷淡的态度说明他什么都没有忘记。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">However, Putin remained cold and said that he did not forget anything.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">However, Mr Putin's persistent indifference suggests that he has not forgotten anything.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Mr. Putin's continued frosty attitude, however, suggests that he has not forgotten anything.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>实际上，他在开场白中提到的第一件事便是此次危机的原因：土耳其于叙利亚边境击落一架俄罗斯战机。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">In fact, the first thing he mentioned in his opening remarks was the reason for the current crisis: Turkey shot down a Russian attack aircraft at the Syrian border.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">In fact, the first thing he mentioned in his opening remarks was the cause of the crisis: Turkey shot down a Russian fighter plane on the Syrian border.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Indeed, the first thing he mentioned in his opening remarks was the cause of the crisis: Turkey shot down a Russian warplane on the Syrian border.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>莫斯科当时的反应很激烈。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Moscow reacted intensely at the time.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Moscow reacted violently.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Moscow's reaction at the time was fierce.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>普京先生针对该事件进行猛烈抨击，指责安卡拉在背后暗算莫斯科。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Mr Putin took aim at this issue, and accused Ankara of stabbing Moscow in the back.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Mr Putin lashed out at the incident, accusing Ankara of plotting against Moscow behind the scenes.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Mr. Putin lashed out at the incident, accusing Ankara of plotting against Moscow behind his back.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>来自所谓朋友的攻击更让人难以接受。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">An attack by someone who is supposedly a friend is hard to stomach.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Attacks from so-called friends are more difficult to accept.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Attacks from so-called friends are more difficult to accept.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>双方很难，甚至不可能重新建立真正的信任。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">It is difficult, perhaps even impossible, for both parties to establish true trust.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">It is difficult, or impossible, to re-establish true trust.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">It is difficult, if not impossible, for the two sides to re-establish real trust.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>自11月份开始，俄罗斯民意也有所扭转。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Russian public opinion has started to change since November.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Russian public opinion has also been reversed since November.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Russian public opinion has also been turned around since November.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>数月来，被政府控制的媒体对安卡拉进行了令人震惊的全力进攻。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">For months, the government controlled media launched a shocking all-out attack on Ankara.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">For months, the government-controlled media have made a shocking and all-out attack on Ankara.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">For months, the government-controlled media have carried out a shocking full-throated attack on Ankara.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>突然之间，土耳其人似乎要为所有事情负责。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Suddenly, the Turks seemed to want to assume responsibility for everything.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Suddenly, the Turks seemed to be responsible for everything.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Suddenly, the Turks seem to be responsible for everything.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>其中，最严重的是来自高级官员的指责：埃尔多安先生的家人从所谓伊斯兰国控制的叙利亚地区的非法石油交易中获利。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">In particular, the most severe criticisms came from senior White House officials: Mr Erdoğan’s family members received gains from illegal oil trading with regions in Syria controlled by the so-called Islamic State.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Among the most serious are accusations from senior officials: Mr Erdogan's family profited from the illegal oil deals in the so-called Islamic State-controlled Syrian region.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">The most serious of these were accusations from senior officials: Mr. Erdogan's family profited from illegal oil deals in areas of Syria controlled by the so-called Islamic State.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>他已断然否认该种说法。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">He has already denied that statement.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">He has flatly denied such a statement.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">He has categorically denied the claim.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>然而，圣彼德斯堡传来的消息显示，是时候该向前看了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">However, news from St Petersburg revealed that it was time to move on.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">However, the news from Fort Petersburg shows that it is time to look ahead.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">However, news from St Petersburg suggests it is time to move on.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>毕竟此次会面的前提是普京收到土耳其总统埃尔多安的道歉。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">The pretext of this meeting is that Putin has received an apology from the President of Turkey Erdoğan.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">After all, the meeting was premised on Mr. Putin's apology from Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">After all, the meeting presupposed that Putin received an apology from Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>俄罗斯可以宣布胜利了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Russia can declare victory.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Russia can declare victory.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Russia could declare victory.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>对于安卡拉来说，休战的好处显而易见。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">For Ankara, the benefits of a truce were crystal clear.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">For Ankara, the benefits of a truce are obvious.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">For Ankara, the benefits of the truce are obvious.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>首先，埃尔多安在上个月政变失败后险些被赶下台，因此他需要所有朋友的支持。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">First, Erdoğan was nearly deposed after the coup failed last month. Therefore, he needed support from all his friends.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">First, Mr Erdogan narrowly missed his ouster after the coup failed last month, so he needs the support of all his friends.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">First, Erdogan was nearly ousted after last month's failed coup, so he needs the support of all his friends.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>不断的恐怖袭击显然已对他造成很大打击。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Ongoing terrorist attacks have clearly shocked him.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">The ongoing terrorist attacks have obviously hit him hard.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">The incessant terrorist attacks have clearly hit him hard.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>同时也有经济动机。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Economic incentives exist as well.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">There are also economic motives.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">There is also a financial incentive.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>俄罗斯制裁对土耳其打击很大，尤其是禁止每年可输送几百万俄罗斯游客至土耳其海岸的包机服务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Russia’s sanctions against Turkey generated significant impacts, and include banning of charter flights that sends millions of Russian tourists to the shores of Turkey.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Russia has been hit hard by sanctions against Turkey, in particular by banning charter services that can send millions of of Russian tourists to the Turkish coast every year.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Russian sanctions have hit Turkey hard, especially by banning charter flights that can transport millions of Russian tourists to Turkey's shores each year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>该数字已大幅下滑近90%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">This figure has drastically decreased by nearly 90%.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">The figure has fallen by nearly 90%.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">That number has plummeted by nearly 90 per cent.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>随着航班恢复，俄罗斯的旅行社与包机公司必将松一口气。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">With resumption of flights, Russia’s travel agencies and charter companies breathed a sign of relief.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">As the flight resumes, Russian travel agencies and charter companies will be relieved.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Travel agencies and charter companies in Russia are bound to breathe a sigh of relief as flights resume.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>他们将迎来季末地中海旅游潮。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">They will be welcoming the Mediterranean tourism wave at the end of the season.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">They will usher in the Mediterranean tourist season at the quarter.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">They will see a wave of Mediterranean tourism at the end of the season.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="34" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>国家电视台甚至在本周预测，一旦土耳其农产品进口重新放开，水果及蔬菜的价格将下降。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">The national television channel even predicted that once imports of Turkish farm products are once again allowed through the borders, the prices of fruits and vegetables will drop.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">State television even predicted this week that the price of fruits and vegetables would fall once Turkey's agricultural imports were reopened.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">State television even predicted this week that the price of fruits and vegetables would fall once Turkey's agricultural imports were liberalized again.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="35" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>莫斯科报纸 Vedemosti 的一篇报道称：“游客去了，番茄回来了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">A report in Russian newspaper Vedemosti stated, “Tourists that way, tomatoes back here.”</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">A report in Vedemosti, a Moscow newspaper, said: "The tourists are gone and the tomatoes are back." ”</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">"The tourists go and the tomatoes come back," said a report in the Moscow newspaper Vedemosti.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="36" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>对于莫斯科来说，此次访问也具有额外的政治价值。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">To Moscow, this visit also provides added political value.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">For Moscow, the visit also has added political value.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">The visit also has additional political value for Moscow.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="37" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>安卡拉对于西方世界对接管意图的微弱反应感到愤怒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Ankara was furious with the West’s weak response to the intentions concerning the takeover.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Ankara was outraged by the West's faint reaction to takeover intentions.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Ankara is furious at the Western world's feeble response to the takeover's intentions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="38" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>此外，安卡拉对于加入欧盟谈判的缓慢进展及普京的插手长期感到不满，普京热衷于利用政治寒意以及削弱土耳其与西方世界的关系。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">In addition, Ankara had, for some time, been unhappy with the slow progress of the EU accession negotiations and Putin’s meddling. Putin was keen on using political chill and weakening the relationship between Turkey and the Western world.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">In addition, Ankara is keen to take advantage of the political chill and weaken Turkey's relations with the West in a long period of frustration over the slow progress of joining the EU negotiations and Mr Putin's involvement.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Moreover, Ankara has long resented the slow pace of EU accession negotiations and the meddling of Vladimir Putin, who is keen to exploit political chill and weaken Turkey ’ s relations with the Western world.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="39" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>由于在政变失败后拥护当选当局，俄罗斯领导人必将获得安卡拉的加分。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">For supporting the current government after the failure of the coup, the Russian leader will definitely get himself on the positive side of Ankara.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">With the election of the elected authorities after the failure of the coup, Russia's leaders will be given Ankara's bonus points.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">The Russian leader is bound to get extra points from Ankara for championing the elected authorities after the failed coup.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="40" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>注意，这对于一直对政权更迭怀抱根深蒂固恐惧的莫斯科来说是一种馈赠。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Note that this was gift to Moscow which has always had a deep-rooted fear for regime change.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Note that this is a gift to Moscow, which has been deeply rooted in the fear of regime change.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Note that this is a gift for Moscow, which has always harboured a deep-seated fear of regime change.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="41" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>因此，在这个金碧辉煌的海边宫殿所举行的会面使俄罗斯与土耳其两个被西方世界拒绝与虐待的国家结成盟友，一位分析师将其描述为“格格不入联盟”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Hence, during the meeting held at this luxurious seaside palace, Russia and Turkey, two countries that had been rejected and abused by the western world, became allies. An analyst described this as an “alliance of misfits”.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Thus, the meeting in this magnificent seaside palace has made Russia and Turkey an ally of two countries rejected and abused by the West, an analyst who described it as "incompatible alliances".</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">So the meeting at the glittering seaside palace has forged an alliance between Russia and Turkey, two countries rejected and abused by the Western world, which one analyst described as an "out of place alliance."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="42" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>然而，尽管公开和解，但双方仍存在重大分歧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Serious disagreement still existed between both parties in spite of a public settlement.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">However, despite public reconciliation, there are still significant differences between the two sides.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">However, despite the public rapprochement, significant differences remain between the two sides.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="43" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>叙利亚是关键因素之一。莫斯科近日在叙利亚扮演和事佬的角色，而俄罗斯与土耳其却支持相反派别。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Syria is a key factor. Moscow has recently played the role of a mediator in Syria. However, Russia and Turkey supported opposing factions.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Syria is one of the key factors. Moscow recently played the role of a peacemaker in Syria, while Russia and Turkey supported the opposing factions.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">One of the key factors is Syria, where Moscow has been playing the peacemaker in recent days, while Russia and Turkey have backed opposing factions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="44" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>可以预见到的是，在经过近三个小时的初步谈话后，两位总统在发布会上表示，尚未谈及那个话题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">It is predictable that after a 3-hour preliminary talk, both presidents would express at the press conference that they have yet to broach the topic.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">Predictably, after nearly three hours of preliminary talks, the two presidents said at the press conference that they had not yet talked about the topic.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">Predictably, after nearly three hours of preliminary talks, the two presidents said at the launch that the topic had not yet been addressed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="45" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>土耳其总统刻意回避关于双方分歧的问题，而普京则予以强调。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">The President of Turkey deliberately avoided questions regarding disagreements between both parties, while Putin emphasized them.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">The Turkish president deliberately sidestepped the issue of disagreement between the two sides, while Putin stressed it.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">The Turkish president has deliberately avoided questions about the differences between the two sides, while Putin has emphasized them.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="46" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>双方就如何在叙利亚问题上求同存异未达成明确共识。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Both parties failed to reach a clear consensus on seeking common ground while reserving differences on the issue of Syria.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">The two sides have not reached a clear consensus on how to disagree on Syria.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">There is no clear consensus between the two sides on how to seek common ground on the Syrian issue.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="47" doc-id="123_bbc.242334_en.sl">
    <source>在北大西洋公约组织成员国土耳其击落俄战机所带来的数月公开敌对及引发大型灾难的可能下，两国领导人再次重启对话肯定是件好事。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.ht">Given months of open hostility and the possibility of triggering a large-scale disaster brought about by the shooting down of a Russian fighter jet by NATO member Turkey, reinitiating dialogue between the leaders of the two countries is definitely a good thing.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.gg">The resumption of dialogue between the two leaders is certainly a good thing, with the possibility of months of open hostility and a major catastrophe caused by the shooting down of Russian warplanes by Turkey, a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization.</translation>
    <translation system="123_bbc.242334_en.c6">With months of open hostility and the possibility of a major catastrophe following the downing of a Russian warplane by Turkey, a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization, it is surely good for the leaders of the two countries to resume talks once again.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
