<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据外媒报道，27岁的韩国射箭女选手张慧珍在女子射箭个人赛中获得金牌，继团体赛后再获奥运会金牌，成为双冠王。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">Foreign media reported that 27-year-old archer Chang Hye-jin won the gold medal for the women’s individual archery event after clinching a gold medal in the team event. She is now a double champion.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">According to foreign media reports, the 27-year-old Korean archery female contestant Zhang Huijin in the women's archery personal competition won the gold medal, after the team won the Olympic gold medal, become double Crown king.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Zhang Huizhen, a 27-year-old female archer from South Korea, won a gold medal in the women's individual archery event, winning the Olympic gold medal after the team event and becoming a double champion, foreign media reported.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张慧珍被认为是一名大器晚成的选手，她曾遗憾未获上届伦敦奥运会的入场券，如今却骄傲地站在了里约奥运的最高领奖台上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">Zhang Huizhen is regarded as an athlete who achieved her glories late in her career. She was once unable to enter the London Olympics, but finally made it to the prestigious podium for the Rio Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Zhang Huijin is considered a bloomer player who regrets not getting tickets to the last London Olympics but is proudly standing on the top podium of the Rio Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Regarded as a late contender, Zhang Huizhen, who regretted not getting a ticket to the last London Olympics, is now proudly standing on the top podium of the Rio Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张惠珍在在巴西里约桑巴大道体育馆举行的女子射箭个人赛决赛中以总比分6-2击败德国的丽萨·翁鲁，获得了金牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">In the women’s archery singles held at the Rio’s Samba Stadium in Brazil, Zhang Huizhen defeated Lisa Unruh from Germany with a total score of 6-2.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Zhang Huijin won the gold medal in the women's archery personal finals in the Brazilian Rio Samba Avenue Stadium, with a total score of 6-2 beats Germany's 丽萨·翁鲁.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Zhang Huizhen won the gold medal by beating Germany's Lisa Onlu 6-2 in the final of the women's archery individual event at the Samba Boulevard Stadium in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她在小学四年级时才第一次射箭，直到27岁的2014年才在世界杯赛上首次获得个人赛金牌，是一位成名较晚的选手。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">An athlete who attained fame later than most others, she shot her first arrow only when she was in Primary 4, and only received her first individual gold medal at the world cup tournament in 2014 when she was 27 years old.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">She first shot archery in grade four, until the 27-year-old 2014 years in the World Cup for the first time to win a personal gold medal, is a late player.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">She did not shoot her first arrow until she was in fourth grade in primary school, and it was only in 2014, at the age of 27, that she won her first individual gold medal at the World Cup, a late starter.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张惠珍回忆道，“上中学以前没有什么水平，以至于无法参加全国的比赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">Chang Hye-jin reminisced: “There was little quality before junior high school, and provided no opportunities in joining national competitions.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Zhang Huijin recalls, "There was no level in high school before, so I couldn't compete in the country."</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">"There was no level before middle school, so that you couldn't compete in the national competition," Zhang recalled.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张惠珍在四年前的伦敦奥运会选手选拔赛上仅获第四名，憾失奥运入场券，只能坐视同事兼好友奇甫倍夺两枚金牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">Chang Hye-jin has only obtained the 4th place during the qualifiers for the London Olympics, and missed her chance to attend the event. She could only sit by and watch her colleague and friend Ki Bo-Bae winning 2 gold medals.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Zhang Huijin, who won only fourth place in the London Olympic Games four years ago, regrets losing Olympic tickets and just sits down to win two gold medals from colleagues and friends.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Zhang Huizhen, who finished fourth in the London Olympic trials four years ago, had to sit back and watch her colleague and friend Chi-fu win two gold medals.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>张惠珍在女子射箭个人赛颁奖仪式结束后谈了自己的夺金感言，“直至最后都是尽可能地一发一发地射箭，可能是这带来了好结果，心满意足。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">After the medal ceremony for the women’s individual archery event, Chang Hye-jin expressed her feelings about winning the gold medal, “Up to the very last, I did my best at every arrow I shot. Perhaps this led to good results. I’m very happy.”</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Zhang Huijin in the women's archery individual contest after the ceremony to talk about their own gold speech, "until the end is as long as possible to shoot a shot, may be this brings good results, satisfied."</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Zhang Huizhen talked about her comments on winning gold at the end of the awards ceremony of the Women's Archery Individual Competition. "Up to the end, she shot as many shots as she could, which may have brought good results and contentment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>28岁的韩国射箭“一姐”、伦敦奥运会射箭个人赛金牌获得者奇甫倍获得了铜牌。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">The Bronze Medal was won by the 28-year-old Bo-bae, known as No. 1 Archer Lady in South Korea and the gold medal winner of archery in the London Olympic Games.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">The 28-year-old South Korean archery "one sister", the London Olympic archery individual gold medalist won the bronze medal.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Kifubi, a 28-year-old South Korean archer and gold medalist in the individual archery competition at the London Olympics, won the bronze medal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>奇甫倍在半决赛中输给张惠珍，与墨西哥选手亚力杭德拉·瓦伦西亚展开铜牌争夺。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">Ki Bo-Bae lost to Chang Hye-jin in the semi-finals, and was then matched up against the Mexican athlete Alejandra Valencia.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">He lost in the semi-final to Zhang Huijin, with the Mexican player Arnie Alejandro 拉·瓦伦西亚 to start the bronze medal competition.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Chippee lost to Zhang Huizhen in the semifinals to compete for the bronze medal with Mexico's Alejandra Valencia.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>奇甫倍在确保铜牌后泪洒赛场，其间默默承受的冲金负担可想而知。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">Ki Bo-bae wept after it was confirmed that she had won the bronze medal. One could only imagine the burden of having to win a gold medal that she had to suffer in silence in the interim.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Qi Fu Times to ensure that the bronze after the tears on the field, in the meantime, silently bear the burden of the gold is conceivable.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">Chi-fu times in ensuring that the bronze medal after the tears sprinkled the arena, in the meantime, silently bear the burden of gold can be imagined.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>首先是教练组在不断研究中积累了丰富经验，其次是科学的训练方式，这些都是需要长期积累的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">The training team accumulated plenty of experience during continuous research. Scientific training method comes in second. All these can only be acquired through many years of learning.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">First of all, the coaching team has accumulated rich experience in continuous research, followed by scientific training methods, which need long-term accumulation.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">The first is that the coaching staff has accumulated rich experience in constant research, followed by scientific training methods, which need to be accumulated over a long period of time.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.sl">
    <source>射箭队以军训、夜间穿越墓地等方法帮助队员集中注意力并保持平常心。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.ht">The archery team employed military training, crossing cemeteries at night and other methods to help team members focus and concentrate as well as to take things in stride.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.gg">Archery team to the military training, night through the graveyard and other methods to help the team focus and maintain the normal heart.</translation>
    <translation system="140_ifeng0812.news.49765687_0_zh.c6">The archery team helps the players to concentrate and stay calm through military training and through the graveyard at night.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
