<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>莱曼届时将作为德甲亚洲媒体合作伙伴的专家，参加当地各种球迷活动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">Lehmann will serve as a pundit for the Bundesliga’s media partners, and take part in various local fan activities.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">Lehmann will be an expert in the Bundesliga Asian media partners to participate in various local fan activities.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">Lehmann will then take part in a variety of local fan events as an expert on the Bundesliga's Asian media partners.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据介绍，今年秋季，德甲联赛形象大使莱曼和马特乌斯将代表德甲在亚洲和美洲陆续展开传奇之旅，为2016/17赛季德甲的开幕打响前哨。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">According to information, ambassadors Raisman and Matthäus of the German Bundesliga will be initiating their Legends Tour this autumn in Asia and the Americas to prepare fans for the opening ceremony of the 2016/2017 season.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">According to the introduction, this fall, the Bundesliga league image of the Ambassador Lyman and Matt will be on behalf of the Bundesliga in Asia and the Americas to launch a legendary tour, for the 2016/17 season Bundesliga opening outpost.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">In the autumn, German Bundesliga ambassadors Lehmann and Mateus will represent the Bundesliga on a legendary tour of Asia and the Americas, setting the stage for the opening of the Bundesliga for the 2016 / 17 season, according to the report.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>本次活动将横跨两个大洲、覆盖四座顶级城市，他们将在各地和球迷们一起为新赛季预热造势。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">This event will span two continents and cover 4 first-tier cities. They will fan the flames of public attention for the new season at these locations with fellow fans.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">The event, which spans two continents and covers four top cities, will be warmed up for the new season with fans everywhere.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">The event will span two continents and cover four top cities, where they will be working with fans around the world to prepare for the new season.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>德甲联赛被誉为欧洲五大联赛(英超、西甲、意甲、德甲、法甲)之一，是足球王国德国体育界当仁不让的旗舰赛事。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">The German premier league Bundesliga is lauded as one of the top five leagues of Europe (English Premier League, the Primera División of Spain, Serie A of Italy, Bundesliga of Germany, and France Ligue 1 of France), and is therefore one of the most important sporting event for the football kingdom of Germany.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">The Bundesliga league is regarded as one of the top five European leagues (the Premier League, La Liga, Serie A, Bundesliga, French), and is the flagship event of the German sport in the football kingdom.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">The Bundesliga is hailed as one of the top five leagues in Europe (Premier League, La Liga, Serie A, Bundesliga, La Liga) and is the flagship event of the German sports world of the football kingdom.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>作为全球最具实力的联赛之一，德甲仅2014-2015赛季就吸引了约1330万名观众来到球场观战。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">As one of the most influential leagues in the world, the 2014-2015 season of Bundesliga attracted about 13.30 million visitors to watch the football games.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">As one of the world's most powerful leagues, the Bundesliga has attracted about 13.3 million spectators to the stadium in just 2014-2015 seasons.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">One of the world's most powerful leagues, the Bundesliga attracted about 13.3 million spectators to the stadium for the 2014-2015 season alone.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>德甲豪门的代表拜仁慕尼黑、多特蒙德和著名球星托马斯·穆勒、拉姆、格策等在中国可谓家喻户晓。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">German premier league teams include Bayern Munich and Dorftmund, as well as famous football stars such as Thomas Müller, Philipp Lahm, and Mario Götze who are extremely well-known in China.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">The Bundesliga giants representing Bayern Munich, Dortmund and famous star Thomas, Ram, and GE are widely known in China.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">Representatives of the Bundesliga giants Bayern Munich, Borussia Dortmund and famous stars Thomas Müller, the Rams, Götze and so on are household names in China.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.sl">
    <source>配合此前德甲已上线的微博、优酷和微信中文平台，德甲方面寄望为中国球迷提供更广泛和及时便捷的渠道，获取该联赛的最新消息。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.ht">Bundesliga places great hopes to provide Chinese football fans with more accessible and prompt channels for acquiring the latest information of the league, and will be using Weibo, Youku, and WeChat Chinese language platforms that the league has previously established.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.gg">With the previous Bundesliga on-line microblogging, Youku and micro-letter Chinese platform, the Bundesliga hopes to provide Chinese fans with a broader and more timely and convenient channels to obtain the latest league news.</translation>
    <translation system="066_ifeng0812.news.49768452_0_zh.c6">In line with the Bundesliga's previous Weibo, Youku and WeChat Chinese platforms, the Bundesliga side is looking to provide Chinese fans with wider and timely and convenient access to the latest news from the league.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
