<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>社区法律中心每年将16万人拒之门外</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">Community Legal Centres turn away 160,000 people each year</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">Community Law Center shuts 160,000 people out every year</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">Community legal centres shut out 160,000 people a year</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>每年有超过16万最弱势的群体被社区法律中心拒之门外。这项服务的资金本已捉襟见肘，而现在又要面对进一步的资金削减。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">Every year, over 160,000 of the most underprivileged groups have been denied access to the community legal center. This service is already facing the issue of inadequate funds. Now they must face an additional budget slash.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">Every year more than 160,000 of the most vulnerable groups are shut out of Community law centres. The service is already overstretched and now faces further capital cuts.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">More than 160,000 of the most vulnerable people are turned away from community legal centres each year and the service is already stretched to the limit and now faces further funding cuts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>在昆士兰，每五个人中有三个人在寻求免费法律咨询和代理服务时被拒，其中大部分是老年人、移民、弱势的工人、暴力事件的受害人以及没有资源对抗不公正驱逐的人等。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">In Queensland, three in every five persons have been rejected when seeking free legal advice and representation services. Most of these were the elderly, migrants, vulnerable workers, victims of abuse, as well as people without resources opposing unfair expulsion.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">In Queensland, three out of every five persons were rejected in the search for free legal advice and agency services, most of them elderly, migrants, vulnerable workers, victims of violence and those who did not have the resources to fight unjust evictions.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">In Queensland, three out of five people are denied access to free legal advice and representation, mostly elderly people, migrants, vulnerable workers, victims of violence and those who do not have the resources to fight unfair evictions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>社区法律服务的资金缺乏早已超过了限值，现在又要面临进一步的资金削减。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">The lack of funding for community legal services has long been stretched beyond limit. Now the fund must face additional budget slashes.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">The lack of funding for community legal Services has already exceeded the limit and now faces further capital cuts.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">The lack of funding for community legal services has long exceeded the limit and now faces further funding cuts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>自明年六月起，联邦政府为这些法律中心提供的资金将再减少30%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">From June next year, the federal government will reduce funds provided to these legal centers by another 30%.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">The federal government's funding for these legal centres will be reduced by another 30% per year since June.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">Federal funding for the centres will be cut by a further 30 per cent from June next year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>昆士兰社区法律中心负责人詹姆斯·法雷尔表示，根据最新的国家社区协会法律中心调查报告，每年有数千人被拒之门外。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">James Farrell, Director of Community Legal Centres Queensland, said that according to a National Association of Community Legal Centres survey, thousands are turned away every year.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">詹姆斯·法雷尔, head of the Queensland Community Law Center, said thousands of people were turned away every year according to the latest National Community Association Law Center Investigation report.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">James Farrell, the head of the Queensland Community Law Centre, said thousands of people were turned away each year, according to the latest survey by the National Community Association's Law Centre.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>法雷尔先生表示，如果联邦政府不改变现有的决定，这一情况只会变得更糟。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">Mr. Farrell expressed that if the federal government does not change the current decision, this situation will only get worse.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">Mr Farrell says the situation will only get worse if the federal government does not change the existing decision.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">Mr Farrell said the situation would only get worse if the federal government did not change existing decisions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>他表示：“昆士兰的社区法律中心长期处于资金不足的状况，这意味着数千人将无法获得所需要的重要服务。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">He said, “Queensland’s Community Legal Centers constantly suffers from inadequate funding. This implies that many are unable to receive important services they require.”</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">"The Queensland Community Law Centre is chronically underfunded, which means thousands of people will not be able to get the essential services they need," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">"Queensland's community legal centres are chronically underfunded, which means thousands of people will not be able to access the vital services they need," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>需要远离暴力的人、背负无法偿还的巨额债务的人、面临分崩离析的家庭、被压榨的工人，这些人群都面临着法律层面的问题，并且该报告显示他们无法获得所需要的帮助。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">People such as those who must seek shelter from violence, who are unable to pay back their large debts, families facing the threat of disintegration, and abused workers face legal issues. This report showed that they were unable to receive the help they need.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">People who need to stay away from violence, those who are burdened with huge debts, families that are falling apart, and squeezed workers face legal problems, and the report shows that they are unable to get the help they need.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">People in need of protection from violence, people with huge debts that cannot be paid, families that are falling apart, workers who are being squeezed, all face legal problems, and the report shows that they are unable to get the help they need.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>联邦政府将自2017年6月起再削减30%的资金，这意味着昆士兰数千弱势群体将被迫在没有帮助的情况下面对复杂的法律问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">With effect from June 2017, the Federal government will cut funding by another 30%, implying that thousands of vulnerable groups in Queensland would be forced to face complex legal issues without any help.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">The federal government will cut back 30% of its funding since June 2017, which means thousands of vulnerable groups in Queensland will be forced to face complex legal problems without help.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">The federal government will cut funding by a further 30 per cent from June 2017, meaning thousands of vulnerable people in Queensland will be forced to deal with complex legal issues without help.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>我们呼吁司法部长兼昆士兰议员乔治·布兰迪斯立刻撤消这些削减资金的决定，让人们可以在面对法律问题时获得所需要的帮助。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">We call upon George Brandis, Attorney-General and senator representing Queensland, to revoke the decision for cutting back investments so that people can acquire the help they need to deal with legal issues.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">We call on the Attorney-General and Queensland Congressman 乔治·布兰迪斯 to withdraw the money-cutting decisions immediately so that people can get the help they need in the face of legal problems.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">We call on Attorney General and Queensland MP George Brandis to reverse these funding cuts immediately so that people can get the help they need when they face legal issues.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>去年，州政府承诺将法律援助资金提高到国家平均水平。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">The state government made a commitment last year to increase the legal aid fund to the national average.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">Last year, the state pledged to raise legal aid funds to the national average.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">Last year, the state government promised to raise legal aid funding to the national average.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.sl">
    <source>现在必须关注社区法律中心及其对应社区的需求，白乐琪政府也必须投入到这项重要的工作中。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.ht">Priority must now be placed on community legal centres and how they correspond to the needs of the community. The Palaszczuk government must also commit to this important task.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.gg">Attention must now be paid to the needs of Community law centres and their corresponding communities, and the Bai government must also devote itself to this important work.</translation>
    <translation system="083_smh.com.au.191329_en.c6">Attention must now be given to the needs of the community legal centres and their corresponding communities, and the Bellagio Government must also be involved in this important work.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
