<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>里德：希拉里若当选总统将提名加兰德进入最高法院</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Reid: Hilary would pick Garland as nominee for the Supreme Court if she was elected president</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Reid: Hillarijo elected president will nominate Garland to the Supreme Court</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">Reid: Hillary Clinton, if elected president, would nominate Garland to the Supreme Court</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>参议院民主党领袖哈里·里德 (Harry Reid) 说，他确信若民主党总统候选人希拉里·克林顿(Hillary Clinton) 当选总统，她将提名加兰德 (Merrick Garland) 法官进入最高法院。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Harry Reid, the Democratic Party leader in the United States Senate, said that he believes that if the Democratic Party presidential candidate Hillary Clinton becomes the President, she will nominate Merrich Garland to the Supreme Court.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Harry Reid, the Senate Democratic leader, said he was convinced that if Hillary Clinton, the Democratic presidential candidate, was elected president, she would nominate Garland (Merrick Garland) to the Supreme Court.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">Senate Democratic Leader Harry Reid said he is confident that if Democratic presidential candidate Hillary Clinton is elected president, she will nominate Judge Merrick Garland to the Supreme Court.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>参议院共和党人自巴拉克·奥巴马 (Barack Obama) 总统三月份提名加兰德以来，一直阻止对加兰德进行确认。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Since Barack Obama nominated Garland, Republican senators have constantly refused to ratify Garland’s nomination.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Senate Republicans have blocked confirmation of Garland since President Barack Obama nominated Garland in March.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">Senate Republicans have blocked the confirmation of Garland since President Barack Obama nominated him in March.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>参议院多数党领袖米奇·麦康奈尔 (Mitch McConnell) 表示，下届总统将选择此人来接替已故最高法院法官斯卡利亚 (Antonin Scalia)。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell expressed that the next President will select this person to replace Antonin Scalia, the late Justice of the Supreme Court.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Senate Majority Leader McConnell Mitch McConnell said the next president will choose this person to replace the late Supreme Court Judge Scalia (Antonin Scalia).</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said the next president would choose him to replace the late Supreme Court Justice Antonin Scalia.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>里德在周四的一次电话会议上说，他预测希拉里会选择“有一些可信度”的加兰德。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Reed said, during a teleconference on Thursday, that he expects Hillary to select Garand, which is “somewhat reliable”.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Reid said in a conference call in Thursday that he predicted Hillary would choose "some credibility" garland.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">Reid said on a conference call Thursday that he predicted Hillary would pick Garland who "has some credibility."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>里德的一位女发言人随后说，里德没有就是否会提名加兰德直接与希拉里对话，并说他只是猜测。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">A spokeswoman for Reid said subsequently that Reid did not speak to Hilary directly about whether she would nominate Garland, and said that he was just guessing.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">A spokeswoman for Reed said later that Reed did not talk directly to Hillary about whether he would nominate Garland and said he was just guessing.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">A spokeswoman for Reid later said Reid had not spoken directly to Hillary about whether she would nominate Garland, and said he was only guessing.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>他对加兰德大加赞赏，并说希拉里的团队不希望因新人选而“搅局”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">He praised Garland profusely, and said that Hillary’s team did not wish to “make a mess” because of the new candidate.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">He praised Rand and said Hillary's team did not want to "disrupt" the new candidate.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">He heaped praise on Garland and said Hillary's team didn't want to be "spoiled" by the new pick.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>加兰德是美国哥伦比亚特区联邦巡回上诉法院的首席法官。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Garland is the  Chief United States Circuit Judge of the United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Garland is the chief judge of the United States Columbia, Dist. OF Federal Circuit appeals court.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">Garland is the chief justice of the United States Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit in the District of Columbia.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>里德说，阻止加兰德提名的共和党人是共和党总统候选人唐纳德·特朗普 (Donald Trump) 的“宠臣”与“成就者”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">Reid said that Republicans blocking Garland’s nomination are Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump’s “minions” and “enablers”.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">Mr. Reid said the Republicans who blocked the nomination of Garland were the "doting" and "achievers" of the Republican presidential candidate, Donald Trump.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">The Republicans who blocked Garland's nomination are "favorites" and "achievers" of Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump, Reid said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="100_foxnews.68156_en.sl">
    <source>他说特朗普不适合当总统。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.ht">He said Trump is not President-type.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.gg">He said that Trump was not fit to be president.</translation>
    <translation system="100_foxnews.68156_en.c6">He said Trump was unfit to be president.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
