<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>塔吉克斯坦“阿维斯塔”通讯社11日援引塔央行的消息称，今年前7个月塔国的通货膨胀率为3.7%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">Tajikistan’s “Avesta” news agency, citing information from the Tajik central bank, claimed that Tajikistan’s inflation was 3.7% for the first seven months of this year.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">Tajikistan's "Avesta" news agency 11th quoted the Tower Central Bank as saying that the first 7 months of this year's inflation rate of 3.7%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">The country's inflation rate in the first seven months of this year was 3.7 percent, Tajikistan's Avesta news agency said on Monday, citing the central bank.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>报道指出，今年前7个月塔国的通货膨胀率为3.7%，其中7月份的通胀率为0.6%，而近一年的通胀率为6%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">The report pointed out that inflation in Tajikistan was 3.7% in the first seven months of this year. In particular, inflation in the month of July was 0.6%, while inflation for the most recent year was 6%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">reported that the first 7 months of this year's inflation rate of 3.7%, which July inflation rate of 0.6%, and nearly a year's inflation rate of 6%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">The country's inflation rate was 3.7 percent in the first seven months of the year, with an inflation rate of 0.6 percent in July, compared with 6 percent in the past year, the report said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>报道称，塔政府的目标是计划将2016年的年通胀率控制在7.5%的水平，而2015年塔国的通胀率为5.1%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">The report said that the aim of the Tajik government is to maintain annual inflation rate within 7.5% in 2016. In 2015, the inflation rate of Tajikistan was 5.1%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">The government's goal is to plan to keep inflation at 7.5% per cent in 2016, compared with 5.1% in 2015, the report said.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">The government aims to keep annual inflation at 7.5 percent in 2016, compared with 5.1 percent in 2015, the report said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>另外，报道还指出，在塔国2016年的经济发展和通胀的问题上，塔政府与一些主要的国际金融机构的预测存在着一定的出入。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">Reports further pointed out that for economic development and inflation issues faced by Tajikistan in 2016, the Tajik government and a number of major international financial institutions made different predictions in these areas.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">In addition, the report points out that there is a certain discrepancy between the tower government and some of the major international financial institutions in the country's economic development and inflation in the 2016.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">Also, the report points out that there are some discrepancies between the forecasts of the government and some of the major international financial institutions when it comes to economic development and inflation in the country in 2016.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>根据塔贸易和经济发展部的预测，2016年塔国的经济增长将达到7%，而国家的通胀也基本是在这一水平之上。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">Tajikistan’s Ministry of Economic Development and Trade forecast that the nation’s economic growth would reach 7% in 2016, while inflation would also be above this level in general.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">According to the Ministry of Trade and Economic development, the economic growth of the country in 2016 will be 7%, and the inflation rate of the state is basically above this level.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">The country's economy will grow by 7 per cent in 2016, according to forecasts from the country's Ministry of Trade and Economic Development, while the country's inflation is also largely above that level.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而亚洲开发银行、世界银行和国际货币基金组织则是对于塔国2016年经济发展和通胀水则纷纷给出了不同的预测。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">On the other hand, the Asia Development Bank, the World Bank, and the International Monetary Fund respectively gave different predictions for economic development and inflation of Tajikistan in 2016.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">The Asian Development Bank, the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund have given different forecasts for the 2016 economic development and inflationary waters of the country.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">The Asian Development Bank, the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund have given different forecasts for the country's economic development and inflation in 2016.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>对于这两项指标，亚洲开发银行的预测为4.2%和7%，世界银行的预测为4.8%和7.5%，国际货币基金组织的预测为3.4%和8.2%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">As regards these two indicators, forecasts by the Asian Development Bank was 4.2% and 7%; the World Bank’s was 4.8% and 7.5%; and that of the International Monetary Fund at 3.4% and 8.2%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">For both indicators, the Asian Development Bank forecasts 4.2% and 7%, the World Bank forecasts 4.8% and 7.5%, and the IMF forecasts 3.4% and 8.2%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">For both indicators, the projections are 4.2 per cent and 7 per cent for the Asian Development Bank, 4.8 per cent and 7.5 per cent for the World Bank and 3.4 per cent and 8.2 per cent for the International Monetary Fund.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据悉，尽管受到了国际经济不景气、俄罗斯卢布贬值以及侨汇减少等一系列不利外部因素的影响，但是2015年塔国的经济还是实现了6%的增长。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.ht">From our understanding, although affected by a series of negative external factors that include poor global economy, depreciation of the Russian ruble, and reducing foreign remittance, the Tajik economy managed to achieve a 6% growth in 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.gg">It is reported that despite a series of adverse external factors, such as the international economic downturn, the devaluation of the Russian rouble and the reduction of remittances, the 2015 economic growth of the country was 6%.</translation>
    <translation system="004_ifeng0812.news.49767570_0_zh.c6">Despite a series of adverse external factors, including the international economic downturn, the depreciation of the Russian rouble and the decline in remittances, the country's economy grew by 6% in 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
