<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>传统习俗引入新亮点“2016盂兰文化节”香港维园开幕</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">Traditional customs with new highlights - 2016 Ullam Cultural Festival unveiled at Victoria Park in Hong Kong</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">Traditional customs introduce new bright spot "2016 culture festival" opening of Hong Kong Victoria Park</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">Traditional customs introduce new bright spot "2016 Ullambana Cultural Festival" Hong Kong Victoria Park opening</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>敲锣打鼓的音乐、传统的小食、花俏的装饰、人群汹涌的现场。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">Music with drums and gongs, traditional snacks, fanciful decorations, and a chock-a-block crowd at the scene.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">Gongs and drums of music, traditional snacks, fancy decorations, crowds raging scene.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">Gongs and drums music, traditional snacks, fancy decorations, the crowd surging scene.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>由香港潮属社团总会主办的“2016盂兰文化节”12日至14日在维多利亚公园举办，这是香港最盛大的一场盂兰胜会。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">The “2016 Ullam Cultural Festival” organized by the Federation of Hong Kong Chiu Chow Community Organizations will be held at Victoria Park from 12th to the 14th. This will be the largest Ullam celebration held in Hong Kong.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">The "2016 Culture festival" organised by the Hong Kong Association of the Tides is the largest in Hong Kong in Victoria Park from 12th to 14th.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">Organised by the Federation of Teochew Societies in Hong Kong, the "2016 Python Cultural Festival" is held at Victoria Park from 12 to 14 July.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>除了延续已有的“抢孤竞赛”，还增加了全家可以参加的“亲子盆供堆垒赛”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">Other than the " Catching the Single" from the previous events, a new game of " Family Piling" was added for the whole family to enjoy.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">In addition to the continuation of the existing "race", but also increased the family can participate in the "Children's bowl for the heap base race."</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">In addition to the continuation of the existing "solitary race", but also added the whole family can participate in the "parent-child basin for the Stack."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>不仅用漫画形式介绍盂兰文化历史，现场还设有盂兰主题3D自拍区、传统小食区以及传统手艺流动教室等，吸引不少小朋友和海外人士来体验参观。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">A comic is used to introduce the cultural history of Ullam festival. The venue also included 3D photograph area based on the Ullam theme, traditional snacks, and mobile traditional hands-on workshops that attracted many children and overseas visitors to visit the place and experience its attractions.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">Not only in the form of the introduction of the cultural history of the orchid, the scene also has the theme of 3D self-portrait area, traditional small food areas and traditional crafts, such as mobile classrooms, attracting many children and overseas people to experience the visit.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">Not only in the form of comics to introduce the culture and history of pyelan, the scene also has the theme of pyelan 3D selfie area, traditional snack area and traditional crafts mobile classrooms, etc., attracting many children and overseas visitors to experience the visit.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>一对来自法国的夫妻在活动现场逗留了近3个小时，并且在迷你花牌流动教室体验了一番。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">A French couple stayed in the event venue for nearly 3 hours, and had a great experience with the mini floral card workshop.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">A couple from France stayed at the scene for nearly 3 hours and experienced a mini card mobile classroom.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">A couple from France spent nearly three hours at the event and had an experience in the mini floats mobile classroom.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“在网上查到这个特别的节日，所以决定来看看，感到很新鲜。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">“I found this special festival on the net, and decided to come and have a look. Its really interesting.”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">"On the Internet to find this special holiday, so decided to see, feel very fresh." ”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">"I found out about this special holiday on the Internet, so I decided to come and have a look.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他们表示，虽然法国也有类似纪念先人的节日，但气氛很沉重，不像这里，有音乐，有食物还可以学习传统手艺。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">They expressed that though France have similar holidays to celebrate historical characters, the atmosphere is more somber unlike this place where there is music, food, and an opportunity to learn about the traditional arts.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">They said that although France has a similar commemoration of ancestors of the festival, but the atmosphere is very heavy, unlike here, there is music, there is food can also learn traditional crafts.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">They said that while there were similar festivals in France to honour their ancestors, the atmosphere was heavy, unlike here, where there was music, food and learning traditional crafts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她说，“在香港这么繁忙的金融大都市，还能看到这么有规模、有组织的祭拜祖先的仪式。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">She said: “It is surprising to see an ancestral worshiping ceremony of such scale and organization in a busy financial metropolis such as Hong Kong.”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">She said, "in such a busy financial metropolis as Hong Kong, we can see the rituals of such a large and organized cult ancestor." ”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">"In such a busy financial metropolis as Hong Kong," she said, "you can still see such a large-scale, organized ceremony of ancestor worship."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这不仅体现了中国文化的多元性，还能让更多人了解这些传统手艺并且传承下去。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">“This not only highlighted the diversity of Chinese culture, but also allowed more people to learn about these traditional handicraft and pass on this legacy.”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">"This not only embodies the diversity of Chinese culture, but also allows more people to understand these traditional crafts and pass on." ”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">"This not only reflects the diversity of Chinese culture, but also allows more people to understand these traditional crafts and pass them on."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>本次活动总统筹胡炎松表示，“我们不想把盂兰文化节布置得很恐怖，让人不敢接近，特别是小孩子。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">Wu Yim-chung, overall coordinator of this event, said, “We didn't want to have scary decorations for the Hungry Ghost Cultural Festival so that people, particularly little kids, dare not approach.”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">Hutison said, "We do not want to decorate the Orchid culture festival is very scary, people dare not close, especially children." ”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">"We don't want to make it too scary for people to approach, especially children," said Hu Yansong, the event's general manager.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“我们希望通过现场年轻化的活动和布置，让年轻人知道盂兰节文化背后想表达的是孝道和感恩。“</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">“We hope that by providing a younger setting and decor for the event, youths will be able to learn that the Ullam Festival aims to communicate the virtue of filial piety and thanksgiving.”</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">We hope that through the site rejuvenation of the activities and arrangements, let young people know that the culture behind the Orchid Festival is filial piety and Thanksgiving. “</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">"We hope to let young people know that filial piety and gratitude are behind the culture of the festival," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他也表示，这次共有24个队伍参加“抢孤竞赛”，其中不仅有社团组织，还与一些学校合作，让学生参加。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">He also said that a total of 24 teams will take part in this “compete with lonely souls for sacrificial offerings” contest. In addition to social groups and organizations, they are also working with a few schools to allow students to take part in the contest.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">He also said that a total of 24 teams participated in the "Race to compete", including not only the community organizations, but also with some schools to participate in the students.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">He also said that this time a total of 24 teams to participate in the "orphan race," which not only organizations, but also in cooperation with a number of schools to allow students to participate.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据了解，香港潮人盂兰胜会已于2011年列入“国家级非物质文化遗产名录”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.ht">It is reported that the Hungry Ghost Festival of the Federation of Hong Kong Chiu Chow Community has been included in the “National Grade Intangible Cultural Heritage Catalog” in 2011.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.gg">It is understood that the Hong Kong tide People's victory will be included in the "National Intangible Cultural Heritage Directory" in 2011.</translation>
    <translation system="081_ifeng0812.news.49768271_0_zh.c6">It is understood that the Tidal Orchid Society of Hong Kong has been included in the "National Intangible Cultural Heritage List" in 2011.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
