<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月11日上午8点，齐鲁晚报记者跟随“健康中国行”义诊服务小组来到东港区西湖镇河沟村。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">At 8:00 AM of August 11, the reporter of Qilu Evening News followed the volunteer health consultation team of “Healthy China Tour” and arrived at Hegou Village in Xihu County, Donggang District.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">August 11 8 o'clock in the morning, Qilu Evening News reporter followed the "Healthy China Line" Free clinic service team came to East Haven District West Lake Town Ditch village.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">At 8 a.m. on August 11, a reporter from Qilu Evening News followed the "Healthy China Tour" volunteer medical service team to the village of Hegou, Xihu Town, Donggang District.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>该村地处偏僻，距市区约24公里，村里居民200多户，因经济、交通和身体等方面的局限性，给很多中老年患者出门看病带来不便。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">The village, approximately 24 km from the city, is remotely situated. There are more than 200 households living in the village. Limited by economic, transport and physical factors, middle aged and elderly patients find it inconvenient to visit the doctor.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">The village is located in the remote, about 24 kilometers from the urban area, the village residents more than 200 households, because of economic, transportation and physical limitations, to many elderly patients out of the doctor brought inconvenience.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">The village is located in a remote area, about 24 kilometers away from the city, the village residents more than 200 households, because of economic, transportation and physical limitations, to many middle-aged and elderly patients to go out to see a doctor inconvenience.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>此次义诊的项目比较全面，内科、外科、呼吸科、精神科、皮肤科、儿科。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">The scope of this volunteer medical consultation service is quite thorough, and includes internal medicine, surgery, pneumology, psychiatry, dermatology, and pediatric departments.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">The Free Clinic program is comprehensive, medical, surgical, respiratory, psychiatric, dermatology, pediatrics.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">The free consultation project is more comprehensive, internal medicine, surgery, respiratory, psychiatry, dermatology, paediatrics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>很多村民听说义诊的专家要来，早早就已经在村里的小广场等待。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">Many villages heard that volunteer health care specialists would be visiting, and began waiting at the small village square very early on.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">Many villagers have heard that experts from the clinic are coming and have been waiting in the village's small square early.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">Many villagers heard that experts from the free clinic were coming and had been waiting in the village's small square early on.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>67岁的薛大娘患有先天性脊柱侧弯，而最近几年的时间她又深受“哮喘”的困扰，以致连走着上个坡都会气喘吁吁，喘不上气。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">Mdm Xue, who is 67 years old this year, suffers from congenital scoliosis. She also recently experienced the issues caused by asthma, and would often pant and find herself short of breath when climbing slopes.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">67-year-old aunt Xue suffers from congenital scoliosis, and in recent years she was suffering from "asthma", so that even walking on the last slope will be breathless, gasping for breath.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">Dame Xue, 67, suffers from congenital scoliosis and has been suffering from asthma in recent years, leaving her breathless and breathless even walking up the slope.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>医生告诉薛大娘，慢性支气管炎想要根本治愈的可能性不大，平常坚持用药可有所缓解。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">The doctor told Aunty Xue that there is little possibility of a cure for chronic bronchitis, but regular and determined medical treatment can provide relief.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">Doctors tell aunt Xue, chronic bronchitis want to cure the possibility of a little, usually adhere to medication can be alleviated.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">Doctor told xue auntie, chronic bronchitis wants to cure the possibility of fundamental is not big, usually insist on medication can be alleviated.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在皮肤科医生问诊处，一名60多岁的老人带着她的小孙子前来咨询。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">An elderly lady in her sixties brought her little grandchild for consultation at the clinic of the dermatologist.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">At the dermatologist's office, a more than 60-year-old man came to consult with her little grandson.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">At the dermatologist's office, a man in his 60s came to the consultation with her baby grandson.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>老人的小孙子今年11岁，从孩子3岁开始，左脚一直受“脚气”困扰。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">The old man’s youngest grandson is 11 years old. Since the boy was 3, he has been chronically affected by “jiaoqi” on his left foot.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">The old man's grandson is 11 years old, and his left foot has been plagued by "beriberi" since he was 3 years old.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">The old man's young grandson, aged 11, has been suffering from "beriberi" in his left foot since the child was three years old.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>医生查看后告诉老人，这并不是“脚气”而是季节性的湿疹，千万不要随意用药耽误了治疗。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">After checking the legs, the doctor told the elderly that the issue was not “jiaoqi” (athlete’s foot) but seasonal dermatitis, and gave the reminder to stop using non-prescription drugs and avoid delaying proper treatment.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">After the doctor looked at the elderly, this is not "beriberi" but seasonal eczema, do not use drugs delayed treatment.</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">Doctors checked it out and told the elderly that it was not "beriberi" but seasonal eczema and never delay treatment with random medication.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“在这个村我们提供了看病和B超的服务，而另一队在五莲县户部乡邱家店子村的义诊服务队还提供了免费体检的服务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">“We provided medical treatment and B-scan ultrasonography services in this village, while another team of volunteer doctors also provided free medical examination services at Qiujiadianzi Village, Hubu Township, Wulian County.”</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">"In this village we have provided medical treatment and B-super services, while the other team in the Wulian County village of the township of the Clinic of the medical unit to provide free health care services."</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">"In this village we provide medical treatment and B ultrasound services, while another team of free medical services in Qiu Jiadian Village, Hubu Township, Wulian County, also provides free medical examination services.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.sl">
    <source>此次下乡义诊只是‘健康中国行’的其中一个部分，在以后的日子里，其他活动还将陆续开展。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.ht">This round of volunteer medical consultation service is only part of the Healthy China Tour. Other activities will be implemented accordingly in the future.”</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.gg">The trip to the countryside is just one part of a ' healthy China ', and in the days to come, other activities will continue. ”</translation>
    <translation system="076_ifeng0812.news.49767410_0_zh.c6">The free clinic is just one part of the 'Healthy China Tour' and other activities will follow in the days to come.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
