<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>格雷西亚是一只萌萌的雌性巨嘴鸟，浑身散发着热带雨林的气息。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Gracia is a cute female toucan with the scent of the jungle about her.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Gracian is an eruption of female giant beak bird, the whole body exudes the breath of the rainforest.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Gracia is a budding female toucan with the scent of a tropical rainforest.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在中美洲国家哥斯达黎加，巨嘴鸟格雷西亚和它的故事早已家喻户晓。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">In the Central American country of Costa Rica, the toucan Gracia and its story are extremely well-known.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">In the Central American country Costa Rica, the Gracian and its story has long been a household name.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">In the Central American country of Costa Rica, the toucan Gracia and its story have long been a household name.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月10日的新闻发布会上，术后康复的格雷西亚终于亮相，向人们展示它崭新的3D打印塑料鸟喙。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">The August 10 press conference finally revealed Gracia after recovering from the operation, displaying its brand new 3D-printed plastic beak.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">At the August 10 press conference, the Gracian of postoperative recovery finally unveiled its brand-new 3D print-plastic beak.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">At a press conference on August 10, Gracia, who is recovering from surgery, finally appeared to show off her brand-new, 3D printed plastic beak.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这只一年半前被人折断上喙、奄奄一息的巨嘴鸟，如今终于重获新生。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">This toucan whose upper beak was broken by someone, and which was on the brink of death, has now finally received a new lease of life.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">The giant beak, which had been broken up by a 1.5 ago and was dying, has now finally been reborn.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">The dying toucan, which had its beak snapped off a year and a half ago, has been given a new lease of life.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>这一天不仅宣告着它已100%恢复健康，更是它搬进豪华鸟舍、与关心它的人类朋友们见面的日子。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">This is the day that the bird has reached 100% recovery and the day when it could be moved to a luxurious bird house and meet its human friends who have been caring for it.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Not only did this day proclaim that it was 100% restored to health, it was the day when it moved into the luxury aviary and met with the human friends who cared for it.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">This day heralds not only its 100 per cent return to health, but also its move into the luxurious aviary and its meeting with human friends who care about it.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>初进新家的格雷西亚稍显腼腆，但不多时就变得活泼起来，在水盆里打滚嬉闹，用新喙吃葡萄。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Gracia appears to be rather shy after moving to her new home, but quickly revealed her lively side, playing in the pool of water and using her new beak to eat grapes.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">First entered the new home of the Gracian slightly shy, but not too much to become lively, in the water Basin, roll frolic, with a new beak to eat grapes.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Gracia, who had just entered her new home, was a little shy, but soon became active, wallowing in the basin and eating the grapes with her new beak.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>为了提醒人们它曾经遭受的伤害，技术人员没有给它的新喙上色，而是保留了3D打印材料原有的白色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">To remind people of the abuse it once suffered, the technicians did not color its new beak, but kept it white, the original color of the 3D printing material.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">To remind people of the damage it had suffered, the technician did not paint its new beak, but retained the original white of the 3D printing material.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">To remind people of the damage it has suffered, instead of painting its new beak, technicians have kept the original white of the 3D printing material.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>鸟喙外是一层薄薄的角质鞘，里面中空，只有一些细细的骨质支撑杆交错排列。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">The external layer of the beak is a thin keratin sheath. The beak is hollow and only reinforced by thin, criss-crossing supporting struts of bone.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Outside the beak is a thin layer of cutin sheath, inside hollow, only some thin bone supporting rod staggered arrangement.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">The beak is covered with a thin, horny sheath that is hollow inside, with only a few thin, bone-supporting poles interlaced.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>虽然有这种内部加固成份，巨嘴鸟的喙还是脆弱，受到伤害时会破碎。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Although reinforced internally, the toucan’s beak is still fragile, and will crack when it is harmed.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Despite this internal reinforcement, the beak of a giant beak is fragile and broken when it is hurt.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Despite this internal reinforcement, the toucan's beak is still fragile and will break when it is damaged.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>动物救助中心、鸟类学家和一家美国3D打印公司通力合作，为格雷西亚制作了好几个“试验喙”，终于造出最适合它的“完美喙”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">The animal aid center, an ornithologist, and a 3D printing company from the United States are working together, making several “experimental beaks” for Gracia before creating the “perfect beak” that best suits the bird.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">The animal Rescue Center, a bird biologist and a US 3D printing company worked together to produce several "test beaks" for Gracian, finally creating the "perfect beak" best suited to it.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">The Animal Rescue Center, ornithologists and an American 3D printing company worked together to create several "experimental beaks" for Gracia, finally creating the "perfect beak" for her.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>如今格雷西亚已能熟练使用新喙喝水、吃东西，甚至啄起细小谷粒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Now Gracia has become proficient in using her beak to drink, eat, and even pick up fine seed grains.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Now Gracian is adept at using new beaks to drink, eat, and even peck up tiny grains.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Gracia is now adept at using her new beak to drink, eat and even pick up tiny grains.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“最终成品的设计花了大约2个月，打印出来只需4、5个小时。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">“The design of the final product took about two months; printing took just four to five hours.”</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">"The final finished design took about 2 months to print out and only 4, 5 hours." ”</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">"The final product took about two months to design and only four or five hours to print."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“3D打印并不是未来技术，它已经实实在在走进了你我的生活。”美国SG3D打印公司董事长托马斯·朗格在接受新华国际记者采访时说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">"3D printing is not for next generation. It has become part of our life." Thomas Lange, President of SG3D told the  Xinhua News Agency.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">"3D printing is not the future technology, it has actually come into your life." "U.S. Sg3d printing company Chairman 托马斯·朗格 in an interview with Xinhua International reporter said.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">"3D printing is not the technology of the future, it has really come into your life and mine," Thomas Langer, chairman of SG3D printing company, told Xinhua International.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2015年1月，在哥斯达黎加中部阿拉胡埃拉省格雷西亚的一个农场，浑身是血的巨嘴鸟格雷西亚被人发现。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">On January 2015, Gracia the toucan was found, bleeding from its mouth, by a person in a farm at Gracia, Alajuela Province in central Costa Rica.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">In January 2015, a farm in Gracian, a Alajuela province in central Costa Rica, was found to be a blood-soaked giant beak gracian.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Gracia, a toucan covered in blood, was discovered on a farm in Gracia, in the central Alajuela province of Costa Rica, in January 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>当时它的上喙被一伙年轻人残忍折断，它完全无法进食，生命垂危。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">At the time, its upper beak was cruelly broken by a group of youths. It could not eat and was dying.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Its upper beak was brutally broken by a gang of young men, and it was utterly incapable of eating and dying.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">At that time, its beak was brutally broken by a group of young people, it was completely unable to eat, life-threatening.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>格雷西亚的惨状经媒体报道后，在哥斯达黎加内外引起如潮的反对虐待动物呼声。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Once reported in mass media, Gracia’s sad state initiated a wave of outcry against animal abuse in and outside Costa Rica.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Gracian's horror was reported in the media, in Costa Rica and outside the cause of the wave of opposition to cruelty to animals.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">The tragedy in Gracia has caused a flurry of calls against animal cruelty in and around Costa Rica after media reports.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>人们要求设立更为严格的动物保护法、加大对虐待者的惩罚力度。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">The public requested more rigorous animal protection laws to be established, and punishment for abusers to be stepped out.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Stricter animal-protection laws and tougher punishments for abusers are called for.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">There have been calls for stricter animal protection laws and greater penalties for abusers.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>人们自发前来，尽最大努力帮助格雷西亚尽可能恢复受伤前的生活。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">People came forward voluntarily, and did the best they could to help Grecia regain its life prior to the injury.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">People come spontaneously and do their best to help Gracian to recover as much as possible before the injury.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">People came spontaneously and did their best to help Gracia get back to life as much as possible before the injury.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>甚至3D打印技术发明人查克·赫尔也参与到格雷西亚上喙的设计中来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Even Chuck Hull, the inventor of 3D printing technology, also contributed towards the design of Gracia’s upper beak.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Even 3D print technology inventor 查克·赫尔 was involved in the design of Gracian's beak.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Even Chuck Hull, the inventor of 3D printing technology, was involved in the design of Gracia's upper beak.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“格雷西亚的情况很特殊，它的上喙剩余部分不足1厘米，所以给安装新喙带来许多困难。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">“Gracia’s condition is quite unique. Less than 1 cm of its upper beak has remained, making it difficult to install a new beak.”</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">"The Gracian is very special, its upper beak is less than 1 centimeters, so it poses many difficulties in installing the new beak." ”</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">"The case of Gracia is unique in that the remaining part of its upper beak is less than one centimetre, which makes it difficult to install a new beak," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“我们先对格雷西亚扫描，然后设计、制作出一个稍长于它上喙剩余部分的延长假体，用粘胶固定在它的上喙上。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">“We first scanned Gracia and then designed and manufactured an extended prosthetic that is slightly longer than its remaining upper beak. The prosthetic is then glued to its upper beak.”</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">"We scanned the Gracian and then designed and produced an elongated prosthesis that was slightly longer than the remainder of its upper beak, which was glued to its upper beak." ”</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">"We scanned Gracia and then designed and made an extended prosthesis that was slightly longer than the rest of her upper beak.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这样可以减少对格雷西亚造成进一步侵入性伤害。”朗格对新华国际记者说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">“This will help reduce further invasive injury on Grecia,” Lange told a XInhua international news reporter.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">"This can reduce further invasive damage to Gracian." Lange told Xinhua International correspondent.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">"This will reduce further invasive damage to Gracia," Langer told Xinhua International.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在安装假体之前，工作人员每天都要为格雷西亚清理断喙，以防感染。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Prior to installing the prosthetics, workers cleaned the broken beak for Gracia everyday to prevent infections.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Before installing the prosthesis, the worker cleans up the beak for Gracian every day to prevent infection.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Before installing the prosthesis, staff had to clean up Gracia's beak every day to prevent infection.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>远在千里之外，巨嘴鸟格雷西亚的故事感动了著名纪录片导演葆拉·埃雷迪亚和探索新闻频道制片人约翰·霍夫曼。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Thousands of miles away, the story of Gracia the toucan has moved renowned documentary filmmaker Paula Heredia and investigative journalist John Hoffman.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">Far away, the story of giant Beak bird Gracian moved the famous documentary filmmaker Paula 拉·埃雷迪亚 and Discovery News channel producer 约翰·霍夫曼.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">Thousands of miles away, the story of Toucan Gracia moved famous documentary filmmaker Paula Heredia and Discovery News producer John Hoffman.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>他们记录下格雷西亚安装新喙过程中的点点滴滴，录制了一部纪录片《巨嘴鸟之国》，已于本月在动物星球频道上播放。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">Toucan Nation is a documentary that recorded in detail the process of fitting a new beak for Grecia, which was broadcast on Animal Planet this month.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">They recorded the gracian of the new Beak, recording a documentary film, "The Kingdom of the giant beak," which was broadcast on the Animal Planet Channel this month.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">They chronicled the installation of Gracia's new beak and recorded a documentary, "Land of the Toucans," which was shown on Animal Planet this month.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.sl">
    <source>纪录片《巨嘴鸟之国》向人们展示，一只小小的巨嘴鸟是如何让一个国家为之改变、如何让国民都参与到反对虐待动物当中来。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.ht">The documentary Toucan Nation showed how a small toucan bird could change a country and encourage every citizen to participate in the movement against animal abuse.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.gg">The country of the giant beak shows how a tiny giant beak can change a country and involve its citizens in the fight against cruelty to animals.</translation>
    <translation system="166_ifeng0812.news.49766158_0_zh.c6">The documentary "Land of Toucans" shows how a tiny toucan can make a country change for itself, and how it can involve its citizens in the fight against animal cruelty.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
