<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>宁泽涛在100米自由泳半决赛中的表现，已经让很多中国观众无语。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Ning Zetao’s performance during the 100-meter freestyle semi-finals has left many Chinese viewers speechless.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Ningzetao's performance in the semi-finals of the 100-metre freestyle has made many Chinese audiences silent.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Ning's performance in the 100m freestyle semi-final has left many Chinese viewers speechless.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>可就在50米自由泳预赛中，宁泽涛再一次刷新了人们的“底线”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Again, Ning Zetao dropped the jaw of everyone during the 50m freestyle in the heats.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">But in the 50-metre freestyle preliminaries, Ningzetao once again refreshed people's "bottom line."</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">But in the 50m freestyle preliminaries, Ning Zetao once again refreshed the people's "bottom line."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>其实50米自由泳并非宁泽涛主项，他在喀山世锦赛上的表现和最好成绩，也决定了他在这个项目取得突破的可能性不大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">In fact, the 50-meter freestyle was not Ning Zetao's dominant event. His performance and best result at the Kazan FINA World Championships have also meant that the possibility of getting a breakthrough in this event is quite small.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">In fact, 50 meters freestyle is not Ningzetao items, his performance in the Kazan World Championships and the best results, but also decided that his project to make a breakthrough is unlikely.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">In fact, 50 meters freestyle is not the main event Ning Zetao, his performance at the Kazan World Championships and the best results, but also decided that he is unlikely to break through in this project.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>果然，香港权威媒体《大公报》透露，宁泽涛失利的最大原因，就在于他已经失去了对游泳的兴趣。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">As expected, Takungpao, a renowned Hong Kong news company, disclosed that the biggest reason behind Ning Zetao’s defeat was that he had already lost interest in swimming.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Sure enough, Hong Kong's authoritative media, the big communiqué, revealed that the biggest reason for Ningzetao's failure was that he had lost interest in swimming.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Sure enough, the Ta Kung Pao, an authoritative Hong Kong media outlet, revealed that the biggest reason for Ning's loss was that he had lost interest in swimming.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>场外的许多因素，可能对他对未来的想法产生了很大影响，他现在对进军娱乐圈可能更感兴趣。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Many external factors could play a significant role in his thoughts about the future. At this time, he is probably more interested in the entertainment business.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Many factors outside the field may have had a big impact on his ideas for the future, and he is now more interested in entering the entertainment circle.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Many factors off the field may have had a big impact on his thinking about the future, and he may now be more interested in moving into the entertainment industry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>喀山世锦赛后，宁泽涛凭借其超高颜值和好成绩，瞬间成为网红。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">After the Kazan FINA World Championships, Ning Zetao became an instant Internet celebrity because of his good looks and good performance.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Kazan World Championships, Ningzetao by virtue of its super high value and good results, instant become a net red.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">After the world championships in Kazan, Ning Zetao became an instant net red thanks to his super high Yan value and good results.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>于是，“国民老公”、“小鲜肉”、“花样美男”等称呼也不断成为他身上的标签。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">He was therefore tagged with the labels of “public husband”, “young hunk”, “flowery boy”, and other similar monikers.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Thus, "national husband", "small meat", "pattern of the United States" and other forms of address has become his label.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">As a result, "national husband", "small fresh meat", "pattern beautiful man" and other terms also continue to become the label on his body.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>各种商业活动找上门来，美好的钱途，成为一条金光闪烁的大道。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Various commercial opportunities have arrived, providing great economic prospects for building a bustling boulevard.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">A variety of business activities to find the door, the good money, become a glittering road.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">A variety of commercial activities come to the door, a good money, become a golden twinkling Avenue.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在这种情况下，宁泽涛即使选择在此时退役加入娱乐圈，不仅是他的自由，也是一条看似可行的道路。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Under these circumstances, even if Ning Zetao chooses to retire and join the entertainment business, not only is this his own choice, it is also a feasible option.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">In this case, Ningzetao even choose to retire at this time to join the entertainment circle, is not only his freedom, but also a plausible path.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">In this case, even if Ning Zetao chooses to retire and join the entertainment industry at this time, it is not only his freedom, but also a seemingly viable path.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>毕竟他只有23岁，经过一定的学习，完全可以凭借其人气出演一两部电视剧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">He is just 23 after all. With a bit of training, he will definitely be able to act in a couple of TV dramas based on his popularity.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">After all, he is only 23 years old, after a certain amount of study, can rely on his popularity to play one or two TV dramas.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">After all, he is only 23 years old, after a certain amount of learning, can rely on its popularity to star in one or two television series.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但宁泽涛需要看看，自己和这些前辈相比，是不是具备了足够的资格呢？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Ning Zetao must make sure that he is qualified enough to be considered an equal to his predecessors.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">But Ningzetao need to see, oneself and these predecessors compared, not have enough qualifications?</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">But Ning Zetao needs to see if he has enough qualifications compared with those of his predecessors.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>2000年悉尼奥运会，已经21岁的刘璇已经来到了运动员生涯的末期。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">For the 2000 Sydney Olympics, Liu Xuan, who was 21 years old by that time, has arrived at the end of her athletic carrier.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">The 2000 Sydney Olympic Games, the 21-year-old Xuan has come to the end of the athlete's career.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">At the 2000 Sydney Olympics, Liu Xuan, now 21, had reached the end of his athletic career.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刘璇靓丽的外表让她迅速被人们记住，也奠定了她今后进军娱乐圈的基础。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Liu Xuan’s attractive appearance quickly made a impression with the people, and also served as the basis for her entry in the entertainment industry.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Xuan's beautiful appearance made her quickly remembered and laid the groundwork for her future foray into the entertainment circle.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Liu Xuan's beautiful appearance made her quickly remembered and laid the foundation for her future foray into the entertainment industry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>退役后，刘璇出演了多部电视剧，并在2013年成立了自己的工作室。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">After retiring, Liu Xuan appeared in many television drama series and even established her own studio in 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">After retiring, Xuan starred in a number of TV dramas and set up his own studio in 2013.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">After retiring, Liu Xuan starred in a number of television series and set up his own studio in 2013.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>田亮参加了两次奥运会的单双人十米台比赛，并获得了2金2银。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Tian Liang participated in the men’s single and synchronized 10 meter platform competition, winning 2 gold and 2 silver medals.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Tian participated in the two Olympic Games single two-person 10-meter competition, and won 2 Gold 2 silver.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Tian Liang competed in the single double 10-meter platform race in two Olympic Games and won two gold and two silver.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但在2004年奥运会单人十米台比赛中输给队友胡佳后，田亮的竞技状态出现下滑，并被爆出被跳水队开除。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">After losing to Hu Jia, a fellow team mate, for the single 10 meter platform in the 2004 Olympics, Tian Liang’s athletic competitiveness deteriorated, and it was heard that he was expelled from the diving team.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">But after losing to teammate Hu Jia in the 2004 Olympic Games single 10-meter competition, Tian's athletic state declined and was fired by the diving team.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">But after losing to teammate Hu Jia in the individual 10m platform competition at the 2004 Olympics, Tian Liang's athletic performance slipped and he was blown out of the diving team.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而他和女儿参加“爸爸去哪”等综艺节目，更是让他赚足了眼球。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">He and his daughter participated in variety shows such as “Where Are We Going, Dad?” which provided with him with a great deal of celebrity attention.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">And he and his daughter to participate in "Dad to where" and other variety shows, but also let him earn enough eyeballs.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">And his participation with his daughter in variety shows such as "Where's Daddy Going?" has made him even more eye-catching.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>曾经的体操黄金一代杨威、李小鹏以及陈一冰都高调参加各种综艺节目。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Yang Wei, Li Xiaopeng and Chen Yibing, once part of the golden era of gymnastics, have taken to various variety shows in a high profile manner.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Once the gymnastics gold generation Yang, Xiaopeng and yibing all high-profile participate in various variety shows.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Once the golden generation of gymnastics Yang Wei, Li Xiaopeng and Chen Yibing all participate in a variety of high-profile programs.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>值得一提的是，杨威李小鹏当时带领中国获得了2008年奥运会男团冠军，杨威更是两次拿到个人全能金牌，被称为全能王。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">It is worth mentioning that Yang Wei and Li Xiaopeng led China to the 2008 Olympic men’s team championship. Yang Wei even won the individual all-around gold twice, and was named All-around King.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">It is worth mentioning that, Yang Xiaopeng then led China to win the 2008 Olympic Games Nan Champion, Yang is two times to get a personal all-around gold, known as the Almighty King.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">It is worth mentioning that Yang Wei Li Xiaopeng led China to win the 2008 Olympic men's team championship, Yang Wei was twice won the individual all-around gold medal, known as the all-rounder.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而陈一冰则在率领中国拿到2012年奥运团体冠军的同时，也成为了吊环王。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Chen Yibing, who led the Chinese gymnastics team to an Olympic gold in 2012 also became known as the king of rings.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">While Yibing led China to the 2012-year Olympic Group championship, it also became the King of the Rings.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Chen, on the other hand, became the king of the rings while leading China to the 2012 Olympic team championship.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而在伦敦奥运会上遭遇误判痛失金牌的后，陈一冰大度的举动，也让他圈粉无数。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">After a controversial officiating decision at the London Olympics cost him a gold medal, Chen Yibing’s magnanimity won him legions of fans.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">And in the London Olympic Games suffered a miscarriage of justice after the loss of gold, yibing magnanimous move, also let him circle powder countless.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">And Chen's magnanimous move, after suffering a miscarriage of justice and a painful loss of his gold medal at the London Olympics, has left him with countless laps.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但这些运动员目前的主要精力依旧在赛场，对于综艺节目也只是如蜻蜓点水般——碰下就走。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">However, the main focus of these athletes remains firmly on the competition at this time. Appearances at variety programs are just superficial.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">But the athletes ' main energy is still on the field, and for the variety show is just like a superficial-touch off.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">But the main energy for these athletes is still in the arena, and for variety shows, it's just a touch and go.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但无论是退役还是现役运动员，能够得到娱乐圈的青睐都需要有拿得出手的成绩做保障。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Both former or current athletes must at least provide impressive performance in their field to gain the attention of the entertainment industry.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">But whether it is retired or active athletes, to be able to get the favor of the entertainment circle need to get the results to do the protection.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">But whether retired or active athletes, to be able to get the favor of the entertainment industry need to have to take the results as a guarantee.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>毕竟运动员踏入一个新的领域，无论是能力还是人脉，均是一个空白状态。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">After all, athletes enter a new field, and everything is blank, be it skill or connection.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">After all, the athlete enters a new field, whether ability or network, is a blank state.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">After all, the athlete steps into a new field, regardless of ability or human relations, is a blank state.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>即使是田亮、刘璇这样混迹娱乐圈多年的“老人”，普通观众提起他们，更多的还是想到他们在奥运会上的表现。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">For “older athletes” such as Tian Liang and Liu Xuan who frequent the celebrity circles, the general public largely remember them for their performance in the Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Even the "old man", who has been in the entertainment circle for many years, is Tian and Xuan, and the average audience is still thinking about their performance at the Olympics.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Even Tian Liang, Liu Xuan such mixed entertainment industry for many years "old people," ordinary spectators mentioned them, more still think of their performance at the Olympic Games.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>而杨威、李小鹏等新人，在综艺节目出场时的介绍，无一例外都是“奥运冠军”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">When Yang Wei, Li Xiaopeng and other newcomers are introduced at variety programs, “Olympic champion” is mentioned without exception.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">And Yang, Xiaopeng and other new, in the variety show when the introduction, no exception is "Olympic champion."</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">And Yang Wei, Li Xiaopeng and other newcomers, in the introduction of variety show appearances, without exception, are "Olympic champion."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>相比于以上几个人，宁泽涛一个游泳世锦赛冠军的名头还是略显单薄。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">When compared to the other athletes mentioned, Ning Zetao’s champion in the FINA World Championships seems somewhat less impressive in comparison.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Compared to the above several people, Ningzetao a swimming world champion's first name still slightly thin.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Compared to the above several people, Ning Zetao a swimming world championships champion's name is still slightly thin.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>更何况，相比于田亮、刘璇、杨威等人的功成身退，宁泽涛若在23岁、运动生涯稍遇挫折就急流勇退，对其形象造成的负面影响大概也是不可估量。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">When compared to Tian Liang, Liu Xuan, and Yang Wei who were able to retire after attaining glorious moments in history, if Ning Zetao were to retreat at the age of 23 after meeting a minor setback, the negative impact to his image would be quite significant.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">Moreover, compared to Tian, Xuan, Yang and other people's career, Ningzetao if in 23 years of age, a little setback in sports life Jiliuyongtui, the image of its negative impact is probably immeasurable.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">What's more, compared with Tian Liang, Liu Xuan, Yang Wei and other people's success and failure, if Ning Zetao at 23 years old, a slight setback in his sports career on the precipitous retreat, the negative impact on its image is probably immeasurable.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>毕竟，提起运动员，人们的要求都是“不求百战百胜，但求不畏艰险”，宁泽涛距离这一点还差了不少。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">When talking about athletes, the public requirement is that “constant victory is not necessary, but they should not fear difficulties”. Ning Zetao is found quite wanting in terms of this.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">After all, to mention the athletes, people's requirements are "not to seek the invincible, but for the sake of difficulties," Ningzetao distance this point is still a lot worse.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">After all, when it comes to athletes, people are asking for "not to win a hundred battles, but to be fearless," and Ning Zettao is a long way from that.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>退一万步说，宁泽涛长得帅，完全可以依靠颜值获得万千脑残粉的支持。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">On the other hand, given his dashing looks, Ning Zetao could rely on his handsome features and win support from tens of thousands of superficial fans.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">10,000 step back said, Ningzetao long handsome, can rely on the value of beauty to obtain thousands of brain residue powder support.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">Retreat 10,000 step said, Ning Zetao long handsome, can completely rely on the face value to obtain the support of thousands of brain residues.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>没点功力，只靠外表，想在娱乐圈混好，这难度不比好好训练找回应有的状态难吧。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Lack of skill, and relying on appearance alone - if you want to make it big in the entertainment business, this should not be more difficult than getting proper training and rediscovering the form you ought to have.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">No point of skill, only rely on the appearance, want to mix in the entertainment circle, this difficulty is not better than good training back to the state is difficult.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">No point of power, relying only on appearance, want to mix well in the entertainment industry, this difficulty is not better than good training to get back to the state it should be difficult.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.sl">
    <source>人生之路选择全凭个人意愿，但到底如何选择，宁泽涛心里应该有数。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.ht">Ultimately, personal journey is based upon personal will. Ning Zetao should be aware how this choice is made.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.gg">The way of life choice depends on the individual will, but in the end how to choose, Ningzetao heart should have several.</translation>
    <translation system="104_ifeng0812.news.49767201_0_zh.c6">The choice of the road of life is entirely up to the will of the individual, but in the end how to choose, Ning Zetao should have a number in mind.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
