<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据外媒报道，因跳水池池水从蓝变绿，里约奥运“绿池”事件近日备受外界关注。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">Foreign media reported that the Rio Olympics’ “green pool” incident has attracted much attention recently because of the change in the color of the water in the diving pool from blue to green.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">According to foreign media reports, because the pool pool water from blue to green, Rio Olympic "green pool" incident recently attracted outside attention.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">The Rio Olympic "Green Pool" incident has come under scrutiny in recent days as the water in the diving pool turned from blue to green, foreign media reported.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>然而，10日早晨，与跳水池相邻的水球比赛池的水也变成了绿色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">However, on the morning of the 10th, the water in the water polo pool next to the diving pool also turned green.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">On the morning of 10th, however, the water in the pool of polo matches adjacent to the diving pool turned green.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">However, water from the water polo match pool adjacent to the diving pool also turned green on the morning of Oct.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>澳大利亚水球选手赛后表示他的眼睛感到刺痛，想流眼泪。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">An Australian water polo player said that he experienced stinging pain in his eyes after the competition and felt teary.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">The Australian Water polo player after the match said his eyes were stinging and wanted to shed tears.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">The Australian water polo player said after the match that he felt a tingling in his eyes and wanted to shed tears.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>此前，里约奥运官方人员确认了池水变绿的情况，并表示池水变色是由于碱性变弱的原因，不会影响运动员身体健康。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">Officials of the Rio Olympics confirmed the pool water turning green, and expressed that the color change was a result of reduced alkalinity of the water and will not affect the physical health of the athletes.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">Earlier, the Olympic official officials confirmed the water green situation, and that the water color is due to alkaline weakening, will not affect the athlete's health.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">Earlier, Rio Olympic officials confirmed the pool turned green and said the discoloration was due to a weakening of the alkalinity and would not affect the athletes' physical health.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但是澳大利亚运动员在与日本代表队在水球池进行比赛获得胜利之后表示，眼睛感到刺痛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">However, athletes from the Australian team expressed that they felt stinging pain in their eyes after beating the Japanese team in the water polo pool.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">But Australian athletes, after winning a match with the Japanese team in the water polo pool, said their eyes were stinging.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">But Australian athletes said after their victory against the Japanese team in the water polo pool that they had a tingling in their eyes.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>最早在跳水池池水变绿后，比赛主办方在9日晚加班处理跳水池的问题，但在10日早晨发现水球池颜色也迅速发生变化。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">At first, after the water in the diving pool turned green, the tournament organizer worked over time to address the issue of the diving pool on the night of the 9th, but on the morning of the 10th, the color of the water polo pool also turned green rapidly.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">The first time in the diving pool to turn green, the competition organizers on 9th night to deal with the problem of the pool, but on the morning of 10th found that the color of water balloons also changed rapidly.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">After the water in the diving pool turned green at the earliest, the competition organizers worked overtime on the night of 9 to deal with the problem, but on the morning of 10 found that the color of the water polo pool also changed rapidly.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>澳大利亚队与日本队比赛期间，水球池的环境条件逐步恶化，但官方强调他们会在11日将两个泳池的水质恢复到原来的颜色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">During the competition between the Australian and Japanese teams, conditions and environment of the water polo pool continued to worsen. However, officials emphasized that they will restore the two swimming pools to their original quality and color on the 11th.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">The environmental conditions of the water polo pool deteriorated gradually during the Australian and Japanese competitions, but officials stressed that they would revert to the original colours of the two swimming pools on 11th.</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">Environmental conditions in the water polo pools deteriorated during the Australian team's match against Japan, but officials stressed they would return the water quality in both pools to its original colour on Nov.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>里约奥运会发言人安德拉达(Mario Andrada)表示：“昨天午后，跳水池中的水碱性程度首先变弱。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">Mario Andrada, the spokesman of Rio Olympic Games said:" the alkaline level of the diving pool decreased from yesterday afternoon."</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">"Yesterday afternoon, the degree of water alkalinity in the plunge pool was first weakened," said Mario Andrada, a spokeswoman for the Andrada Olympic Games. ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">"The water in the diving pool was the first to weaken in alkalinity yesterday afternoon," Rio Olympic spokesman Mario Andrada said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“我们了解了一系列可能会引发池水变色的原因以及水质的含碱度。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">“We learned about a number of factors that may cause the water to change in terms of color as well as water quality and alkalinity.”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">"We understand a range of causes and alkalinity of water quality that may cause discoloration of the pool," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">"We learned about a range of possible causes of pool water discoloration and the alkalinity of the water quality," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>水上运动中心对水质进行了一系列检测，数百名潜水员及游泳者使用了泳池可以确定水质条件达到标准。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">The water sports center performed a series of tests on water quality. Several hundred divers and swimmers who used the pool can also testify that the water quality has reached the required standards.”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">A series of tests on water quality were conducted at the Aquatics Centre, with hundreds of divers and swimmers using the pool to determine the water quality standards. ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">The water sports centre has carried out a series of tests and hundreds of divers and swimmers have used the pool to make sure the conditions are up to standard.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这些天我们一直走正常程序，但我们可能忽略了运动员越多可能对水质的带来影响。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">“We have been operating according to normal procedures these days, but we may have neglected the impact that more athletes may have on the quality of water.”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">"These days we have been going through normal procedures, but we may have overlooked the impact that the more athletes may have on water quality." ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">"We've been following normal procedures these days, but we may have overlooked the impact more athletes could have on water quality," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“但水颜色发生变化肯定对身体健康，特别是对运动员是没有影响的。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">“Although the color of the water has changed, it will definitely not affect one’s health, especially as regards athletes.”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">"But the change in the color of the water is certainly not affecting the physical health, especially the athlete." ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">"But a change in the colour of the water certainly has no effect on health, especially for athletes," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“这个独立的团队确认了我们的评估，也肯定了我们将泳池恢复正常颜色及正常的化学状态所采取的措施。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">“This independent team verified our assessments and acknowledged the measures that we took to restore the swimming pool to its original color and normal chemical state.”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">"The independent team confirmed our assessment and affirmed the steps we took to restore the pool to normal color and normal chemical status," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">"This independent team confirmed our assessment and confirmed the steps we have taken to restore the pool to its normal colour and chemical condition," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“我们本来希望早晨泳池就能恢复正常颜色，但是由于下雨所以恢复的速度受到了影响。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.ht">“We had hoped that the pool would return to its normal color in the morning, but rain had affected the pace of restoration.”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.gg">"We had hoped that the morning pool would return to normal colours, but the speed of recovery was affected by the rain," he said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="046_ifeng0812.news.49765934_0_zh.c6">"We had hoped that the pool would return to normal color in the morning, but the pace of recovery was affected by the rain," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
