<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>“身中数弹”的6岁 Mahaj Brown 在费城枪击案中幸免</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">“Riddled with bullets”, six-year-old Mahaj Brown survives Philadelphia shooting</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">6-year-old Mahaj Brown was spared in the Philadelphia shootings.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">'Several Shot '6-year-old Mahaj Brown survives Philadelphia shooting</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>警方称，一名六岁的男孩在费城遭到枪击，这也是本周该市第二个中枪的六岁儿童。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Police claimed that a six-year-old boy was shot in Philadelphia, the second time a six-year-old child was shot in the city this week.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Police say a six-year-old boy was shot in Philadelphia, a six-year-old child in the city's second shot this week.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">A six-year-old boy was shot in Philadelphia, the second six-year-old to be shot in the city this week, police said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>孩子的祖父母向 CBS Philadelphia 证实，遭枪击的孩子是 Mahaj Brown。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">The grandparents of the child proved to CBS Philadelphia that the child who was shot was Mahaj Brown.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">The child's grandparents confirmed to CBS Philadelphia that the child being shot was Mahaj Brown.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">The children's grandparents confirmed to CBS Philadelphia that the child who was shot was Mahaj Brown.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>他们说，Brown 的腹股沟、腿、胳膊和腹部等部位有多处枪伤，但是孩子在送医途中是清醒的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">They say that multiple gunshot wounds were found on Brown’s groin, legs, arms, abdomen, and other parts of his body, but the child remained conscious on the way to the hospital.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Brown's groin, legs, arms and abdomen have multiple gunshot wounds, they say, but the child is awake on the way to the hospital.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">Brown had multiple gunshot wounds to his groin, leg, arm and stomach, they said, but the child was conscious on the way to the hospital.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>“他遭了不少罪，小小的身体被子弹打得千疮百孔，”他的祖母 Delores Melendez 对电视台说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">“He was hit very badly. His small body was riddled with bullets,” Delores Melendez, his grandmother, told the television station.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">"He's had a lot of sins and his little body was riddled with bullets," his grandmother Delores Melendez told the television.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">"He suffered a lot, his tiny body was riddled with bullets," his grandmother, Delores Melendez, told the station.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>我简直不敢相信。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">I couldn’t believe my eyes.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">I can't believe it.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">I couldn't believe it.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>这名男孩在医院的情况很危急，已经接受了多次手术。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">The boy is in critical condition at the hospital and has received multiple operations.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">The boy was in a critical condition at the hospital and had been undergoing several surgeries.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">The boy is in a critical condition in hospital and has undergone multiple surgeries.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>他的家人告诉电视台说，孩子有望康复。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">His family told the TV station that the child is expected to recover.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">His family told the TV station that children are expected to recover.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">His family told the station that the child was expected to recover.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>他原本要开始在当地一所小学读一年级了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">He was supposed to enroll in a local elementary school as a grade 1 student.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">He was supposed to start his first grade in a local primary school.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">He was to have started first grade at a local elementary school.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>Brown 是 Germantown 地区遭到枪击的四人之一。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Brown is one of the four shooting victims in Germantown.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Brown is one of four people who were shot in the Germantown area.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">Brown was one of four people who were shot in the Germantown area.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>其他遭到枪击的三人中，两人29岁，一人32岁。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Of the other three who were shot, two were 29 years old, and one, 32.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Of the other three people who were shot, two were 29 years old and one 32 years old.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">Two of the other three people who were shot were 29 years old and one was 32 years old.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>据 CBS Philadelphia 称，其中一名29岁的受害者情况危急；另两名受害者情况稳定。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">According to CBS Philadelphia, a 29-year-old victim is in critical condition, while another two victims are in stable condition.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">According to CBS Philadelphia, one of the 29-year-old victims was in critical condition and two other victims were in stable condition.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">According to CBS Philadelphia, one of the victims, aged 29, is in a critical condition; the other two victims are in stable condition.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>电视台称，这名孩子与那名29岁的情况危急的受害者是在汽车前座上被发现的。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">The television station claimed that the child and the 29-year old victim, currently in critical conditions, were found at the front seat of the vehicle.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Television said the child and the 29-year-old victim was found in the front seat of the car.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">The child was found in the front seat of the car with the 29-year-old victim in critical condition, the station said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>另两名受害者不在车上，警方正在调查是否受伤人员中就有枪手。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">The two other victims are not in the car. The police is investigating whether the wounded include the gunman.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">The other two were not in the car and the police were investigating whether the gunman was among the injured.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">Two other victims were not in the vehicle and police are investigating whether the gunman was among those injured.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>调查人员告诉 CBS Philadelphia，看起来像是多名枪手交火。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Investigators told CBS Philadelphia that it seems like a shooting incident involving multiple armed persons.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Investigators told CBS Philadelphia that it looked like multiple gunmen had exchanged fire.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">Investigators told CBS Philadelphia that it looked like multiple gunmen exchanged gunfire.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>现场发现了不少攻击性武器的弹壳，由此可推断他们使用的是不同的攻击性武器。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Numerous assault weapon cartridges were found at the scene. It could be inferred therefore, that they had used different assault weapons.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Many of the shells of offensive weapons were found at the scene, which could be inferred that they were using different offensive weapons.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">A number of shell casings of offensive weapons were found at the scene, from which it can be inferred that they were using different offensive weapons.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>由此判断，这无疑是一场持续战。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">On this basis, this will undoubtedly be a long-drawn-out conflict.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">Judging from this, this is undoubtedly a continuous war.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">Judging from this, there is no doubt that this is an ongoing battle.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>街道两边的人行道上都有弹壳。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Cartridges were found on the sidewalks on both sides of the road.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">There are shells on the sidewalks on both sides of the street.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">There were shell casings on the sidewalks on both sides of the street.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>“所以，由此可见当时现场有多名武装人员处于激战状态，”费城警察局长Anthony Ginaldi 对电视台说。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">“Hence, we can see that there were multiple armed personnel engaged in intense battle at the site,” Anthony Ginaldi, Police Captain of Philadelphia, told the television station.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">"Therefore, it can be seen that at that time there were many armed men in a state of fierce fighting," Philadelphia Police Commissioner Anthony Ginaldi told television.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">"So, this shows that there were a number of armed men on the scene at the time in a state of heavy fighting," Philadelphia Police Chief Anthony Ginaldi told the station.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>该地区有不少房屋及车辆受损。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">Many houses and vehicles were damaged in this region.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">A number of buildings and vehicles have been damaged in the area.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">A number of homes and vehicles were damaged in the area.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>尚未实行抓捕行动，据说，警察在调看监控录像。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">The arrest has yet to be carried out. The police are reportedly looking at the surveillance video.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">No arrests have been made, and police are said to be watching surveillance footage.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">No arrests have been made and police are said to be looking at surveillance video.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>周二，还有一名六岁儿童（女孩），在位于 West Oak Lane 社区的家门口玩耍时，被流弹射中胳膊。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">On Tuesday, a 6-year old child (a girl) was hit by a stray bullet on her arm while playing at the doorsteps of her home in the West Oak Lane community.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">In Tuesday, a six-year-old child (girl) was shot in the arm by a stray bullet while playing at the doorstep of the Oak Lane community in West.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">On Tuesday, another six-year-old, a girl, was playing outside her home in the West Oak Lane neighborhood when she was shot in the arm by a stray bullet.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="115_cbsnews.146310_en.sl">
    <source>她目前正在康复，警察仍在追捕嫌犯。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.ht">She is currently recovering. The police is still hunting for the suspect.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.gg">She is recovering and the police are still chasing suspects.</translation>
    <translation system="115_cbsnews.146310_en.c6">She is now recovering and police are still hunting for the suspect.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
