<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>洛杉矶中央图书馆的惊艳结构先睹为快</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">Take a look of the astounding architecture of the Los Angeles Central Library</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">The stunning structure of the Los Angeles Central Library</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">A sneak peek at the stunning architecture of the Los Angeles Central Library</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>美国建筑史学家学会南加利福尼亚洲分会与新书《洛杉矶中央博物馆：其艺术与建筑历史》的作者阿诺·斯瓦茨曼和史蒂芬·吉举办了一场沙龙。观众们可通过此次活动进一步了解市中心中央图书馆的历史。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">A salon will be hosted by Southern California Branch of Society of Architectural Historians and the co-authors of Los Angles Central Museum: Art and Architectural History, Arnold Schwarzman and Stephen Gee. It will deliver more knowledge of the Central Library to the participants.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">The Southern California branch of the American Institute of Architectural Historians has held a salon with 阿诺·斯瓦茨曼 and 史蒂芬·吉, author of the Los Angeles Central Museum: its art and architectural history. Through this event, viewers can learn more about the history of Central Library in the city centre.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">The Southern California chapter of the American Society of Architectural Historians and the authors of a new book, "Los Angeles Central Museum: Its Art and Architectural History," Arnold Schwartzman and Steven Gee, hosted a salon at which viewers learned more about the history of the Central Library in the city center.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>吉和斯瓦茨曼将讨论并分享1926年贝特伦·古德西的设计图片以及1933年哈迪・霍尔兹曼・弗夫尔事务所的修复与扩建图片。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">Gee and Schwarzman will discuss and share images of design by Bertram Goodhue in 1926 and restoration and expansion of  Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Associates in 1933.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">Gillette and Swatzman will discuss and share images of the 1926 贝特伦·古德西 Design and the restoration and expansion of the 哈迪·霍尔兹曼·弗夫尔 office in 1933.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">Guy and Swartzman will discuss and share the design of Bertram Goodsey in 1926 and the restoration and expansion of the Hardy Holzman Favre office in 1933.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>此次沙龙的时间为：8月21日下午2点至4点，地点：Salle Moderne，Art Deco Southwestern School of Law（前Bullocks Wilshire)，3050 Wilshire Blvd。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">The salon hours are: 2pm to 4pm, August 21. Address: Salle Moderne, Art Deco Southwestern School of Law (formerly Bullocks Wilshire), 3050 Wilshire Blvd.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">The salon's time is: August 21 2 o'clock in the afternoon to 4 points, location: Salle Moderne, Art Deco Southwestern School of the (former Bullocks Wilshire), $number Wilshire Blvd.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">The salon will be held from 2 to 4 p.m. on 21 August at Salle Modern, Art Deco Southern School of Law (formerly Bullocks Wilshire), 3050 Wilshire Blvd.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>参加者可以参观中央大厅、时代展室、仙人掌休息室和茶室。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">Visitors can visit the venues of the central hall, the history exhibit, the cactus lounge, and the tea lounge.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">Participants can visit the central hall, the time room, the Cactus Lounge and the teahouse.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">Participants can visit the Central Lobby, the Times Room, the Cactus Lounge and the Tea Room.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>需要提前订票；SAHSCC会员：15美元；非会员：25美元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">Advance ticket reservation required; SAHSCC members: US$15; non-members: US$25.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">Advance booking is required; SAHSCC member: USD 15; Non-member: $25.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">Advance reservations are required; SAHSCC members: $15; non-members: $25.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>DTLA的开放式工厂阁楼进行了一次舒适的改造。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">A comfortable makeover was provided to the open factory building design of DTLA.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">DTLA's Open factory loft has a comfortable makeover.</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">DTLA's open-plan factory loft has undergone a comfortable makeover.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="015_latimes.173028_en.sl">
    <source>庆祝洛杉矶中央图书馆90周年以及新书的发售</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.ht">Celebrating the 90th anniversary of the Los Angeles Central Library and sale of new book</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.gg">Celebrating the 90 anniversary of the Los Angeles Central Library and the sale of new books</translation>
    <translation system="015_latimes.173028_en.c6">Celebrating the 90th anniversary of the Los Angeles Central Library and the release of new books</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
