<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>作为2014年的首轮12号新秀，萨里奇将在下赛季正式登陆NBA，并加盟费城76人队。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">As the 12th new player in the first round of 2014, Šarić will be formally entering the NBA with the Philadelphia 76ers in the next season.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">As the first round of the 2014 rookie 12th, Saric will be officially landed in the NBA next season and join the Philadelphia team.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">A rookie in the first round of 12 in 2014, Saric will officially land in the NBA next season and join the Philadelphia 76ers.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>萨里奇身为一个年轻的欧洲球员，很多球迷对他并不是很了解，但是通过本届奥运会，相信萨里奇的表现给人们留下了很深的印象。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">As a young European basketball player, many fans were unfamiliar with Šarić but after this Olympic Games, it is believed that his performance would leave an indelible impression on everyone.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">Saric as a young European player, many fans are not very familiar with him, but through the Olympic Games, I believe that Saric's performance has left a deep impression on people.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">As a young European player, many fans do not know him very well, but through this Olympic Games, it is believed that Saric's performance has left a deep impression.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>上一场克罗地亚险胜西班牙的比赛，萨里奇在最后时刻成功封盖掉保罗-加索尔试图将比赛拖入加时的篮下进攻。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">In last match where Croatia narrowly defeated Spain, Šarić successfully blocked Pau Gasol’s attempt at the last minute, taking the match into an overtime shootout.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">At the last moment, Saric successfully sealed off Pau Gasol in an attempt to pull the game into overtime after a Croatia victory over Spain.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">The last time Croatia had a narrow victory over Spain, Saric managed to seal off Pau Gasol's last-minute attempt to drag the game into the basket.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>近日，76人队主帅布雷特-布朗给予萨里奇很高的评价，这位马刺系主帅认为他在萨里奇看到了年轻时的马努-吉诺比利的影子。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">Brett Brown, head coach of the 76ers, recently gave a great review for Šarić. The coach who had served the Spurs before believed that he saw in Šarić the shadow of a younger Manu Ginóbili.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">Recently, the 76-person team coach Brett Brown gave Saric a high rating, the Spurs manager believes he saw in Saric young Manu-Gino's shadow.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">76ers coach Brett Brown recently spoke highly of Saric, the Spurs department manager who believes he saw the shadow of Manu Ginobili in his youth.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>很显然，萨里奇已经展现出了他的天赋，并且让76人对他充满期待。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">Clearly, Šarić has already displayed his gift, and the 76ers are expecting many things from him.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">Obviously, Saric has shown his talent and has made 76 of people look forward to him.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">It's clear that Saric has shown his talent and has 76 people looking forward to him.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>克罗地亚在本届奥运会上的前两场比赛，萨里奇一共得到24分、17个篮板和12次助攻。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">In Croatia’s first two matches at the Olympic Games, Šarić had a total of 24 points, 17 rebounds and 12 assists.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">Croatia scored 24 points, 17 rebounds and 12 assists in the first two games of the Saric.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">Croatia scored 24 points, 17 rebounds and 12 assists in its first two games at the Olympics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>上半场，萨里奇展现出了他在场上拉开空间的能力，通过与队友的挡拆之后，他在三分线外能命中投篮。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">In the first half of the game, Šarić demonstrated his ability to capitalize on isolation. Once his teammates sets a screen, he would be able to score a shot outside the 3-point line.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">In the first half, Saric showed his ability to open up space on the pitch, and he hit the ball outside the three-point line after he pulled his teammates off.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">In the first half, Saric showed his ability to open up space on the field, hitting shots from beyond the three-point line after breaking up with his teammates.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>虽然目前这支76人的内线囤积了不少有天赋的年轻球员，但是他们并不具备萨里奇的外线能力。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">Although the 76ers has enough talent and young insiders, they are lack of the outline performance as good as Saric.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">Although the 76-person insider is hoarding many talented young players, they do not have the ability to saric outside the perimeter.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">The 76ers currently have plenty of talented young players on the inside, but they don't have Saric's outside expertise.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>从盖帽到发动长传快攻并完成助攻，当今NBA赛场上能做到这点的内线球员屈指可数。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">Few insider player is able to block, start long-pass and fast-break and assist in the current NBA arena.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">From the CAP to the launch of the long break and assists, there are only a handful of players in the NBA that can do it today.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">From blocked shots to long passing fast breaks and assists, there are only a handful of infielders who can do that in the NBA today.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.sl">
    <source>自从本届奥运会开始以来，萨里奇在3场比赛里场均得到13分、8个篮板和5次助攻，表现堪称全面。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.ht">Since the beginning of this Olympics, Šarić achieved 13 points, 8 rebounds, and 5 assists in 3 games, giving a well-rounded performance.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.gg">Since the beginning of the Olympic Games, Saric in 3 games have won 13 points, 8 rebounds and 5 assists, performance is comprehensive.</translation>
    <translation system="010_sina0812.sports.doc-ifxuxnak0000530_zh.c6">Since the start of the Games, Saric has averaged 13 points, eight rebounds and five assists in three games, a well-rounded performance.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
