<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>犹太电影制片人批评柏林酒店按照阿拉伯客户的“要求”删除以色列电话代码 —— 路透社新闻</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Jewish filmmaker criticizes Berlin hotel for removing Israel’s dial code upon “request” by an Arab guest - Reuters</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Jewish film producer criticizes Berlin hotels to delete Israeli phone codes according to Arab customers ' requirements-Reuters News</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Jewish filmmakers criticise Berlin hotel for removing Israeli phone code as "requested" by Arab customers - Reuters News</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>一位有着犹太血统的法国电影制片人向媒体透露，位于柏林的凯宾斯基酒店没有列出以色列的电话代码，并且酒店员工表示这是按照阿拉伯客户的“要求”，这引发了舆论一片哗然。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">A French filmmaker of Jewish origin told the media that the Kempinski Hotel in Berlin did not list Israel’s dial code, and a hotel employee said that this was in accordance with a “request” made by an Arab customer. This triggered a public outcry.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">A French filmmaker with Jewish ancestry told the press that the Kempinski Hotel in Berlin did not list Israel's phone codes and that the hotel staff said it was "demanded" by Arab customers, sparking a public outcry.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">A French filmmaker with Jewish roots revealed to the media that the Kempinski Hotel in Berlin did not list the Israeli phone code, and that the hotel staff said it was in accordance with the "requirements" of Arab customers, sparking a public outcry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>犹太人大屠杀纪录片《浩劫》的作者克劳德·朗兹曼表达了他对凯宾斯基酒店的失望，并且在德国《法兰克福汇报》上发表了一封公开信。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Claude Lanzmann, the author of Shoah, a documentary film about the Jewish Holocaust, expressed his disappointment in Kempinski hotel and wrote an open letter that was posted on the German newspaper Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">克劳德·朗兹曼, author of the Holocaust documentary Holocaust, expressed his disappointment with the Kempinski Hotel and published an open letter in Germany's Frankfurt report.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Claude Lanzmann, author of the Holocaust documentary The Holocaust, expressed his disappointment at the Kempinski Hotel and published an open letter in Frankfurt, Germany.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>在最近入住期间，朗兹曼想在酒店提供的电话代码列表上找到以色列。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">When he last checked-in, Lanzmann wanted to find Israel in the list of telephone dialing codes provided by the hotel.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">During the recent stay, Lanzman wanted to find Israel on the list of phone codes provided by the hotel.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">During his most recent stay, Lanzmann wanted to find Israel on the list of phone codes provided by the hotel.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>但以色列没有在客人可以直接从房间通话的国家之列。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">But Israel is not in the country list available for in-room direct dialing</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">But Israel does not have a list of countries where guests can speak directly from the room.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">But Israel is not among the countries where guests can call directly from their rooms.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>以色列居然在2016年德国的首都柏林消失了？</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">How did Israel disappeared from the 2016 German capital of Berlin?</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Did Israel disappear in 2016 in Berlin, the capital of Germany?</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Israel actually disappeared in Berlin, Germany's capital, in 2016?</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>朗兹曼写道。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Lanzmann wrote.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Lanzman wrote.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Lanzmann wrote.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>取而代之的是，客人可以通过凯宾斯基酒店的呼叫中心拨打以色列电话。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">In replacement, guests can now use the Kempinski Hotel call center to make a call to Israel.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Instead, guests can call Israel via the Kempinski Hotel's call center.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Instead, guests can call Israel through the Kempinski Hotel's call center.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>为了寻求解释，这位电影制片人询问了酒店的前台。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">To search for an explanation, this film producer asked the hotel receptionist.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">To seek an explanation, the filmmaker asked the hotel's front desk.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">In search of an explanation, the filmmaker asked the hotel's front desk.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>朗兹曼在信中表示，他在前台得到的回答“令他感到震惊”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Lanzmann wrote in the letter that the answer he got at the front desk was " shocking".</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">In his letter, Lanzman said he was "shocked" by the answer he received at the reception desk.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">In his letter, Mr Lanzman said he was "shocked" by the response he received at the front desk.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>酒店人员表示，这是“凯宾斯基酒店管理层刻意作出的决定”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Hotel staff expressed that “this was a deliberate decision made by the management of Kempinski Hotel”.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Hotel staff said it was "a deliberate decision by Kempinski Hotel management."</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Hotel staff said it was a "deliberate decision by the management of the Kempinski Hotel."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>而这么做的理由更是让这位电影制片人感到愤怒。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">The reason for doing that was to infuriate the filmmaker.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">The reason for this is to make the filmmaker angry.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">And the reason for doing so has made the filmmaker angry.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>朗兹曼引用了这名员工的原话：我们的大部分客人都是阿拉伯人，他们要求删除以色列的代码。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Lanzmann quoted what this employee said, “The majority of our guests are Arabs and they demanded Israel’s code to be deleted.”</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Lanzman quotes the employee as saying: Most of our guests are Arabs and they want to delete the Israeli code. ”</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Langzman quoted the employee as saying: "Most of our guests are Arabs and they are demanding that the Israeli code be removed."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>根据《南德日报》的报道，以色列驻德国大使雅科夫·哈达斯·汉德尔斯曼将这件事称为“奇耻大辱”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">According to the Süddeutsche Zeitung, the Israeli ambassador to Germany, Yakov Hadas-Handelsman, treated this event as a “great shame”.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Israel's ambassador to Germany, 雅科夫·哈达斯·汉德尔斯曼, described the incident as "a disgrace", according to the daily newspaper.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">According to the South German Daily News, Israel's ambassador to Germany, Yakov Haddas Handelsmann, called the incident "an outrage."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>得知这一事件，我们感到大吃一惊。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">We were shocked when we found out about this.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">We were surprised to learn of the incident.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">We were surprised to learn about the incident.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>这件事本身就是一个巨大的耻辱。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">This is a huge shame in itself.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">The matter itself is a huge disgrace.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">This in itself is a great shame.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>而发生在德国和那家连锁酒店更是丢人现眼。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">The incident that occurred in Germany and the franchise hotel was shameless.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">In Germany and that chain hotel is a disgrace.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">And what happened in Germany and the hotel chain was even more humiliating.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>这件事无需任何解释。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">This matter does not require further explanations.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">There is no need to explain this matter.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">There is no need for any explanation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>“我们希望该酒店能够得出正确的结论，”该官员表示。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">“We hope that this Hotel can provide an accurate conclusion,” the official expressed.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">"We hope the hotel can draw the right conclusions," the official said.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">"We hope that the hotel will come to the right conclusion," the official said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>这一事件在网上引发了热议，大家都认为这是一桩丑闻。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">This matter triggered an intense debate on the Internet. Everyone thought it was scandalous.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">The incident sparked a heated debate online, and everyone thought it was a scandal.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">The incident sparked a heated debate online and everyone thought it was a scandal.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>有人认为凯宾斯基酒店简直是为了满足阿拉伯客户的要求而“卑躬屈膝”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Some people felt that the Kempinski Hotel “groveled” just to keep the Arab customer happy.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Some people think that Kempinski hotel is simply to meet the requirements of Arab customers and "grovel."</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Some see the Kempinski hotel as simply "kowtowing" to meet the demands of Arab customers.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>另一个帖子直指酒店“真不要脸”，并且指出这家位于著名的库达姆大街的大街就在一座犹太教会堂附近。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Another post said that the hotel is “shameless” and pointed out that the famous Kurfürstendamm that the establishment was located is next to a synagogue.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">Another post points to the hotel's "really shameless face", pointing out that the main street in the famous Kurfuerstendamm Street is near a synagogue.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">Another post pointed to the hotel as "shameless" and pointed out that the main street on the famous Kudam Street is near a synagogue.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>据《明镜周刊》的报道，酒店很快对所有指控予以澄清，声称一切都是“疏忽”并且向朗兹曼表示“歉意”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Der Spiegel reported that the hotel swiftly clarified all accusations. It claimed that it was all due to “negligence”, and “apologized” to Lanzmann.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">The hotel quickly clarified all charges, claiming that everything was "negligent" and apologized to Lanzman, according to the Der Spiegel report.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">According to Der Spiegel, the hotel was quick to clarify all the allegations, claiming that everything was "negligent" and offering "apologies" to Lanzmann.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>《南德日报》引用了凯宾斯基代表的话：“从来没有下达过将以色列从快速拨号列表中删除的直接命令”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">Süddeutsche Zeitung quoted a Kempinski representative as saying, “There was never a direct order to remove Israel from the fast dial list.”</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">"Never issued a direct command to remove Israel from the speed dial list," the newspaper quoted the Kempinski representative as saying.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">The Nande Daily News quoted Kempinski's representative as saying: "There has never been a direct order to remove Israel from the speed dial list."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="016_rt.com.45940_en.sl">
    <source>该报还表示以色列代码已加入到列表中。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.ht">This paper also claimed that the dial code of Israel has been added to the list.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.gg">The newspaper said the Israeli code was added to the list.</translation>
    <translation system="016_rt.com.45940_en.c6">The newspaper also said the Israeli code had been added to the list.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
