<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.sl">
    <source>现年63岁的流浪者韩某与另一流浪汉肖某酒后发生争执，遂持刀将其扎死。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.ht">Han, a 63-year old homeless individual, began arguing with Xiao, another homeless individual, and then drew a blade to stab the latter to death.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.gg">The 63-year-old homeless man, South Korea, and another tramp Shaw, a drunken quarrel, then holding a knife to tie it to death.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.c6">Rangers Han, 63, had a drunken argument with another tramp Xiao and stabbed him to death with a knife.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.sl">
    <source>韩某称案发前他和流浪汉肖某都住在东城区一胡同内的地上，两人相距20多米。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.ht">Han said that prior to the incident, he and the homeless person Xiao lived at the same alley in Dongcheng District. They were only 20 meters from each other.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.gg">Han said that before the murder he and Tramp Shaw lived in a hutong in the Dongcheng district of the ground, the two people are 20 meters apart.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.c6">Han said before the crime he and tramp Xiao are living in an alley in the Dongcheng District on the ground, the two are more than 20 meters apart.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.sl">
    <source>韩某称，案发当天，他俩被朋友叫去一起喝酒，两人在吃饭时和饭后曾两次发生争执。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.ht">Han said that during the day of the incident, both of them were invited by a friend for a drink. The two argued twice during the meal and after the meal.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.gg">Han said that the day of the crime, they were friends called to drink together, two people at the dinner and after dinner two times have a quarrel.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.c6">Han claimed that on the day of the crime, they were called by friends to drink together, and that the two men had argued twice during and after dinner.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.sl">
    <source>韩某称，他怕肖某打他，就从垃圾堆捡来一把水果刀，将其扎死。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.ht">Han said he was afraid that Xiao might hit him, so he picked up a paring knife and stabbed him to death.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.gg">Han said that he was afraid of Shaw hit him, from the garbage heap to pick up a fruit knife, will be stabbed to death.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.c6">Han claimed he was afraid Xiao would hit him, so he picked up a fruit knife from the rubbish heap and stabbed him to death.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.sl">
    <source>庭上，被害人家属要求韩某赔偿丧葬费、死亡赔偿金等共计53万余元。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.ht">During the court proceedings, the grieving family members demanded Han to pay a compensation amounting to over 530,000 RMB for the burial fees and death of the victim.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.gg">In court, the victims ' families demanded a total of 530,000 yuan for the funeral expenses and death compensation.</translation>
    <translation system="031_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxhas1624320_zh.c6">The court, the victim's family asked Han to compensation for funeral expenses, death compensation, etc., a total of more than 530,000 yuan.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
