<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.sl">
    <source>51Talk无忧英语被认为在构建在线教育行业生态圈方面具有里程碑的意义。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.ht">51Talk is believed to have landmark significance in the area of building an online education industry ecosphere.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.gg">51Talk worry-free English is considered to be a milestone in building an online education industry ecosystem.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.c6">51Talk worry-free English is considered a milestone in building an online education industry ecosystem.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.sl">
    <source>CEO黄佳佳表示，将全球最佳的学习资源带给中国的孩子们是他们未来五年的战略。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.ht">CEO Huang Jiajia expressed that their strategy for the next 5 years is to provide the world’s best learning materials to the children in China.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.gg">CEO Huang Jiajia says that bringing the world's best learning resources to China's children is their strategy for the next five years.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.c6">CEO Huang Jiajia says bringing the world's best learning resources to children in China is their strategy for the next five years.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据了解，“51Talk的最大优势就在于能够满足不同年龄段不同需求的用户。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.ht">According to information, “The biggest advantage of 51Talk lies in its ability to cater to the different requirements of users of different age groups.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.gg">It is understood that "the biggest advantage of 51Talk is to meet different age groups of different needs of users."</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.c6">It is understood that "51Talk's greatest strength lies in being able to meet the needs of users of different age groups.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.sl">
    <source>首席运营官张礼明则表示，将全球优质外教师资和服务与学生端相连，家长们再也不用舟车劳顿，将宝贵的时间用于接送孩子了。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.ht">Chief Operating Officer Zhang Liming said however that by linking global quality foreign teachers and services with students, parents will no longer have to tire themselves and waste precious time picking up and dropping off their children.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.gg">Chief operating Officer Zhang Liming said that the global quality of foreign teachers and services to connect with students, parents no longer need to travel, the precious time for the transfer of children.</translation>
    <translation system="142_ifeng0812.news.49767414_0_zh.c6">Zhang Liming, chief operating officer, said that by connecting the world's top quality foreign teachers and services to their students, parents would no longer have to worry about spending precious time picking up and dropping off their children.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
