<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月11日，首届锦州湿地旅游文化节在锦州东方华地城“鹤泉湖”畔启幕。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.ht">On August 11, the inaugural Jinzhou Wetlands Tourism and Cultural Festival opened on the banks of “Hequan Lake” at Jinzhou Dongfang Huadi City.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.gg">August 11, the first Jinzhou Wetland Tourism Culture Festival in Jinzhou Oriental City, "Crane Spring Lake," the curtain.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.c6">On August 11, the first Jinzhou Wetland Tourism and Culture Festival kicks off on the banks of Hequan Lake in the eastern Chinese city of Jinzhou.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.sl">
    <source>从2014年起，旅游产业创造的收入，占锦州市GDP10%；2015年更是达到了11.3%。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.ht">Since 2014, the revenue generated by the tourism industry made up 10% of the GDP of Jinzhou City. By 2015, this figure has increased to 11.3%.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.gg">From 2014 onwards, the tourism industry created income, accounting for Jinzhou GDP; 2015 was 11.3%.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.c6">Since 2014, the tourism industry has generated 10% of Jinzhou's GDP, and 11.3% in 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.sl">
    <source>东方华地城湿地温泉旅游区，地处锦州市凌海大有经济区滨海公路凌海段1号，距离锦州市区70公里，距离凌海市区50公里，距离盘锦市70公里。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.ht">The wetlands hot spring recreation area at Dongfang Huadi City is located at No. 1, Linghai Section, Binghai Road, Linghai Dayou Economic Area, Jinzhou City, and is only 70 kilometers away from Jinzhou City, 50 kilometers away from Linghai City, and 70 kilometers from Panjin City.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.gg">East China city wetland Hot spring tourist area, is located in Jinzhou Ling Great economic Zone Binhai Highway Ling section 1th, from Jinzhou City 70 kilometers away from the Ling urban area 50 kilometers, distance Panjin 70 kilometers.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.c6">Dongfang Huadicheng Wetland Hot Spring Tourism Zone, located in Jinzhou City, Linghai Economic Zone, Binhai Road, Linghai Section 1, 70 kilometers away from Jinzhou City, 50 kilometers away from Linghai City, 70 kilometers away from Panjin City.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.sl">
    <source>景区有室内温泉占地3000平方米，室外温泉占地4600平方米。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.ht">The attraction area is provided with 3,000 square meters of indoor hot springs and 4,600 square meters of outdoor hot springs.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.gg">Scenic area has indoor hot springs covers an area of 3000 square meters, outdoor hot springs covers an area of 4600 square meters.</translation>
    <translation system="049_ifeng0812.news.49765212_0_zh.c6">Scenic area has indoor hot spring covers an area of 3,000 square meters, outdoor hot spring covers an area of 4,600 square meters.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
