<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>国会小组表示，军事官员扭曲了ISIS的情报</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">House panel says military officers distorted ISIS intelligence</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Congressional panel says military officials distort ISIS's intelligence</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Congressional panel says military officials distorted ISIS intelligence</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>一个国会小组在周四发布的报告中指出，美国中央司令部的官员更改了情报报告，将在伊拉克和叙利亚对抗伊斯兰国的战争情况描述得比实际情况更为乐观。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">A report issued by a congressional panel on Thursday revealed that US Central Command officials altered intelligence reports to portray a more optimistic picture of the war against the Islamic State in Iraq and Syria than events on the ground warranted.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">A congressional team in a report released in Thursday noted that U.S. Central Command officials have changed intelligence reports, describing the war situation in Iraq and Syria against Islamic countries as more optimistic than the actual situation.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">In a report released Thursday, a congressional panel noted that officials at U.S. Central Command changed intelligence reports to describe the war against ISIS in Iraq and Syria as more optimistic than it actually was.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>这份中期报告来自一个由众议院军事委员会、情报委员会和众议院拨款委员会国防分委会共和党主席组建的专项工作小组。报告称，中央司令部情报分析员存在“广泛的不满”，这些分析员表示上级正在篡改他们对于美国与伊斯兰国之战的评估。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">This mid-term report is prepared by a special task force established by the United States House Committee on Armed Services, House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, and Republication Party chairperson of the House Appropriations Defense Subcommittee. The report claimed that “displeasure is common” amongst intelligence analysts of the United States Central Command. These analysts expressed that their superiors are changing their assessments regarding the war between the United States and the Islamic State.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The interim report comes from a special working group organized by the House Armed Services Committee, the Intelligence Commission and the Republican chairman of the House Appropriations Committee, the Defence Subcommittee. The report said there was "widespread dissatisfaction" among central Command intelligence analysts, who said their superiors were tampering with their assessment of the war between the United States and the Islamic nation.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The interim report, from a special working group formed by the Republican chairmen of the House Armed Services Committee, the Intelligence Committee and the House Appropriations Committee's defense subcommittee, said there was "widespread dissatisfaction" among Central Command intelligence analysts who said their superiors were tampering with their assessment of the US war against Islamic State.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>位于佛罗里达州坦帕的中央司令部 (Centcom) 是负责监管美国在中东和中亚地区的军事行动的军事总部。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">The United States Central Command (Centcom), located at Tampa in the State of Florida, is a military headquarter responsible for monitoring US military activities in the Middle East and Central Asia regions.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The Central Command (CENTCOM), located in Florida State Tampa, is the military headquarters responsible for overseeing U.S. military operations in the Middle East and Central Asia.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Central Command (Centcom) in Tampa, Florida, is the military headquarters that oversees U.S. military operations in the Middle East and Central Asia.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>根据一份关于该报告的新闻，“经过中央司令部高级领导者审核的情报对于美国反恐行动的描述比实际情况更乐观，并且始终比其他情报机构的分析更乐观。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">According to news about this report, “intelligence review by high ranking leadership of the United States Central Command gave more optimistic descriptions for US counter-terrorism activities compared to actual situations. The review was also more optimistic compared to analyses carried out by other intelligence agencies.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">According to a report on the news, "the intelligence that has been vetted by senior leaders at the Central Command has been more optimistic about U.S. counterterrorism operations than it is, and has always been more optimistic than the analysis of other intelligence agencies." ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">According to a news release on the report, "Intelligence vetted by senior leadership at Central Command presents a more optimistic picture of U.S. counterterrorism operations than is actually the case, and is consistently more optimistic than other intelligence agencies' analysis."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>加利福尼亚州共和党代表表示：“中央司令部的行为难以令人接受。一边是我们的战士饱受战争之苦，另一边则是高层政策制定者收到错误的分析。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Republican Party representative of the state of California expressed: “The actions of the United States Central Command is hard to accept. Our soldiers are suffering and bearing the brunt of the war while higher ups making the policies are receiving wrong analysis.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">California State Republican representative said: "The Central Command's behavior is difficult to accept." One side is that our warriors are suffering from war, and the other side is the wrong analysis of senior policy makers. ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">"The actions of Central Command are unacceptable," said a Republican representative in California. "On the one hand, our fighters are suffering from the war, and on the other hand, senior policymakers are receiving the wrong analysis."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>中央司令部的领导层问题已延伸到该机构的最高层。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Leadership issues have spread to the highest echelons of the US Central Command.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The leadership issues of the Central Command have been extended to the highest level of the agency.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The question of the leadership of the Central Command has extended to the highest levels of the institution.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>该报告详细指出了2014年和2015年中央司令部在描述和分析美国培训伊拉克军队方面长期存在的问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">The report gave detailed descriptions and analysis of the United States Central Command in 2014 and 2015 for long-term issues regarding US training provided to the Iraqi armed forces.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The report details the long-standing problems of the 2014 and 2015 Central Command in describing and analysing the United States training of Iraqi troops.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The report detailed long-standing problems at Central Command in 2014 and 2015 in describing and analyzing U.S. training of Iraqi forces.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>虽然没有确定性的证据表明，奥巴马政府的高层官员下令更改这些报告，但根据报告的描述，这些分析员感到自己受到了来自中央司令部领导者的压力，迫使他们对伊斯兰国 （ISIS或ISIL) 的威胁发表更乐观的意见。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Although there was no clear evidence to show that senior officials of the Obama administration ordered the reports to be altered, the report said that these analysts felt that they were under pressure from Central Command leaders to portray a more optimistic view of threats from the Islamic State (ISIS or ISIL).</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">While there is no certainty that the Obama administration's top officials have ordered the changes, the analysts feel they are under pressure from Central Command leaders to make them more optimistic about the threat of the Islamic State (ISIS or ISIL), as described in the report.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">While there is no conclusive evidence that senior officials in the Obama administration ordered changes to the reports, the analysts, according to their descriptions, felt pressured by central command leaders to express more optimistic views about the threat from Islamic State (ISIS or ISIL).</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>该报告称，“在2015年上半年，许多中央司令部的新闻稿、声明和国会证言比实际情况要乐观得多。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">The report claimed that “in the first half of 2015, many Central Command press releases, statements and congressional testimonies were significantly more positive than actual events.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">"In the first half of 2015, many Central Command press releases, statements and congressional testimony were much more optimistic than they were," the report said. ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">"In the first half of 2015, many of the Central Command press releases, statements and congressional testimony were much more optimistic than they actually were," the report said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>比如，一名中央司令部的官员公开表示可能最早在2015年4月或5月采取一次大型军事行动夺回摩苏尔。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">For example, a Centcom official stated publicly that a major military assault to take back Mosul could begin as early as April or May 2015.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">For example, a central command official said publicly that it was possible to take a major military operation to retake Mosul as early as April 2015 or May.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">For example, a Central Command official has publicly stated that a major military operation to retake Mosul could take place as early as April or May 2015.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>伊拉克第二大城市摩苏尔目前仍在伊斯兰国的控制之下。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Mosul, the second largest city of Iraq, is currently under the control of the Islamic State.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Almawsil, Iraq's second-largest city, is still under the control of the Islamic State.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Mosul, Iraq's second-largest city, is still under IS control.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>堪萨斯州共和党代表迈克·蓬佩奥在一份声明中表示：“经过数月的调查，这一结果已十分明显。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Kansas Republican Representative Michael Pompeo said in a statement, “After months of investigation, this much is very clear.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">"After months of investigation, the results are clear," The Kansas Republican Representative, Mike Peo, said in a statement. ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">"After months of investigation, the results have been very clear," Mike Pompeo, a Kansas Republican representative, said in a statement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>自2014年中期到2015年中期，美国中央司令部的大部分高层情报官员操控了司令部的情报产品，隐瞒了伊拉克伊斯兰国的威胁。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">From mid-2014 to mid-2015, most senior intelligence officials of the United States Central Command manipulated intelligence products of the Command and covered up threats posed by the Islamic State of Iraq.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Since the middle of 2014 to the middle of 2015, most senior intelligence officers at the U.S. Central Command have manipulated the command's intelligence products, concealing the threat of the Islamic State of Iraq.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">From mid-2014 to mid-2015, most of the top intelligence officials at U.S. Central Command manipulated the command's intelligence products, hiding the threat from ISIS in Iraq.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>共和党在从分析员那里得知有关伊斯兰国的情报被操控后，成立了一个专项工作小组。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">After Republicans learned from analysts that information on the Islamic State was manipulated, they formed a special taskforce.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The Republican Party has set up a special working group to learn from analysts about Islamic intelligence being manipulated.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The Republican Party set up a task force after learning from analysts that intelligence about ISIS was being manipulated.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>随着调查的继续，继周四发布的这篇报告后将会有更多发现。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Along with ongoing investigation, more findings will be forthcoming following the issuance of Thursday’s report.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">As the investigation continues, there will be more discoveries following the report released in Thursday.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">More findings will follow this report, released on Thursday, as the investigation continues.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>国防部总检察长也对中央司令部进行了长期调查。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">The General Counsel of the Department of Defense conducted a long-term investigation of the Central Command.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The attorney general of the Ministry of Defence also conducted a long-term investigation into the central Command.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The Attorney General of the Ministry of Defence has also conducted a lengthy investigation into the Central Command.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="18" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>众议院情报委员会的民主党成员于周四公布了其调查结果，与共和党专项工作小组的部分结论相一致。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Democrat members of the US House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence reported the results of the investigation on Thursday. The results were consistent with parts of the conclusion reached by the Republican Party task force.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Democratic members of the House Intelligence Committee published their findings in Thursday, in line with some of the conclusions of the Republican ad Hoc working group.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Democratic members of the House Intelligence Committee released their findings on Thursday, in line with some of the conclusions of the Republican Task Force.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="19" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>委员会民主党领袖代表谢安达在一份声明中表示：2014年至2015年期间，中央司令部针对伊斯兰国和伊拉克维和部队的情报评估制定了一项过于狭隘的流程。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Adam Schiff, the committee’s Democratic Party leader said in a statement, “Between 2014 and 2015, Centcom created an overly insular process for producing intelligence assessments on ISIL and Iraqi Security Forces.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">In a statement, the committee's Democratic leader, Cheandar, said: "During the period from 2014 to 2015, the Central Command developed an overly narrow process for intelligence assessments of Islamic countries and Iraqi peacekeepers." ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">"Between 2014 and 2015, Central Command developed an overly narrow process for intelligence assessments of Islamic State and Iraqi peacekeeping forces," Xie Anda, a representative of the committee's Democratic leadership, said in a statement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="20" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>谢安达先生表示，该流程“妨碍了情报的发布”、降低了分析员的士气并且“无法接受不同的意见。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Mr Xie Anda said that this process “hindered intelligence disclosure”, lowered the morale of analysts, and “rejected different opinions.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Mr Cheandar says the process "interferes with the release of intelligence", lowers analyst morale and "cannot accept different opinions." ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Mr Sheanda said the process "interfered with the release of intelligence", demoralised analysts and "could not accept different opinions."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="21" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>但谢安达先生与民主党人还表示，他们未发现任何证据能够证明白宫试图给中央司令部的分析员施加压力，从而时他们的结论符合“预设或政治叙事。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Adam Schiff and the democrats also expressed that they did not find any evidence proving the White House tried to press on analysts in the Central Command. It's a way to fit their conclusion with the " preset or political story".</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">But Mr Cheandar and Democrats said they had found no evidence that the White House was trying to put pressure on analysts at the Central Command, and that their conclusions were consistent with "presupposition or political narratives." ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">But Mr. Sheanda and the Democrats also said they had found no evidence that the White House was trying to put pressure on analysts at Central Command, so that their conclusions were consistent with "preconceived or political narratives."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="22" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>《野兽日报》在周二报导了国会调查的初步结果。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">On Tuesday, The Daily Beast reported the results of preliminary investigations by the Congress.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The Beast Daily reported the preliminary results of congressional investigation in Tuesday.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The Beast Daily News reported the preliminary results of the congressional investigation on Tuesday.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="23" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>去年八月，《纽约时报》报导了在收到中央司令部分析员的投诉后，五角大楼总检察长开始进行调查。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Last August, The New York Times reported that the Inspector General of the Pentagon has initiated investigations after receiving complaints from the United States Central Command analysts.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Last August, the New York Times reported that after receiving a complaint from a central Command analyst, the Pentagon attorney general began an investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Last August, the New York Times reported that the Pentagon Attorney General opened an investigation after receiving complaints from analysts at Central Command.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="24" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>五角大楼发言人海军少校帕特里克·埃文斯在一份声明中表示，在总检察长的调查未结束前，国防部不对这份国会报告发表任何评论。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Pentagon spokesperson Navy Lieutenant Commander Patrick Evans said in a statement that the Department of Defense will refrain from making any comments on the congressional report until after the Attorney General has concluded its investigation.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Pentagon spokesman Navy Major 帕特里克·埃文斯 said in a statement that the Pentagon did not comment on the congressional report until the Attorney-General's investigation was completed.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Pentagon spokesman Navy Major Patrick Evans said in a statement that the Defense Department would not comment on the congressional report until the attorney general's investigation is complete.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="25" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>但他表示：“专家有时会对复杂数据的解读产生分歧，而情报机构和国防部鼓励就这些重要的国家安全主题进行健康的对话。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">However, he said, “Experts sometimes disagree when it comes to interpretation of complex data, and intelligence agencies and the Ministry of National Defense encourage healthy dialogue on these important national security topics.”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">But he said: "Experts sometimes disagree over the interpretation of complex data, and intelligence agencies and the Ministry of Defence encourage healthy dialogue on these important national security themes." ”</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">But he said: "Experts sometimes disagree on the interpretation of complex data, while intelligence agencies and the Department of Defense encourage healthy dialogue on these important national security themes."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="26" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>此次调查的影响已超过了美国领导的在伊拉克和叙利亚的轰炸行动是否取得 （越来越多国防部官员所声称的) 成功这一问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">The impact of this investigation has already surpassed the issue of whether the bombing of Iraq and Syria led by the US would be successful (as claimed by an increasing number of Department of Defense officials).</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The impact of the survey exceeded the success of U.S.-led bombing operations in Iraq and Syria, as more and more defense officials claimed.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">The impact of this investigation has outweighed the question of whether the U.S.-led bombing campaign in Iraq and Syria has succeeded, as more and more Defense Department officials claim.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="27" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>但去年，这些主张使公众质疑奥巴马总统可以在多大程度上信任中央司令部所发布的伊拉克、阿富汗、利比亚和其他危机地区的军事行动评估。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Last year however, these assertions have caused the public to question the extent to which President Obama can trust the assessment for military action issued by the Central Common on Iraq, Afganistan, Libya and other areas of crisis.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">But last year, these assertions raised questions about the extent to which President Obama could trust the assessment of military operations in Iraq, Afghanistan, Libya and other crisis areas issued by the Central Command.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">But last year, the claims raised questions about the extent to which President Obama could trust the assessments of military operations in Iraq, Afghanistan, Libya and other crisis areas issued by Central Command.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="28" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>有关伊斯兰国情报的批评令人想起出十多年前的争议，当时中央司令部情报分析员格雷戈里·胡克撰写了一篇研究文章，文中指出乔治·布什的政府不顾众多分析员的反对，坚持派遣小规模的部队前往伊拉克并且几乎没有考虑2003年入侵后的情况。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">The critiques on the Islamic State intelligence mirror disputes of more than a decade ago, when a Centcom intelligence analyst, Gregory Hooker, wrote a research paper saying that the administration of President George W. Bush, over many analysts’ objections, advocated a small force in Iraq and spent little time thinking about what would follow the 2003 invasion.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The criticism of Islamic intelligence was reminiscent of the controversy more than 10 years ago, when Central Command analyst 格雷戈里·胡克 wrote a study that said George Bush's government insisted on sending small troops to Iraq despite the objections of many analysts and gave little consideration to the aftermath of the 2003 invasion.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Criticism of ISIS intelligence is reminiscent of the controversy more than a decade ago, when Central Command intelligence analyst Gregory Hooker wrote a research article stating that George Bush's administration, despite the objections of many analysts, insisted on sending small forces to Iraq and gave little thought to the aftermath of the 2003 invasion.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="29" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>胡克先生在此次关于伊斯兰国情报的反对活动中扮演了关键角色。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Mr. Hooker played an important role in opposing the incident regarding the Islamic State intelligence.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Mr Hooker played a key role in the opposition to intelligence in the Islamic State.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Mr. Hooker played a key role in the campaign against Islamic State intelligence.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="30" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>去年，有官员表示，胡克先生的团队所得出的结论是针对伊斯兰国炼油厂的空袭并未大幅削减恐怖组织的经济收入，因为该恐怖组织建造了临时炼油厂继续在黑市上出售石油，而这与所公布的声明大相径庭。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">Last year, an official expressed that the conclusion reached by Mr. Hook’s team is that air strikes launched against oil refinery facilities of the Islamic State failed to drastically reduce the economic income of the terrorist organization as they had constructed a temporary refinery and continued to sell oil on the black market. This was greatly different from the published statement.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">Last year, officials said Mr. Hooker's team concluded that the air strikes against the Islamic State's refineries did not significantly reduce the economic revenues of terrorist groups, as the terrorist group built a temporary refinery to continue to sell oil on the black market, which was in stark contrast to the announcement.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Last year, officials said Mr. Hooker's team came to the conclusion that airstrikes targeting Islamic State refineries had not significantly cut the economic revenue of the terrorist group, which has built temporary refineries to continue selling oil on the black market, a far cry from the published statement.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="31" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>根据《时代周刊》9月的报道，中央司令部未对外公布这一发现。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">According to a September report in Time magazine, the US Central Command did not disclose this finding to the public.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">According to Time Magazine's September report, the Central Command did not disclose the findings.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Central Command did not release the findings to the public, according to a September report in Time magazine.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="32" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>当多名律师审阅了有关对于战争作出过度乐观评估的参议院证词后，中央司令部指挥官劳埃德·奥斯汀三世去年饱受批评。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">When numerous lawyers reviewed the overly optimistic assessments regarding the war within the testimony given to the Senate, Commander Lloyd James Austin III of the US Central Command came under intense criticisms.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">The commander of Central Command 劳埃德·奥 Austin III was criticized last year after a number of lawyers reviewed the Senate testimony on the overly optimistic assessment of the war.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">Central Command Commander Lloyd Austin III came under fire last year after several lawyers reviewed Senate testimony about an overly optimistic assessment of the war.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="33" doc-id="151_nytimes.69755_en.sl">
    <source>奥斯汀将军于4月退役，目前由约瑟夫·沃特尔接替他在中央司令部的职位。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.ht">General Austin retired from military service in April, and his position as commander of United States Central Command has been succeeded by Joseph Votel.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.gg">General Austin retired in April and is now 约瑟夫·沃特尔 to replace his position at Central Command.</translation>
    <translation system="151_nytimes.69755_en.c6">General Austin retired in April and is currently being replaced by Joseph Votel in his position at Central Command.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
