<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月11日，记者电话采访已回到四川绵阳家中的黄伊琳时，她说：“当时情况太紧急了，我心里只有一个念头就是救人!”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">On August 11, when the reporter’s telephone interview reached Huang Yilin who has returned to her home at Jinyang in Sichuan, she said: “It was an emergency. The only thing I could think of is to rescue people.”</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">August 11, reporter telephone interview has returned to Sichuan Mianyang home in Huang Yilin, she said: "The situation is too urgent, my heart only one idea is to save lives!"</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">"It was so urgent," said Huang Yilin, who returned to her home in Mianyang, Sichuan province, in a telephone interview on August 11. "My only thought was to save people!"</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>黄伊琳是中南林科大风景园林学院2015级的学生。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Huang Yiling is a student of the 2015 cohort of the Landscape Architecture School in the Central South University Forestry and Technology.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Huang Yilin is a 2015-level student at the University of Southern China's landscape architecture.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Eileen Huang is a 2015 student at the School of Landscape Architecture, Central South China University of Science and Technology.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>就读城乡规划专业的黄伊琳想去四川阆中参观学习当地的建筑设计，于是一家人便前往旅游。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Huang Yilin who is now studying the professional field of town and country planning wishes to visit Langzhong in Sichuan to learn about architecture in that region, and thus took the entire family to a trip to that location.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Huang Yilin wants to go to Sichuan Langzhong to visit the local architectural design, so a family will travel.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Huang Yilin, who studies urban and rural planning, wanted to visit Langzhong in Sichuan to learn about local architectural design, so the family went on a trip.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月8日上午10点左右，黄伊琳的父亲在酒店休息，母女俩出来准备逛逛阆中古城。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">At about 10 am on August 8, Huang Yilin’s father was resting at the hotel, while she and her mother were getting ready to wander about Langzhong Ancient City.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">August 8 around 10 o'clock in the morning, Huang Yilin's father in the hotel rest, mother and daughter out to stroll Langzhong ancient city.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">On August 8, around 10 o'clock in the morning, Huang Yilin's father rested in the hotel, the mother and daughter came out to prepare to stroll the Langzhong ancient city.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>刚走了没多远，突然看到一群人在大呼小叫，出于好奇便走上前去。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">After walking for a short distance, they saw a small crowd screaming and yelling, and approached them out of curiosity.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Just walked not far, suddenly saw a group of people yelling, out of curiosity and went forward.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Just go not far away, suddenly see a group of people shouting, out of curiosity and then stepped forward.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>眼看着“小男孩已不见了踪影，小女孩在水里拼命扑腾，江面上只露出她的小脑袋，不时往下沉”，小时候学过游泳的黄伊琳急急忙忙地跳下去救人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Seeing that the “little boy has disappeared and that the little girl is splashing around in the water, with her head bobbing up and down the river water as the water keeps dragging her down”, Huang Yilin, who had learned swimming at a young age, jumped into the water to save the child.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">See "The little boy has disappeared, the little girl in the water desperately flop, the river only reveal her small head, from time to times to sink", as a child learned to swim Huang Yilin hurried to jump down to save people.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Seeing the "little boy has disappeared, the little girl in the water desperately flutter, the river only revealed her little head, from time to time to sink," a child learned to swim Huang Yilin hurriedly jumped down to save people.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>下水后，身高165厘米的黄伊琳发现竟踩不到底!</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">After jumping into the river, 165-meter tall Huang Yilin realized she could not find the bottom!</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">After the water, the height of 165 centimeters Huang Yilin found unexpectedly trample!</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">After entering the water, the 165cm Huang Yilin found that she could not walk to the end of the road!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>之前看上去平静的水面，底下却是激流!</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">The water surface which seemed serene previously hid powerful currents underneath.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Before it looked calm, there was a torrent of water!</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Seemingly calm before the surface of the water, but underneath the torrent!</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>但她还是不顾一切地游向小女孩。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">But she did everything she could to swim toward the little girl.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">But she was still desperate to swim to the little girl.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">But she was still desperate to swim to the little girl.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>黄伊琳说，江水浑浊、湍急，不到5米的距离，几乎花光了她所有的力气。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Huang Yilin said that the river was muddy and rapid. She was almost spent swimming a distance of less than 5 meters.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Huang Yilin said, the River muddy, swift, less than 5 meters away, almost spent all her strength.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Huang said the river was muddy and fast-flowing, less than five meters away and it took almost all her strength.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>她拼尽全力把小女孩推到河堤边，“斜坡特别滑，我怕自己没有力气也沉下去了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">She used her entire strength to push the little girl to the side of the levee. “The slope is so slipper. I thought I might sink when I run out of power.”</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">She tried her best to push the little girl to the riverbank, "the slope was slippery and I was afraid I would not have the strength to sink." ”</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">She pushed the little girl as hard as she could to the bank of the river. "The slope was so slippery that I was afraid I wouldn't have the strength to go down."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>于是，黄伊琳向妈妈求救，听到女儿的呼救，水性不好的尹女士准备下水营救，被旁边的游客拦住。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Huang Yilin therefore cried out to her mother for help. Upon hearing her daughter’s cries, Mdm Yin, who was not a good swimmer, decided to go into the water but was stopped by other swimmers.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">So, Huang Yilin to mother for help, hear her daughter's cry, water poor Ms. Yin ready to rescue, by the next tourists stopped.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">So Huang Yilin asked for help from her mother, heard her daughter's cry for help, and Ms. Yin, who was not in good water, prepared to go into the water to rescue her, and was stopped by the tourists next to her.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月10日，黄伊琳跳江救人的事情传开后，尹女士在收到不少亲友慰问、称赞的同时，也受到不少亲友“问责”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">On August 10, after the story of Huang Yilin leaping into the river to save a girl spread, Mdm Yin received plenty of words of comfort and praise from family members and friends, as well as “blame” from many.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">August 10, Huang Yilin jumped river to save the things spread, Ms. Yin received many relatives and friends condolences, praise, but also by many friends and relatives "accountability."</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">August 10, Huang Yilin jumped into the river to save people after the news spread, Ms. Yin received a lot of friends and family condolences, praise, but also by many friends and family "accountability."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“现在回想起来真的很后怕!说实话，当孩子在河堤上快坚持不下去了，向我求救时，我的心都快碎了。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">" I still feel the linger fear! To tell you the truth, my heart was broken when the kid almost fading on the bank cried out for help.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">"I'm really scared to think about it now!" to tell the truth, when the child on the embankment is not going to go on, to me for help, my heart is almost broken. ”</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">"In retrospect it was really scary! To tell you the truth, my heart broke when the child could hardly hold out on the riverbank and asked for my help."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>尹女士心有余悸地说，尽管很危险，但如果再次置身那样的场景，她依然会支持女儿的选择，她为女儿骄傲!</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Fear still lingered in Mdm Yin’s heart. Despite the dangers, Mdm Yin said that she would still support the choice made by her daughter under such circumstances and felt proud for what she did.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Ms. Yin said, despite the danger, but if again in that scene, she will still support her daughter's choice, she is proud of her daughter!</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Ms. Yin said with fright that even though it was dangerous, she would still support her daughter's choice if she was in a scene like that again, and she was proud of her daughter!</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>由于是被逼的，黄伊琳在学会游泳之后就很少主动再下水了，“没想到这项技能还真派上了用场”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">Huang Yilin seldom took the initiative to go swimming after she learned the skill because she was forced into it. “Who would have thought it would come in handy.”</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">Because it is forced, Huang Yilin after learning to swim rarely take the initiative to go into the water, "did not think of this skill is really useful".</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">Being forced, Huang rarely volunteered to go back into the water after learning to swim, "not expecting the skill to really come in handy."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="17" doc-id="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.sl">
    <source>据黄伊琳班上的班长陈亦暘介绍，黄伊琳是班里公认的“学霸”，而且乐于助人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.ht">According to Huang Yilin's class monitor Chen Yiyang, the class has long regarded Huang Yilin as the “top-scoring student” and knew that she is willing to help others.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.gg">According to Huang Yilin class monitor Chen Yi helioversal Introduction, Huang Yilin is recognized in the class "Couba", and is ready to help others.</translation>
    <translation system="139_ifeng0812.news.49767619_0_zh.c6">According to Huang Yilin's class monitor Chen Yilin, Huang Yilin is recognized as a "school bully" in the class, and is willing to help others.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
