<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>法国法院驳回拆除丛林难民营中商店的请愿书</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">French court rejects petition to dismantle shops in the Jungle refugee camp</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">French court rejects petition to dismantle shops in jungle camps</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">French court rejects petition to demolish shops in Jungle refugee camp</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>法国一家法院驳回了加莱政府意在拆除“丛林”难民营中几十家临时搭建的商店及餐馆的请愿书。该难民营中目前居住着上千名难民。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">A French court rejected the proposal of the Calais government aiming to dismantle dozens of temporary shops and restaurants in the refugee “jungle”. Over a thousand refugees currently reside within this camp.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">A French court has dismissed a petition by the Government of Calais to dismantle dozens of makeshift shops and restaurants in the jungle camp. Thousands of refugees currently reside in the camp.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">A French court has rejected a petition by the Calais government to demolish dozens of makeshift shops and restaurants in the "Jungle" refugee camp, where thousands of refugees are currently living.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>在该法院本周的听证会上，加莱政府辩称法国政府应有权拆除该难民营内总计72间临时搭建的商店。民众在难民营中的这些商店里销售从香烟到能量饮料在内的商品、提供理发服务，还在临时搭建的餐馆中以50美分（40便士）的价格卖茶或以几欧元的价格售卖基本餐点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">During the court hearings of this week, the Calais government argued that the French government has the right to dismantle a total of 72 temporary shops and establishments within the refugee camp. At these stores located within the refugee camps, people could sell cigarettes, energy drinks, and other merchandise, provide haircuts, and even sell tea at 50 US cents (40 pence) or a basic meal for several Euros at temporarily constructed restaurants.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">At the court hearings this week, the government argued that the French government should have the right to dismantle a total of 72 makeshift shops in the camp. People in these stores in the camps sell goods ranging from cigarettes to energy drinks, offer haircuts, and sell tea at 50 cents (40 pence) in makeshift restaurants or selling basic meals at a few euros.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">At a court hearing this week, the Calais government argued that the French government should have the power to dismantle a total of 72 makeshift shops in the camp, where people sell everything from cigarettes to energy drinks, offer haircuts and sell tea for 50 cents (40p) or basic meals for a few euros in makeshift restaurants.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>加莱省长办公室认为这些地方应被拆除，因为它们是不缴税的平行经济，还存在火灾和卫生隐患。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">The Calais prefect’s office believed that these places should be dismantled because they were a non-tax paying parallel economy. They were also fire and hygiene risks.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">The Office of the District of Calais believes these places should be dismantled because they are parallel economies that do not pay taxes, as well as fire and health hazards.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">The Office of the Governor of Calais believes that these places should be demolished because they are a parallel economy that does not pay taxes, and there are fire and health hazards.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>人道主义团体却对法院表示这些商店和餐馆极为重要，因为国家支持的协会及其他团体所提供的免费食物根本无法满足该难民营不断增长的难民的需求。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">However, humanitarian groups expressed to the court that these stores and restaurants are especially important because the free food provided by associations sponsored by public agencies and other groups is unable to meet the needs of the growing number of refugees within the camp.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">Humanitarian groups have indicated to the court that these shops and restaurants are of paramount importance, as the free food provided by state-backed associations and other groups simply cannot meet the needs of the growing refugee population in the camp.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">Humanitarian groups, however, told the Court that the shops and restaurants were extremely important because the free food provided by State-sponsored associations and other groups simply did not meet the needs of the growing number of refugees in the camp.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>他们称，这些临时搭建的商店和餐馆经常为有需要之人提供庇护所及免费食物。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">They claimed that these shops and restaurants that are temporarily constructed are to provide shelter and free food for the needy.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">These makeshift shops and restaurants often provide shelters and free food for those in need, they say.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">They claim the makeshift shops and restaurants often provide shelter and free food for those in need.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>里尔一家法院裁定，没有法律依据来驱逐这72间临时商店的经营者，但表示加莱省长的担忧“完全可以理解”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">A court in Lille ruled that there was no legal basis for evicting the operators of the 72 temporary stores but said that the concern of the governor of Calais was “completely understandable”.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">A court in Lille ruled that there was no legal basis to expel the operators of the 72 temporary shops, but said the concerns of the governor of Calais were "fully understandable".</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">A court in Lille ruled that there was no legal basis to evict the operators of the 72 temporary stores, but said the governor of Calais's concerns were "perfectly understandable."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>Jean·François Molla 法官表示，这些杂货店、咖啡馆及餐馆的作用远不止简单地向那些“生活在极其危险条件下”的难民提供食物。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">Judge Jean·François Molla said that the role of these grocery stores, cafés and restaurants were far from simply providing food to the refugees who were “living in extremely precarious conditions".</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">Jean· Judge François Molla says the role of these grocery stores, cafes and restaurants is much more than simply providing food to refugees who "live in extremely dangerous conditions".</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">Judge Jean François Molla said the role of the grocers, cafes and restaurants went far beyond simply providing food to refugees who were "living in extremely dangerous conditions."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>他说，这些地方是难民和志愿者之间平静的汇合点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">He said that some places are peaceful gathering locations for refugees and volunteers.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">These places, he says, are a calming point of convergence between refugees and volunteers.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">These places, he said, were a peaceful meeting point between refugees and volunteers.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>其中一个遭到拆除威胁的地方就是该难民营的“Jungle Book Kids”咖啡馆，该非营利性小店每天提供200份食物、英语及法语课，还为该难民营中数百名无人陪伴的弱势未成年人提供庇护建议。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">One of the areas threatened with dismantling is the Jungle Book Kids coffee house in the refugee camp. This non-profit vendor provides 200 meals a day, lessons in English and French, and provide sheltering consultation for hundreds of underprivileged youths within the refugee camp.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">One of the threats to demolition was the "Jungle Book Kids" Café in the camp, which offered 200 servings of food, English and French lessons each day, as well as advice on asylum for hundreds of of the less-than-vulnerable minors in the camp.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">One of the sites threatened with demolition is the camp's "Jungle Book Kids" cafe, which provides 200 meals a day, English and French lessons, as well as shelter advice for hundreds of unaccompanied vulnerable minors in the camp.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>170000多人签署了请愿书来保护这间咖啡馆。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">More than 170,000 individuals signed a petition to preserve the coffee house.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">More than 170,000 people have signed petitions to protect the café.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">More than 170,000 people signed a petition to protect the café.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>一封给《卫报》(Guardian) 的信中写道，关闭这间咖啡馆“将是这些儿童（很多儿童只有八岁）的一场大灾难。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">In a letter to the Guardian, closing this coffee house “will be a major disaster to these children (many of whom are only eight years old).”</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">The closure of the café "will be a catastrophe for these children (many children are only eight years old)," wrote a letter to the Guardian (Guardian). ”</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">A letter to the Guardian wrote that closing the cafe "would be a major disaster for these children, many of whom are as young as eight."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="092_guardian.128016_en.sl">
    <source>Help Refugees 和 L'Auberge des Migrants 这两家慈善组织周五预计，丛林难民营中的难民数量已突破9000，这也是继夏季难民人数激增以来的最高水平。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.ht">The two charity organizations of Help Refugees and L'Auberge des Migrants estimated on Friday that the number of refugees in the Jungle refugee camp has reached 9,000, the highest figure on the records since the number of refugees exploded after summer.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.gg">Help refugees and L ' Auberge des migrants, two charitable organizations, estimated in Friday that the number of refugees in the jungle camps had exceeded 9000, the highest level since the summer refugee population surged.</translation>
    <translation system="092_guardian.128016_en.c6">The charity Help Refugees and L'Auberge des Migrants on Friday predicted the number of refugees in the Jungle camp had topped 9,000, the highest level since the summer surge.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
