<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>国家发展改革委产业协调司负责人今天在此间指出，钢铁产能过剩是全球性问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The head of the Department of Industry Coordination of the National Development and Reform Commission pointed out today that overcapacity in the steel industry was a global issue.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The head of the Industry coordination Division of the National Development and Reform Commission said here today that overcapacity in steel is a global problem.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The head of the Industrial Coordination Department of the National Development and Reform Commission said here today that steel overcapacity is a global problem.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>我国近年产能利用率均高于全球平均水平，也高于美欧等国家和地区。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">Production capacity utilization in our country is higher than that of the global average, and higher than those in the US and Europe.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">In recent years, China's capacity utilization rate is higher than the global average level, but also higher than the United States and Europe and other countries and regions.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">In recent years, China's capacity utilization rate is higher than the global average and higher than the United States and Europe and other countries and regions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>我国已经采取坚决有效的措施化解过剩产能，而且成效正在逐步显现。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">Our country has taken definite and effective measures to address excess production capacity, and preliminary results are gradually emerging.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">Our country has taken resolute and effective measures to resolve excess capacity, and the effectiveness is gradually emerging.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">China has taken resolute and effective measures to eliminate excess capacity, and the results are gradually emerging.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>该负责人指出，对钢铁产能过剩这一全球性问题，党中央国务院高度重视。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The person-in-charge pointed out that the State Council of the People's Republic of China has placed great importance upon the global issue of excessive steel and iron production capacity.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The Director noted that the Central Committee of the State Council attaches great importance to the global problem of overcapacity in steel.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The person in charge pointed out that the party Central Committee and the State Council attach great importance to the global problem of excess steel production capacity.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>各部门、各地区积极贯彻落实国务院部署，认真开展工作，今年要压减粗钢产能4500万吨左右。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">All departments and regions shall actively implement the plans of State Council, and work conscientiously to reduce crude steel production capacity by about 45 million tonnes this year.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">Departments, regions actively implement the State Council deployment, serious work, this year to reduce crude steel production capacity of about 45 million tons.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">Various departments and regions have actively implemented the State Council's plan and carried out serious work to reduce crude steel production capacity by about 45 million tons this year.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>从我国国情出发，我国并不鼓励钢材出口，相反，还采取一系列切实措施控制钢材出口。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">From the perspective of domestic national conditions, China does not encourage steel exports. On the contrary, it has adopted a series of practical measures to control steel exports.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">From China's national conditions, China does not encourage steel exports, on the contrary, also take a series of practical measures to control the export of steel.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">Proceeding from China's national conditions, China does not encourage steel exports, on the contrary, it has also taken a series of practical measures to control steel exports.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>这位负责人强调，钢铁产品国际贸易本质上讲是市场行为，是源于进口国需求、消费者综合考虑产品性价比等因素后的自主选择。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The person in charge emphasized that the international trade of steel products is essentially market behavior. It is triggered by demand from importing nations, as well as the voluntary choice of consumers after taking into consideration a number of factors such as the products’ price-performance ratio.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The person in charge stressed that the international trade in steel products is essentially market behavior, which is based on the demand of the importing country and the consumers ' independent choice after considering the price ratio of products.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The official stressed that international trade in steel products is essentially a market behavior, is derived from the importing country demand, consumers comprehensive consideration of product value for money and other factors after the independent choice.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>实施贸易保护措施无助于从根本上解决全球钢铁产业的发展问题，相反，只会对国际贸易秩序造成进一步冲击。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The implementation of protectionist measures will not help to fundamentally resolve the development issues of the global steel industry. Instead, this would only result in a further attack on international trade order.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The implementation of trade protection measures does not help to fundamentally solve the global steel industry development problems, on the contrary, will only cause further impact on the international trade order.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The implementation of trade protection measures will not help to fundamentally solve the problem of the development of the global steel industry, on the contrary, it will only cause further impact on the international trade order.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>在谈到债务时，该负责人强调，化解债务问题是化解过剩产能过程中需要妥善处理好的重要问题。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">When talking about the debt, the person-in-charge emphasized that the key for resolving the debt issue is to properly take care of excessive production capacity.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">When it comes to debt, the person in charge stressed that resolving the debt problem is an important issue that needs to be properly handled in the process of resolving excess capacity.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">When talking about debt, the chief stressed that resolving the debt problem is an important issue that needs to be properly handled in the process of resolving excess capacity.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>由于钢铁企业资产规模大，涉及面广，一些企业的债务关系复杂，如果处置不当，有可能引发区域性风险。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">As steel enterprises have massive assets, and cover a broad spectrum, the debt relationships of some of these enterprises are complicated. If handled inappropriately, regional risk could result.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">Because of the large scale of the iron and steel enterprise assets, involving a wide range, some enterprises debt relationship is complex, if improper disposal, it is possible to trigger regional risk.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">Due to the large scale and wide range of assets of steel enterprises, the debt relationship of some enterprises is complex, and it is possible to trigger regional risks if not handled properly.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>据该负责人介绍，近年来，随着经济下行压力加大，社会总需求逐步减弱，部分行业产能利用率下降，企业生产经营困难加大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The person in charge described that recent increase in economic pressures have led to weakening of overall demands from the society. Production capacity utilization for a number of industries have decreased, increasing the difficulties for corporate production and operations.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">According to the director of the introduction, in recent years, with the economic downward pressure, the overall social demand gradually weakened, some industry capacity utilization decreased, the production and operation of enterprises to increase difficulties.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">In recent years, as downward pressure on the economy has increased, aggregate demand in society has gradually weakened, capacity utilization rates in some sectors have declined and enterprises have greater difficulties in production and operation, according to the chief.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>一些企业不适应市场环境变化，生产经营难以为继甚至濒临倒闭，但受一些体制机制因素制约，以市场化方式退出的障碍较多，成为“僵尸企业”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">Some enterprises were unable to adapt to changes in the market environment. Business operations became unsustainable, and were even on the brink of collapse. Constrained by institutional mechanisms however, there were more hindrances to market-oriented exits, resulting in “zombie enterprises”.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">Some enterprises do not adapt to the changes in the market environment, production and operation is difficult or even close to collapse, but by some institutional mechanism constraints, to market-oriented exit obstacles more, become "zombie enterprises."</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">Some enterprises do not adapt to changes in the market environment, production and operation is difficult to sustain or even close down, but subject to some institutional and institutional factors, there are more obstacles to exit in a market-oriented way and become "zombie enterprises."</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>这类企业的存在，扭曲了市场信号，降低了要素资源利用效率，增加了社会管理成本，妨碍了公平竞争市场环境的建立。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The existence of such enterprises distorted market signals, lowered the utilization rate of factor resources, increased the cost of public administration, and hindered the building of a fair and competitive market environment.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The existence of such enterprises distorts the market signal, reduces the efficiency of factor resource utilization, increases the cost of social management and hinders the establishment of a fair competition market environment.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The existence of such enterprises distorts market signals, reduces the efficiency of factor resource utilization, increases the cost of social management and hinders the establishment of a level playing field.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>导致亏损的主要原因与全球钢铁行业面临的困境一样——市场需求不振、产能利用率低。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The major reason for the losses is similar to the difficulty confronting the global steel industry - market demand is sluggish and capacity utilization rates are low.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The main cause of the losses is the same as the global steel industry's woes – sluggish market demand and low capacity utilization.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The main reasons for the losses are the same as those faced by the global steel industry - weak market demand and low capacity utilisation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="15" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>我国主要采取市场机制、经济手段和法治办法，政府主要是做好职工兜底和社会稳定工作，保证公平公正的市场秩序。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">Our nation mainly adopts a market mechanism, economic means and the rule of law. The government is primarily focused on carrying out various aspects of worker resettlement and social stability, ensuring fair and just market order.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">China mainly adopts market mechanism, economic means and rule by law, the Government mainly completes the work of reveals and social stability and ensures fair and impartial market order.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">Our country mainly adopts the market mechanism, economic means and the method of rule of law, and the government mainly does a good job in the work of the bottom line and social stability of the staff and workers to ensure a fair and just market order.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="16" doc-id="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.sl">
    <source>这位负责人强调，下一步，要坚定不移继续抓好去产能工作，确保完成5年化解粗钢产能1亿~1.5亿吨的目标任务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.ht">The person in charge emphasized that the next step forward would be to steadfastly continue to eliminate excess production capacity, and to ensure that the goal of removing 100 million to 150 million tonnes of crude steel capacity in five years would be achieved.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.gg">The person in charge stressed that the next step is to unswervingly continue to work on capacity to ensure that the 5-year-old crude steel production capacity of 100 million ~ 500 million tons of target tasks.</translation>
    <translation system="050_sina0812.news.doc-ifxuxnah3264113_zh.c6">The person in charge stressed that the next step is to continue to work hard to ensure the completion of the five-year target of 100 million to 150 million tons of crude steel production capacity.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
