<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.sl">
    <source>里瓦斯市长维尔弗雷多·洛佩斯在教师培训现场表示尼加拉瓜政府各机构正在通力协作，与HKND集团一起推进环境管理计划并开展植树活动。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.ht">At the teachers’ training site, Mayor of Rivas Wilfredo Lopez said that all Nicaraguan government entities are working together with HKND to jointly advance the environmental management program, and to embark on afforestation activities.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.gg">Rivas Mayor 维尔弗雷多·洛佩斯 on the teacher training site, the Nicaraguan government agencies are working together to promote environmental management plans and tree planting activities with the HKND group.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.c6">The Mayor of Rivas, Wilfredo López, said at the teacher training site that the Nicaraguan government agencies were working together with the HKND Group to promote environmental management plans and tree planting activities.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.sl">
    <source>作为运河项目开发商的HKND集团始终遵循国际最佳惯例，按国际标准修建运河，最大限度地保护尼加拉瓜的生态环境。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.ht">As the canal developer, HKND Group continued to observe international best practice, and constructed the canal according to international standards, protecting Nicaragua’s ecological environment as much as possible.”</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.gg">The HKND Group, a developer of the canal project, has always adhered to international best practices, built canals in accordance with international standards, and protected Nicaragua's ecological environment to the maximum. ”</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.c6">The HKND Group, as the developer of the canal project, has always followed international best practices and built the canal in accordance with international standards in order to maximize the protection of Nicaragua's ecological environment. "</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.sl">
    <source>大学生通过理论和实践结合，带领中小学生一起种树，教育尼加拉瓜下一代如何绿化环境。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.ht">University students, by combining theory and practice, led secondary and primary school students to plant trees, teaching the next generation of Nicaraguans about afforestation and how to go green.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.gg">Through the combination of theory and practice, college students will lead primary and secondary students to plant trees together to educate the next generation on how to greening the Nicaraguan environment.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.c6">Through a combination of theory and practice, university students lead primary and secondary school students to plant trees together to educate the next generation of Nicaraguan how to green the environment.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.sl">
    <source>尼加拉瓜国立农业大学自然资源和环境系的教授弗朗西斯科·雷耶斯全程带队参与了植树造林教育项目。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.ht">National Agrarian University (Nicaragua) Faculty of Natural Resources and Environment Professor Francisco Reyes led a team to participate in an afforestation education project.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.gg">Professor 弗朗西斯科·雷耶斯 of the Natural Resources and Environment Department of the National Agricultural University of Nicaragua participated in the afforestation education project.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.c6">Francisco Reyes, a professor in the Department of Natural Resources and the Environment at the National Agricultural University of Nicaragua, led the team throughout the project.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.sl">
    <source>我们有理由相信同样由HKND集团主导的跨洋大运河项目将会为广大尼加拉瓜人民带来更多的裨益，为当地创造更多的就业机会。”</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.ht">We have reasons to believe that the transoceanic canal project led by the HKND Group will benefit the people of Nicaragua immensely and provide more employment opportunities in the region.”</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.gg">We have reason to believe that the trans-Oceanic Grand Canal Project, which is also dominated by the HKND group, will bring more benefits to the Nicaraguan people and create more job opportunities for the local community. ”</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.c6">"We have reason to believe that the Grand Canal project, also led by the HCND Group, will bring more benefits to the Nicaraguan people and create more jobs there," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.sl">
    <source>为了保证植树造林的长期效果，HKND集团还出品了植树造林培训画册，分发给里瓦斯省所有1.5万中小学生，旨在为师生及家长提供长期的技术指导。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.ht">To ensure long-term benefits of tree planting and reforestation programs, HKND Group also released an illustrated book with tree planting and reforestation training that was given to 15,000 junior-high and elementary school students of Rivas. The aim is to provide students, teachers, and parents with long-term technical guidance.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.gg">In order to ensure the long-term effect of afforestation, HKND Group also produced the afforestation Training album, distributed to all 15,000 primary and secondary school students in Rivas Province, in order to provide long-term technical guidance for teachers, students and parents.</translation>
    <translation system="011_ifeng0812.news.49767544_1_zh.c6">In order to ensure the long-term effects of afforestation, the HKND Group has also produced a training booklet on afforestation, which has been distributed to all 15,000 primary and secondary school students in Rivas province, with the aim of providing long-term technical guidance to teachers, students and parents.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
