<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.sl">
    <source>“环境问题表现在大气、水、土壤污染上，但根子还是在生产生活方式上”。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.ht">“Environmental problems are reflected in air, water, and soil pollution but are ultimately rooted in production methods and lifestyle.”</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.gg">"Environmental problems are manifested in the atmosphere, water, soil pollution, but the root is still in the production lifestyle."</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.c6">"Environmental problems manifest themselves in air, water and soil pollution, but the roots are still in the way of production and life," he said.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.sl">
    <source>例如，2015年江苏省土地开发度高达21%，位列全国省、自治区最高。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.ht">For example, in 2015, the extent of land development in Jiangsu Province was 21%, the highest among all provinces and autonomous regions in the country.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.gg">For example, 2015, Jiangsu Province, land development rate of up to 21%, ranked highest in the national provinces and autonomous regions.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.c6">In 2015, for example, land development in Jiangsu Province reached 21 per cent, the highest in the country's provinces and autonomous regions.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.sl">
    <source>因此，高污染、大能源、多占地的问题还没有从生产生活方式转变上得到根本性应对。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.ht">Therefore, there has been a lack of radical response to issues pertaining to heavy pollution, big energy and large land coverage in terms of a change in production methods and lifestyle.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.gg">As a result, the problem of high pollution, large energy and land occupation has not been fundamentally addressed in the transformation of production lifestyles.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.c6">As a result, the problems of high pollution, large energy sources, and more land occupation have not been fundamentally addressed from the shift in production and life style.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.sl">
    <source>一方面，从江苏省各级各类生态环境创建成效来看，以绝对优势位居全国首位；但另一方面，资源环境承载压力大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.ht">On the one hand, based on the results of the establishment of various levels and types of ecological environment in Jiangsu Province, it ranks first on an overwhelming basis. On the other hand, however, the resource environment in under significant pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.gg">On the one hand, from all kinds of ecological environment in Jiangsu Province to create results, the absolute advantage ranked first in the country, but on the other hand, the resource environment carrying pressure.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.c6">On the one hand, Jiangsu Province at all levels of the effectiveness of various types of ecological environment to create, with absolute superiority in the first place in the country; but on the other hand, the resources and environment bearing pressure.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.sl">
    <source>扎实推进生态环境保护和治理，需要从根本上推进生产生活方式转变，以生态文明建设促转型惠民生。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.ht">Effective promotion of ecological conservation and governance requires a fundamental transformation of production methods and lifestyles. An ecological and civilized approach to development can promote and benefit everyday life.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.gg">To promote eco-environmental protection and governance, we need to radically promote the transformation of the production life style and promote the transformation of the ecological civilization.</translation>
    <translation system="067_ifeng0812.news.49764389_0_zh.c6">To promote the protection and treatment of ecological environment in a down-to-earth manner, it is necessary to fundamentally advance the transformation of production and life style and promote the transformation of people's lives through the construction of ecological civilization.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
