<set id="zhen_hp" source-language="zh" target-language="en">
  <seg id="1" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>云南省首届青运会13日开赛开幕式打民族牌展示青春活力</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Opening Ceremony on the 13th for the first Youth Games of Yunnan Province to display ethnic and youth energies</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">Yunnan Province first Green games 13th opening ceremony playing the national card display youth Vigor</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">The opening ceremony of the first Youth Games in Yunnan Province on the 13th played the national brand to display the youthful vitality</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="2" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>云南省首届青少年运动会将于8月13日至8月22日在德宏州芒市举行。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Yunnan Province’s inaugural Youth Games will be held in Mangshi, Dehong Prefecture, from August 13 to August 22.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">The first youth games in Yunnan Province will be held in Dehong Mangshi from August 13 to August 22.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">Yunnan Province's first Youth Games will be held from August 13 to August 22 in Mangshi, Dehong Prefecture.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="3" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>8月12日，在德宏州芒市，组委会召开新闻发布会，介绍大赛的组织和开幕式筹备情况。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">The organizing committee held a press conference at Mang City in Dehong Prefecture on August 12 to introduce the organization of the event and the state of preparations for the opening ceremony.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">August 12, in Dehong Mangshi, the organizing Committee held a press conference to introduce the organization of the contest and preparations for the opening ceremony.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">On August 12, in Mangshi, Dehong Prefecture, the organizing committee held a press conference to introduce the organization of the competition and the preparations for the opening ceremony.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="4" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>云南省第一届青少年运动会由云南省体育局主办，芒市人民政府承办，运动会将于13日上午举行开幕式。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">The first Youth Games of Yunnan Province is organized by the Yunnan Bureau of Sports with the support of Mangshi People’s Government. The opening ceremony of the Games will be held in the morning of 13th day of the month.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">Yunnan Province, the first youth sports games by the Yunnan Provincial Sports Bureau, Mangshi People's government, the Games will be held on the morning of 13th opening ceremony.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">The first Youth Games in Yunnan Province will be hosted by the Yunnan Provincial Sports Bureau and sponsored by the Mang Municipal People's Government. The opening ceremony of the Games will be held on the morning of the 13th.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="5" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>比赛共设有田径、足球、篮球、网球、排球、举重、自行车、摔跤、体操、武术等11个项目，涉及180个小项的比赛。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">The Games will include 180 competitions divided into 11 events, including track and field, football, basketball, tennis, volleyball, weight-lifting, cycling, wrestling, gymnastics, and martial arts.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">The competition includes 11 items, including track and field, football, basketball, tennis, volleyball, weightlifting, cycling, wrestling, gymnastics and martial arts, involving 180 small competitions.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">The competition has 11 sports, including athletics, football, basketball, tennis, volleyball, weightlifting, cycling, wrestling, gymnastics and martial arts.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="6" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>云南省第一届青运会组委会副主任、省体育局副局长常林介绍，围绕“政府主导、市场运作、节俭办赛”的原则，目前，各项筹备工作已全部到位。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Chang Lin, deputy chairperson of the organizing committee of the first Youth Games and deputy director of the Yunnan Bureau of Sports, introduced the principles based upon “government leadership, market operations, and cost reduction in event organization”. Currently, all preparation tasks are in place.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">Changlin, deputy director of the organizing committee of the first Youth Games in Yunnan province, and vice secretary of the Provincial Sports Bureau, introduced the principle of "government-led, market-operation and thrift-run", and all the preparatory work was in place.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">At present, all the preparatory work has been put in place around the principle of "government-led, market operation and thrift-saving competition," said Chang Lin, deputy director of the organizing committee of the first Youth Games in Yunnan Province and deputy director of the Provincial Sports Bureau.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="7" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>德宏州老体协举重馆和武术馆、芒市一小摔跤馆、银塔景区山地自行车赛道等修缮工作已完成。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Renovation works at the Dehong Prefecture old sports association weightlifting and wushu gymnasiums, Mangshi First Elementary wrestling arena, and Yinta Scenic Area mountain biking trail have been completed.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">Dehong Old league Weightlifting Hall and martial arts Hall, Mangshi a small wrestling hall, the Silver Tower scenic mountain bike track and other repair work has been completed.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">Dehong state old sports association weightlifting hall and martial arts hall, Mangshi a small wrestling hall, silver pagoda scenic mountain bike track repair work has been completed.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="8" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>在赛事保障方面，目前大会招募了580名志愿者，在比赛期间，这些志愿者们将在各个赛场为运动员和观众提供热情服务。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">To secure proper services to the event, a total of 580 volunteers have been recruited. During the course of the competition, these volunteers will provide athletes as well as the audience at every event venue with great services.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">At the event, the Conference has recruited 580 volunteers, who will provide enthusiastic service to athletes and spectators at various venues during the tournament.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">In terms of event security, the General Assembly has now recruited 580 volunteers who will provide enthusiastic service to athletes and spectators at various venues during the competition.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="9" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>同时，从德宏州各医院抽调70名医务人员和11辆救护车组成了11个医疗队，负责比赛现场和运动员住宿的医疗保障工作。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Meanwhile, the Dehong Autonomous Prefecture assembled 11 teams including 70 medical staff and 11 ambulances to guarantee the medical service during the game and in the accommodation area.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">At the same time, 70 medical staff and 11 ambulances were deployed from Dehong hospitals to form 11 medical teams, which were responsible for the health care of the competition site and the athletes ' accommodation.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">At the same time, 70 medical staff and 11 ambulances were deployed from hospitals in Dehong to form 11 medical teams, which were responsible for the medical care of the competition site and the athletes' accommodation.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="10" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>涉及开闭幕式的问题，本届青运会的点火仪式结合了云南少数民族的传统运动特点，将展示丰富的云南文化内涵。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">As regards issues concerning the opening and closing ceremonies, the lighting ceremony of this Youth Games will incorporate the traditional sports features of Yunnan’s ethnic minorities, and display the rich cultural attributes of Yunnan.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">Related to the opening and closing ceremonies, the celebration of the ceremony combined with the traditional characteristics of Yunnan minority nationalities, will show the rich cultural connotations of Yunnan.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">When it comes to the opening and closing ceremonies, the ignition ceremony of the current Youth Games combines the traditional sports characteristics of Yunnan's ethnic minorities and will showcase the rich cultural connotations of Yunnan.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="11" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>目前为准备开幕式文艺演出，共抽调了德宏职业学院1500名学生演员以及其他专业演员共计2000余人。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Currently, to prepare for the cultural performance for the opening ceremony, a total of 1,500 students from Dehong Vocational College and 2,000 other professional performers have been mobilized.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">At present, in preparation for the opening ceremony of theatrical performances, a total of 1500 students from the Dehong Vocational College and other professional actors, the total of more than 2000 people.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">At present, in preparation for the opening ceremony of the theatrical performances, a total of 1500 students Dehong Vocational College actors and other professional actors a total of more than 2000 people.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="12" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>开闭幕式将全面融入云南元素，德宏特色，展示德宏州芒市的地域文化和民俗风物特点。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">The opening and closing ceremonies will fully integrate elements of Yunnan and the characteristics of Dehong, showcasing the regional and folk cultural landscapes of Mang City in Dehong Prefecture.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">The opening and closing ceremonies will be fully integrated into the elements of Yunnan, and the characteristics of Dehong Mangshi regional culture and folklore.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">Opening and closing ceremony will be fully integrated into the elements of Yunnan, Dehong characteristics, show Dehong Mangshi regional culture and folk customs characteristics.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="13" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>目前，开幕式的彩排工作已结束，明天上午将举行正式演出。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">Rehearsals for the opening ceremony have been concluded. Actual performances will be given tomorrow morning.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">At present, the opening ceremony of the rehearsal work is over, tomorrow morning will be a formal performance.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">The rehearsal for the opening ceremony is now over and there will be an official performance tomorrow morning.</translation>
  </seg>
  <seg id="14" doc-id="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.sl">
    <source>本届青运会开幕式文艺演出相对以往而言规模更大。</source>
    <reference>NA</reference>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.ht">The opening ceremony cultural performance of this Youth Games offers a larger scale compared to the previous events.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.gg">The opening ceremony of the green Games is a larger scale than ever before.</translation>
    <translation system="084_ifeng0812.news.49767662_0_zh.c6">The opening ceremony of the Youth Olympic Games was on a larger scale than ever before.</translation>
  </seg>
</set>
